<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 08:27:53 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Create the Future Now! MEAP Early Access Program Books and liveProjects by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/create-future-now-meap-early-access-program-books-and-liveprojects-manning-books</link>
      <description>Create the future now with Python</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills of the future and beyond with the latest Humble Tech Learning Bundle. This comprehensive library of early access program books and liveProjects courses is designed to help you master Multifunctional Enterprise Application Platforms (MEAP) with lessons like <em>Python Workout, Second Edition</em>, <em>Secrets of the JavaScript Ninja, Third Edition</em>, and more. Start a new career using AI, Python, and more today—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the charity of your choice.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Master’s Guild Top Content from the D&amp;D Community</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dungeon-masters-guild-bestselling-tabletop-dd-community-books</link>
      <description>Jump-start your next campaign</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your party and unleash the full might of Dungeons & Dragons with this ultimate D&D accessories bundle! Forged in partnership with the Dungeon Masters Guild and authorized by Wizards of the Coast, this legendary collection spills over with challenging adventures, groundbreaking rule expansions, and must-have player options. Brave sprawling modern epics like <em>Call From the Deep</em> and <em>The Haunt</em>, or level up your campaign with treasure troves of character options from <em>Xanathar’s Lost Notes to Everything Else</em>. Whether you’re a shapeshifting Druid, relentless Barbarian, or iron-willed Monk, this bundle is a veritable loot table of D&D treasures. Expand your table, ignite your imagination, and join the fight for good — every purchase supports Extra Life! <br><br><a style="color: #EF9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through two partners: some on DriveThruRPG, and some with Roll20.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Tabletop RPGs, Worldbuilding, and Folklore by Adams Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-guide-to-tabletop-rpgs-worldbuilding-and-folklore-adams-media-books</link>
      <description>Level up your TTRPG life-stats (+10)</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add new tabletop RPG skills, techniques, and knowledge to your gaming toolbelt with the all-new Humble Book Bundle: The Ultimate Guide to Tabletop RPGs, Worldbuilding, and Folklore. This massive library of curated titles from Adams Media is perfect for TTRPG mega-fans and newcomers alike. Discover exciting insights from ebooks like <em>Ultimate RPG Game Master's Guide</em>, <em>Norse Mythology: The Gods, Goddesses, and Heroes Handbook</em>, and more. Level up your TTRPG life-stats (+10) and help support Worldreader with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Infrastructure and DevOps Toolkit by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cloud-infrastructure-and-devops-toolkit-packt-books</link>
      <description>Live in the clouds with AWS &amp; Azure</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become a 21st-century superstar with the latest Humble Tech Book Bundle: Cloud Infrastructure and DevOps Toolkit. Learn the intricacies of Amazon Web Services with industry-leading courses like <em>AWS for Solutions Architects</em> and <em>AWS Cloud Projects</em>—master Microsoft Azure with professional-quality lessons like <em>Hands-On MLOps on Azure</em> and <em>Azure for Developers</em>. This comprehensive library includes lessons, practice tests, and resources perfect for novices and seasoned professionals alike—build strong foundations in cloud infrastructure and help support No Kid Hungry with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate C++ Developer Masterclass by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-c-developer-masterclass-packt-books</link>
      <description>Get smart in C++</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master the ultimate high-performance, general-purpose programming language with our C++ lessons bundle from the experts at Packt. C++ supports multiple programming paradigms—including procedural, object-oriented, and generic programming—making it the perfect starting point for your journey as a developer. Learn from top-rated courses like <em>C++ Memory Management</em>, <em>C++ in Embedded Systems</em>, <em>Asynchronous Programming with C++</em>, and more. Elevate your C++ skills and help support The Global FoodBanking Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martha Wells&#39; Murderbot and More by TOR</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/martha-wells-murderbot-and-more-tor-books</link>
      <description>Martha Wells&#39; Murderbot &amp; More</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fall for the series that inspired the Apple TV+ hit with the all-new Martha Wells' Murderbot & More Bundle! Wells' Murderbot Diaries series tells the on-going story of an artificial Security Unit that hacks its governor module, enabling it to rebel against its programming. Unlike most constructs, Murderbot just wants to be left alone to stream the tens of thousands of hours of streaming media it's downloaded to its memory banks. But as much as it wants to avoid the human drama around it, Murderbot just keeps getting dragged back in. <br><br>This multi-Hugo Award-winning series includes standout titles like <em>All Systems Red</em> and <em>Artificial Condition</em>. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support World Central Kitchen.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Godzilla X Kong: Tales from the Monsterverse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/godzilla-x-kong-tales-from-monsterverse-books</link>
      <description>The Godzilla x Kong comic takeover </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The gloves are off in this battle of monstrous beasts—who will claim victory? Explore the must-see battles between Godzilla and King Kong with the latest Comics Bundle: Tales From the Monsterverse! These legendary titans headline a mighty collection of hot comics like <em>Godzilla x Kong: The Hunted</em>, <em>Godzilla Awakening</em>, <em>Godzilla Aftershock</em>, and more. Pay what you want to read standout titles and help support The American Civil Liberties Union with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture 2025 by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-architecture-2025-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Software architecture made easy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your skills in software architecture with the latest Humble Tech Book Bundle. Unlock hundreds of hours of valuable information inside this 25 course library. Gain expert insights from professional-quality lessons like <em>Cloud Application Architecture Patterns</em>, <em>Facilitating Software Architecture</em>, and more—pay what you want to deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The New Frontier of Comics from DSTLRY</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/new-frontier-comics-from-dstlry-books</link>
      <description>Refined comics from DSTLRY</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expand your personal library and explore the rich worlds and captivating stories of DSTLRY with the all-new New Frontier of Comics Bundle! This 25+ comic collection features <em>Somna</em>, <em>Gone</em>, <em>Spectregraph</em>, and more from one of the medium’s freshest indie publishers. DSTLRY is creator-owned, offers awesome limited-edition runs, and focuses on digital distribution. Lose yourself in this expansive library and help support BINC with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamite&#39;s Red Sonja! 20 Years of Comics!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dynamites-red-sonja-20-years-comics-books</link>
      <description>Swords, sorcery &amp; sensational comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in 20 years of action-packed adventures with the iconic antiheroine Red Sonja in the latest Humble Comics Bundle from Dynamite Entertainment! Dive into a massive library filled with fan-favorite titles like <em>Red Sonja Vol. 5 #1–28</em>, <em>Red Sonja: She-Devil With a Sword #1–13</em>, <em>Red Sonja: Birth of the She-Devil #1–4</em>, and more—starring the legendary warrior herself. Get 40+ comics celebrating two decades of sword-swinging excellence—and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Witcher Tabletop RPG by R. Talsorian Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/witcher-tabletop-rpg-r-talsorian-games-books</link>
      <description>Spare a coin for The Witcher TTRPG</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Evil is evil—and great games are great games. Pay what you want to explore The Continent like never before. Will you fight with strength and valor like Geralt of Rivia? Or forge your own path as an elf, dwarf, gnome, werebbubb, or vran, and set off on unknown adventures with your party. Get the The Witcher Tabletop RPG core rulebook, the <em>The Witcher: Tome of Chaos</em> campaign, and more for a price you choose. Spare a coin and help support the Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase. <br><br><a style="color: #EF9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through: DriveThruRPG</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comfort Crochet, Amigurumi, and Knitting by Open Road Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/comfort-crochet-amigurumi-and-knitting-open-road-media-books</link>
      <description>Create cute friends from home</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Beat the heat and stay cool inside with the all-new Comfort Crochet, Amigurumi, and Knitting. Try new techniques and fall in love with Amigurumi—the Japanese art of cute crocheting small yarn creations. Unleash your creativity using the very best craft ebooks from Open Road Media like <em>Granny Square Flower Garden</em>, <em>Beyond the Square: Crochet Motifs</em>, <em>100 Micro Crochet Motifs</em>, and <em>200 Crochet Flowers, Embellishments & Trims</em>. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the Breast Cancer Research Foundation. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>