<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 08:32:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Scarlett St. Clair Romantasy Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/scarlett-st-clair-romantasy-collection-books</link>
      <description>Hot and exciting romantasy novels</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fall in love with the hot and steamy fantasy novels of renowned romance author Scarlett St. Clair. This all-new ebook bundle features a rich mix of her best works including <em>A Touch of Darkness</em>, <em>A Game of Fate</em>, and <em>King of Battle and Blood</em>. Lose yourself in the love and lust of this expansive romantasy library. Plus—a portion of your purchase helps support Native Forward Scholars Fund!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sybex Certification by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/sybex-certification-wiley-books</link>
      <description>Sybex prep for IT pros</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dominate your IT certification exams with the latest Sybex prep bundle by Wiley. For over 200 years, Wiley has empowered individuals with the tools to succeed in the digital world. Their Sybex prep series offers top-tier training to help you keep your skillset current in the ever-changing IT landscape. Get study guides like <em>CompTIA Security+ Practice Tests: Exam SY0-701, 3rd Edition</em>, and access industry-leading resources today—plus, help support The Hidden Genius Project with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial Killers: Murder and Mayhem</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/serial-killers-murder-and-mayhem-books</link>
      <description>Murder, mayhem, madness, ‘n’ more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Grab the all-new Murder and Mayhem Bundle if you love a bloody good time. Pay what you want for captivating and gruesome tales from hot true crime ebooks. Read about the famous killings of the late 1960s in <em>The Michigan Murders</em>, cannibals of the Florida Gulf Coast in <em>Flesh Collectors</em>, and so much more. Stimulate your scary side and help support Room to Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midsummer Magick &amp; Witchcraft by Adams Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/midsummer-magick-witchcraft-adams-media-books</link>
      <description>Master magick, witchcraft, and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A world of witchcraft and helpful rituals awaits! Summon an amazing library of mystical ebooks and get the Midsummer Magick & Witchcraft Bundle today. This collection is perfect for budding Green Witches, mixologists, and Moon Witches. Master spells, herbology, and potion-making with books like <em>Green Witch's Garden</em>, <em>Modern Witchcraft Book of Astrology</em>, <em>Hex Your Ex</em>, and more—pay what you want and help support Worldreader!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lilo &amp; Stitch, Gargoyles, and More Disney Comics!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/lilo-stitch-gargoyles-and-more-disney-comics-books</link>
      <description>A constellation of star-studded Disney Comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all Disney fans! Step into the magical world of Disney Comics with our latest collaboration with Dynamite Entertainment. All your favorite critters, heroes, and goofballs are here to entertain fans of all ages. Dive into a vibrant library featuring 50 comics starring beloved characters like <em>Lilo & Stitch</em>, <em>Gargoyles</em>, <em>Hercules</em>, and more. Discover amazing page-turners based on your favorite stories—and help support First Book with every purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Back End Web Development by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/modern-back-end-web-development-packt-books</link>
      <description>Build scalable apps &amp; APIs with Python, Java, Node.js &amp; Go.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unlock the art of backend development with this all-in-one bundle! Featuring over 20 powerful books, you'll master essential tech stack including Python, Node.js, Go, and Java to craft robust APIs and microservices. Explore frameworks like Django, Spring Boot, FastAPI and more through hands-on guides and cookbooks. Whether you’re starting out or scaling up, this bundle delivers the tools and knowledge to create production-ready, scalable applications. Ideal for developers and tech enthusiasts ready to dive into modern backend technologies and best practices]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rick Remender Collection from Image Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/rick-remender-collection-from-image-comics-books</link>
      <description>Remember the name—Rick Remender</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the renowned works of comic book writer and animator Rick Remender with the latest Humble Comics Bundle. Get 30+ volumes of amazing Image Comics titles like <em>SEVEN TO ETERNITY, Vol. 1</em>, <em>DEADLY CLASS, Vol. 1</em>, <em>BLACK SCIENCE, Vol. 1</em>, and more. Read the very best from this legendary creator and help support The BINC Foundation with your purchase. Style, story, and mystique—this bundle has it all!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Ink: IDW&#39;s Latest and Greatest Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/fresh-ink-idws-latest-and-greatest-comics-books</link>
      <description>Fresh ink from the pages to you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want and get the latest and greatest comics from world-renowned publisher IDW. The ink’s still fresh on hot new titles like <em>Dark Spaces: Wildfire</em>, <em>Beneath the Trees Where Nobody Sees</em>, <em>Earthdivers, Vol. 1: Kill Columbus</em>, and more! If you love graphic novels and comics, this is the perfect way to expand your digital comic collection with 20+ outstanding titles. Plus—your purchase helps support The Hero Initiative!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding for the Curious by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/coding-for-curious-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Learn JavaScript, PHP, C++ and more—all in one go.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Exploring the mysteries of programming just got a whole lot easier. Try out any of 10+ languages—from Kotlin to JavaScript and C++ to PHP—with the latest bundle from No Starch Press. Pick up 18 ebooks that will turn you into the ultimate polyglot programmer, plus support the EFF as they fight for your rights online!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Usagi Yojimbo: The Rabbit Ronin Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/usagi-yojimbo-rabbit-rnin-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Read the Rabbit Rōnin’s journey today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ready yourself for the most unique and original story set in classic Japan. The Usagi Yojimbo: The Rabbit Rōnin Bundle is unlike any other, focusing on the life and journey of a legendary anthropomorphic rōnin, Miyamoto Usagi. Set in the Edo period and based on a real-life masterless samurai, this series created by Stan Sakai is thrilling and perfect for readers of all ages. Move with haste—read 20 <em>Usagi Yojimbo</em> comics and help support the Hero Initiative with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters, Traps, &amp; DM Tricks For DnD &amp; DCC</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/monsters-traps-dm-tricks-for-dnd-dcc-books</link>
      <description>Monsters, traps, tricks, and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Teach an old Dungeon Master new tricks with our most epic DM bundle yet! Surprise your companions and foes with new techniques, traps, and tactics from hot books and guides. Create your own original campaigns, get inspired by <em>How to Write Adventure Modules That Don't Suck</em>, and gain access to a limited-quantity supply of <em>Grimtooth's Trapsylvania</em> hardback books! Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support The Trevor Project with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPG Game Master Book Series</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/rpg-game-master-book-series-books</link>
      <description>Teach a Game Master new tricks</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[What makes a great Game Master? Experience, knowledge, resources, and excitement! Become a legendary GM with our all-new RPG Game Master Book Bundle. Elevate your skillset with endless insights from robust ebooks like <em>The Game Master's Book of Random Encounters</em>, <em>The Game Master's Book of Traps, Puzzles and Dungeons</em>, and <em>The Game Master's Book of Astonishing Random Tables</em>. Pay what you want and help support the Breast Cancer Research Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Witcher X Cyberpunk 2025 by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/witcher-x-cyberpunk-2025-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Silver swords and cyber psychos</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Silver swords and cyber psychos. Looking for awesome stories set in two of the most exciting universes around? This bundle of Witcher and Cyberpunk books and comics from Dark Horse has the goods for stone cold monster hunters and chromed-out netrunners alike! The Witcher Volume 1: House of Glass sends Geralt on one of most harrowing adventures yet, replete with human drama and haunting terror in equal measures. Cyberpunk 2077: Your Voice is full of dazzling action and corpo intrigue—the hallmarks of a killer Night City tale. You’ll also get deep looks into these awesome universes with books like The World of Cyberpunk 2077 and The World of the Witcher, and much more! Pay what you want for this action-packed bundle and help support SpecialEffect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning, AI, and Bots by O&#39;Reilly 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/machine-learning-ai-and-bots-oreilly-2025-books</link>
      <description>Master Machine Learning</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills and build your own bots with this comprehensive library from the pros at O’Reilly. Harness the power of machine learning to create digital agents and more with hot courses like <em>Learning LangChain</em>, <em>The Developer's Playbook for Large Language Model Security</em>, <em>Designing Large Language Model Applications</em>, and more. Get elite resources for both novice coders and seasoned pros to grow your career—and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>