<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2025 16:21:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>RuneQuest ENCORE by Chaosium</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/runequest-encore-chaosium-books</link>
      <description>Your gateway to a TTRPG classic</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the legendary and beloved tabletop RPG <em>RuneQuest</em>, where heroes are forged in the fires of myth and magic. This bundle includes everything you need to treat your group to endless adventure in the rich, storied world of Glorantha. The <em>RuneQuest Starter Set</em> will get you up and running, including rulebooks, adventures, pre-generated characters, and more. <em>The Red Book of Magic</em> is an essential sourcebook packed with new rules for magic and a wizard’s library of spells to add to your campaign. <em>The Pegasus Plateau & Other Stories</em> contains 7 adventures that’ll transport your group to some of Glorantha’s most thrilling locales. Pay what you want for all these books and more, and help support Code.org with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality Comics From Top Shelf</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/quality-comics-from-top-shelf-books</link>
      <description>Top quality comics for all</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Great comics come in a wide variety of styles and flavors—so take a bite from a library of fantastic titles! Dive into our Quality Comics Bundle from Top Shelf and get familiar with iconic stories like <em>The League of Extraordinary Gentlemen Volume III & IV</em>, engaging spinoffs like <em>Nemo: River of Ghosts</em>, and compelling dark tales like <em>From Hell: Master Edition</em>. Get a curated collection of amazing comics and help support the BINC Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Development with Apress</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/full-stack-development-with-apress-books</link>
      <description>Comprehensive full stack development tools</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Our latest bundle offers everything you need for comprehensive web development—from front-end to back-end. Learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed in web application creation with this bundle of elite courses from Apress. Inside this 20+ program library, you’ll get expert insights from <em>Master Vue.js in just 6 Days</em>, <em>Angular For Business</em>, <em>Mastering MYSQL Administration</em>, and much more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Erikson&#39;s Malazan Book of the Fallen ENCORE by TOR Publishing Group</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/steven-eriksons-malazan-book-fallen-encore-tor-publishing-group-books</link>
      <description>Lose yourself in an epic fantasy masterpiece</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the sweeping saga of gods, mages, mortals, and warring nations in <em>New York Times</em>–bestselling author Steven Erikson’s Malazan Book of the Fallen, heralded as one of the most ambitious, complex, and masterful epic fantasy series of all time. This epic ebook bundle features the complete main 10-volume saga (from <em>Gardens of the Moon</em> to the gripping final volume <em>The Crippled God</em>), as well as seven additional titles that further explore the history and conflicts of the Malazan Empire. Journey deep into one of fantasy literature’s most celebrated worlds, and help support Covenant House and Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army of Darkness by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/army-darkness-dynamite-books</link>
      <description>The Army of Darkness story continues</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in <em>Army of Darkness</em>, the butt-kicking comic series in this bundle from Dynamite Entertainment! Get 20+ comics that follow the exciting adventures of Ash Williams—the Boomstick wielding, foul-mouthed protagonist with the most unfortunate luck. Read great titles like <em>Army of Darkness: Ashes 2 Ashes</em> and <em>Army of Darkness vs. Re-Animator</em>, and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Kingmaker Bundle from Paizo Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-kingmaker-bundle-from-paizo-inc-books</link>
      <description>Elevate your Pathfinder campaigns </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your party of trusty friends for countless adventures with our latest <em>Pathfinder</em> bundle from Paizo Inc. Enhance your existing <em>Pathfinder</em> collection with new rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources. Highlights from the Pathfinder Kingmaker Bundle include <em>Pathfinder: Kingmaker Enhanced Plus Edition</em> and <em>Pathfinder Kingmaker Companion Guide</em>. Get everything you need to embark on an epic high fantasy journey together, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comics and Graphic Novel Audio Adaptations by GraphicAudio</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/comics-and-graphic-novel-audio-adaptations-graphicaudio-books</link>
      <description>Heroes, antiheroes, and epic comic stories</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Enjoy the page-turning origins of your favorite gritty, brutal, and hilarious antiheroes like the demonic prince, Hellboy and the hardened Billy Butcher. Lose yourself in an awesome comics collection featuring dramatized adaptations of <em>Hellboy: A Plague Of Wasps</em>, <em>The Boys Volume 1-3</em> , and <em>X Volumes 1-6</em>. Get more than 25 titles and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Plants Vs. Zombies by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/plants-vs-zombies-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Who’s winning—Plants or Zombies?</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Do you eat brains or fertilizer? Jump into the epic battle between <em>Plants Vs. Zombies</em> but now, as comic books by Dark Horse! The war has spread from the land of video games into the beautifully drawn and written pages of amazing issues like <em>Plants vs. Zombies Volume 1: Lawnmageddon</em> and <em>Plants vs. Zombies Volume 2: Timepocalypse</em>. This library features 25+ unique titles ranging from comics to behind-the-scenes goodies like <em>The Art of Plants vs. Zombies</em>. Read great comics and help support Child’s Play Charity today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Excel to Impact by Mr. Excel</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/excel-to-impact-mr-excel-books</link>
      <description>Excel to impact by Mr. Excel </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to be the best Excel user in your office, home, and anywhere in between. Our latest bundle from Mr. Excel will teach you the shortcuts, techniques, insider tips to elevate your Excel expertise. Inside this comprehensive library, you’ll gain expert insights from books like <em>MrExcel 2024</em>, <em>Power BI for the Excel Analyst</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, Love, and Everything In Between</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/sex-love-and-everything-in-between-books</link>
      <description>Our hottest and steamiest bundle yet</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Spice up your sex life with a little help from the experts at Adams Media. Don’t be shy—this Sex, Love, and Everything In Between Bundle is perfect for everyone. Teach yourself new tricks or delve into something adventurous and unknown, the sensual choices are yours. Explore the contents of titillating titles like <em>365 Questions For Couples</em>, <em>1001 Sexcapades to Do If You Dare</em>, and more. Add a little something to your love life and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!  <br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences. User discretion is advised.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Cybersecurity Career by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-cybersecurity-career-packt-books</link>
      <description>Jump-start your cybersecurity career</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to build the foundation for a new career in cybersecurity—the pros at Packt are giving you the expert insights you need to succeed in a variety of cybersecurity subsectors. Gain insights from courses like <em>Automating Security Detection Engineering</em>, <em>AWS Certified Security</em>, <em>Pentesting Active Directory and Windows-based Infrastructure</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder &amp; Starfinder Comics by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-starfinder-comics-dynamite-books</link>
      <description>A curated collection of elite comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in a library of fantastic graphic fiction in this bundle of comics from Dynamite Entertainment! Delve into <em>Pathfinder: Runescars #1-5</em>, <em>Starfinder: Angels of the Drift #1-5</em>, <em>Pathfinder: Spiral of Bones #1-5</em>, and 70+ more amazing titles all within one bundle. This curated collection is perfect for fans of high fantasy, scifi, and everything in between. Act now—get amazing comics and help a charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE Tabletop RPG Resources by Dicegeeks</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/more-tabletop-rpg-resources-dicegeeks-books</link>
      <description>D&amp;D resources suited for any style</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing books from Dicegeeks. This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains an amazing variety of rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources that enhance your favorite <em>Dungeons & Dragons</em> games—we’ve included standouts like <em>The Book of Random Tables: Festivals and Fairs</em> and <em>The Book of Random Tables: Superheroes</em>. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support Children's Miracle Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Programming by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/game-programming-pearson-books</link>
      <description>The perfect toolbox for game creation</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Let’s start building games—level up your coding skills with our Gaming Programming by Pearson Bundle! Learn the basics and advanced techniques needed to develop original games that are only limited by your imagination. This 20+ library of extremely useful courses includes standouts like <em>Roblox Game Development in 24 Hours: The Official Roblox Guide</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Game Design</em>, and more. Get the resources you need to start a new career, and help support Girls Make Games Scholarship Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux from Beginner to Professional by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/linux-from-beginner-to-professional-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Make Linux your second language</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Break into the powerful world of Linux with this insightful collection of courses by O’Reilly. Our latest bundle will teach you the fundamentals to build upon so you can master Linux in no time. Start learning today from amazing courses like <em>Learning Modern Linux</em>, <em>Practical Linux System Administration</em>, and <em>Python for DevOps</em>. Get the resources you need to go from a novice coder and to a seasoned pro with a budding career—and help support Code For America!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>