<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Roll Big or Go Home RPG Megabundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/roll-big-or-go-home-rpg-megabundle-books-encore</link>
      <description>Roll big or go home!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for the ultimate TTRPG adventure with the Roll Big or Go Home RPG Megabundle. This legendary 50+ title bundle is jam-packed with rulebooks, auxiliary resources, soundtracks, and more for you to enjoy. Help Aang bring elemental balance to the world in Magpie Games’ <em>Avatar Legends: The Roleplaying Game</em>, use your best chrome to smoke Corpos in R. Talsorian Games’ <em>Cyberpunk RED</em>, and roleplay as a robot in disguise in Renegade Game Studios’ <em>Transformers Roleplaying Game</em>. Play the best games from the best publishers within our biggest TTRPG bundle ever! Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Extra Life.<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through DriveThruRPG.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Tchaikovsky&#39;s Epic Fantasy by Macmillan</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/adrian-tchaikovskys-epic-fantasy-pan-macmillan-books</link>
      <description>Fantasy like you’ve never seen before</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’ve been looking for an expansive book series from one of genre fiction’s greatest living authors, we’ve got you covered with this giant bundle of fantasy epics by Arthur C. Clarke Award winner Adrian Tchaikovsky! This 14-ebook bundle from Pan Macmillan includes all ten books in Tchaikovsky’s Shadows of the Apt series, set in an alternate world where human races who share characteristics with insects must unite against the threat of the Wasp Empire. You’ll also get all three books in the Echoes of the Fall trilogy as well as Tchaikovsky’s “flintlock fantasy” standalone novel Guns of the Dawn, so act now and grab this bundle while you can! All purchases at the price of your choosing support Cancer Research UK!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amigurumi, Crochet, and More by Open Road Media Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/amigurumi-crochet-and-more-open-road-media-books-encore</link>
      <description>Yearn for yarn</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take a step away from the digital world and relax with a cozy new hobby—start your crochet and crafting journey today with the all-new Amigurumi, Crochet, and More Bundle by Open Road Media! Get awesome ebooks jam-packed with the cutest critters and more like <em>Crochet Zodiac Dolls</em>, <em>Funny Amigurumi</em>, <em>Little Happy Circus</em>, and <em>Crochet Animal Slippers</em>. Wear, display, or cuddle with the cutest pals around—plus—your purchase helps support No Kid Hungry!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martha Wells&#39; Murderbot and More by TOR ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/martha-wells-murderbot-and-more-tor-books-encore</link>
      <description>Martha Wells&#39; Murderbot &amp; More</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fall for the series that inspired the Apple TV+ hit with the all-new Martha Wells' Murderbot & More Bundle! Wells' Murderbot Diaries series tells the on-going story of an artificial Security Unit that hacks its governor module, enabling it to rebel against its programming. Unlike most constructs, Murderbot just wants to be left alone to stream the tens of thousands of hours of streaming media it's downloaded to its memory banks. But as much as it wants to avoid the human drama around it, Murderbot just keeps getting dragged back in. <br><br>This multi-Hugo Award-winning series includes standout titles like <em>All Systems Red</em> and <em>Artificial Condition</em>. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support World Central Kitchen.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition Holiday Haul Bundle by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-holiday-haul-bundle-paizo-books</link>
      <description>A holiday haul of fantasy adventures</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A vast world of adventure and danger awaits—the only piece missing is your heroism. Gather your party of friends-turned-trusty companions for countless adventures with our latest <em>Pathfinder 2e</em> bundle from Paizo Inc., filled with epic new campaigns like <em>Pathfinder Rage of Elements</em> and <em>Pathfinder Adventure Path: Pactbreaker</em>. Plus, the first 2,500 purchasers receive Pathfinder Elemental Stones! Get everything you need to embark on an epic high-fantasy journey together and help support ComicBooks for Kids.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monstrous Mignolaverse Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/monstrous-mignolaverse-bundle-books</link>
      <description>To Hell and back</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wanted to immerse yourself in the worlds of the legendary Mike Mignola but have no clue where to start, well, we can’t tell you where to start either, but we <em>can</em> give you the option to start anywhere you’d like with this enormous 166 title collection! Check out everything Mignola—the whole Mignolaverse, if you will—from the vampire hunting adventures of Lord Baltimore and Frankenstein’s New World miniseries to the occult detective stories of Joe Golem and, of course, the saga of Hellboy and his B.P.R.D. buddies. This bundle includes iconic titles for the Mignola novices and deep cuts for the Mignola superfans, so grab it while it’s red-hot and support World Central Kitchen’s food relief efforts with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Certification Prep by Microsoft Press and Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/microsoft-certification-prep-microsoft-press-and-pearson</link>
      <description>Become a Certified Microsoft expert</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Not sure where to start with Microsoft certifications? Want to go beyond the basics and prove your skills? This official Exam Ref eBook bundle has everything you need to prep smarter—from Azure fundamentals and data analytics to security, identity, and hybrid infrastructure. Each guide is packed with real‑world scenarios, exam tips, and focused review notes so you can skip the fluff and study what matters. Grab these eBooks while you can, and support the connectivity and sustainable power efforts of Hello World with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hacking-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Hack for good—never for harm.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Turn your curiosity about computer hacking into a fast-paced, proven, and practical career with our latest collaboration with tech experts at No Starch. Pay what you want for industry-leading instruction from courses like <em>Black Hat Bash</em>, <em>Microcontroller Exploits</em>, and <em>The Art of Cyberwarfare</em>, all designed to help you combat bad hackers and secure your cyberspace. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Get-Your-Sh*t-Together Growth Bundle by HarperCollins</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/getyourshttogether-growth-bundle-harpercollins-books</link>
      <description>Get your sh*t together—now!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hey, man—ready to level up your work and your life? Unlock tricks, tips, and hacks to power up your finances, sharpen your business instincts, and upgrade your mental health with The Get-Your-Sh*t-Together Growth Bundle by HarperCollins! This powerhouse collection brings together bold and not-so-subtly titled ebooks like <em>Unfu*k Yourself and The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck</em>— alongside game-changing business classics like Never Split the Difference and Tools of Titans. Pay what you want for the ultimate self-help collection and help support Room to Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Comics in the &#39;10s</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/image-comics-in-10s-books</link>
      <description>Bold and expressive comics by Image</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepare for a bundle of can’t-miss digital comics with the attitude cranked all the way up—this powerhouse collection delivers iconic Image Comics stories like <em>SAGA, Vol. 1, Sex Criminals, Vol. 1, Paper Girls, VOL. 1</em>, and more. This 100+ title library doesn’t pull any punches—explore the full spectrum of the femme experience with the women-in-prison sci-fi exploitation riff <em>BITCH PLANET</em>. Pay what you want for some of the hottest comics from Image, and support the BINC Foundation with your purchase.</p> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences.</strong></a><br><br>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Who Megabundle: Explore the Whoniverse ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/doctor-who-megabundle-explore-whoniverse-books-encore</link>
      <description>Explore the Whoniverse in comic form</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whovians, this one's for you! The Whoniverse comes alive on the page in this collection of comics, packed with dozens of volumes exploring the Doctor’s adventures and exploits across time and space! See the 8th and 11th Doctors team up to face down the Bad Wolf Empress in <em>Doctor Who: Empire of the Wolf</em>. In <em>Doctor Who: Origins</em>, a mission to hunt down a threat to Gallifrey puts the Doctor in the sites of the secretive Time Lords known as the Division. Get these awesome comics and a great many more, and help support BBC Children in Need with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate AI: Algorithms and LLMs by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-ai-algorithms-and-llms-manning-books</link>
      <description>Transform Your Tech Future</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive deep into the world of Artificial Intelligence with this essential collection of books, covering everything from core concepts to cutting-edge applications in generative AI, financial modeling, software testing, and more. Whether you're a developer looking to integrate AI into your workflow, a data scientist exploring large language models, or a business professional seeking to understand AI strategy, this bundle is your complete roadmap to succeeding in the age of AI.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black+Decker Home Improvement How-To Guides Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/blackdecker-home-howto-guides-books-2025-encore</link>
      <description>Get Black &amp; Decker The Complete Guide to Lower South Gardening and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We've teamed up with Quarto Publishing for our newest bundle! Get ebooks like <em>Black and Decker The Complete Guide to Bathrooms 6th Edition</em>, <em>Black & Decker The Complete Guide to Lower South Gardening</em>, <em>Black & Decker The Complete Guide to Carpentry for Homeowners</em>, <em>Black and Decker The Complete Guide to Plumbing Updated 8th Edition</em>, <em>Black & Decker The Complete Guide to Landscape Projects, 2nd Edition</em>, and <em>Black & Decker The Complete Photo Guide to Home Repair, 4th Edition</em>. Plus, your purchase will support It Gets Better!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Strategy and Risk Management by Pragmatic Programmers</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-strategy-and-risk-management-pragmatic-programmers-books</link>
      <description>Solutions for every problem</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Even the most efficient, streamlined, and well-ordered teams hit a snag once in a while. Whether it’s software issues, gaps in work structuring, or any number of other things, this bundle of workplace strategy resources from The Pragmatic Programmers is here to help you find a solution to every problem you encounter. In this bundle of 19 ebooks you’ll find breakdowns of the Kanban board method, instructions on running experiments with A/B testing that’ll get you real results, advice on how to use free and open source software, tons of strategies for building an accomplished, motivated team, and more! Build the kind of team that works for everyone and get stuff done—and support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Cybersecurity Career by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-cybersecurity-career-packt-books-encore</link>
      <description>Jump-start your cybersecurity career</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to build the foundation for a new career in cybersecurity—the pros at Packt are giving you the expert insights you need to succeed in a variety of cybersecurity subsectors. Gain insights from courses like <em>Automating Security Detection Engineering</em>, <em>AWS Certified Security</em>, <em>Pentesting Active Directory and Windows-based Infrastructure</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding Challenges and Interview Prep / Mammoth</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/coding-challenges-and-interview-prep-mammoth-books</link>
      <description>Hands-on training for every skill</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learning can be tough in any discipline, but especially in tech. The digital world is changing so fast it can be hard to figure out what you need to know, let alone where to even start—so bundles like this compilation of coding and interview prep resources from Mammoth Club will come in mighty handy. Inside this 26-ebook library you’ll find AI-powered training for learning Python, Java, and C++ on the go, coding challenges and interview prep for navigating algorithms and AI programs, and all the machine learning and engineering guides you need to master any problem an interview can throw at you. This bundle is meant for coders of all skill levels, so grab it while you can and help support Children’s Miracle Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-architecture-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Discover how everything fits together</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A software system is only as good as its architecture—all of the building blocks that make the system work—allows it to function. In order to build better software, you’ll need to understand the fundamentals of how everything fits together, and that’s where this handy ebook bundle of textbooks from Pearson comes in. Learn the importance of coupling in everyday software architecture, how to make your software shift and flow depending on the needs of the system, how to use the fundamentals of software architecture to build your software more efficiently, and much more in this 19-book library. Get a foothold on the basics so that your future projects are foolproof. Every purchase at the price of your choice supports Code.org, ensuring every student has access to computer science.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georges Simenon&#39;s Inspector Maigret Series by Picador</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/georges-simenons-inspector-maigret-series-picador-books</link>
      <description>A new look at France’s great detective</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Earlier this year, readers of detective fiction got some great news: Belgian author Georges Simenon’s iconic Inspector Maigret novels are getting a brand-new reissue from Picador. We have some equally great news: a bundle of all 18 of Simenon’s Maigret novels that have been republished thus far, to read along with PBS’s currently running Maigret series! Start at the very beginning of Maigret’s adventures with Pietr the Latvian, a manhunt for a notorious gangster who happens to have a number of mysterious doubles. Board a yacht and solve a murder with The Carter of “La Providence”. That’s only the tip of the Maigret iceberg, so grab this timeless library while you can, and support Come Back Alive with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>