<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 22:07:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Get-Your-Sh*t-Together Growth Bundle by HarperCollins</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/getyourshttogether-growth-bundle-harpercollins-books</link>
      <description>Get your sh*t together—now!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hey, man—looking for new perspectives on life? Unlock tricks, tips, and hacks to improve your mental and physical health with The Get-Your-Sh*t-Together Growth Bundle by HarperCollins! Reshape how you view the world with lessons from practical and not-so-subtly titled ebooks like <em>Unfu*k Yourself, Everything Is F*cked, and The Subtle Art of Not Giving a F*ck</em>—meaningful change is only a book chapter away. Pay what you want for the ultimate self-help collection and help support Room to Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Comics in the &#39;10s</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/image-comics-in-10s-books</link>
      <description>Bold and expressive comics by Image</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepare for a bundle of can’t-miss digital comics with the attitude cranked all the way up—this powerhouse collection delivers iconic Image Comics stories like <em>SAGA, Vol. 1, Sex Criminals, Vol. 1, Paper Girls, VOL. 1</em>, and more. This 100+ title library doesn’t pull any punches—explore the full spectrum of the femme experience with the women-in-prison sci-fi exploitation riff <em>BITCH PLANET</em>. Pay what you want for some of the hottest comics from Image, and support the BINC Foundation with your purchase.</p> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences.</strong></a><br><br>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Who Megabundle: Explore the Whoniverse ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/doctor-who-megabundle-explore-whoniverse-books-encore</link>
      <description>Explore the Whoniverse in comic form</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whovians, this one's for you! The Whoniverse comes alive on the page in this collection of comics, packed with dozens of volumes exploring the Doctor’s adventures and exploits across time and space! See the 8th and 11th Doctors team up to face down the Bad Wolf Empress in <em>Doctor Who: Empire of the Wolf</em>. In <em>Doctor Who: Origins</em>, a mission to hunt down a threat to Gallifrey puts the Doctor in the sites of the secretive Time Lords known as the Division. Get these awesome comics and a great many more, and help support BBC Children in Need with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate AI: Algorithms and LLMs by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-ai-algorithms-and-llms-manning-books</link>
      <description>Transform Your Tech Future</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive deep into the world of Artificial Intelligence with this essential collection of books, covering everything from core concepts to cutting-edge applications in generative AI, financial modeling, software testing, and more. Whether you're a developer looking to integrate AI into your workflow, a data scientist exploring large language models, or a business professional seeking to understand AI strategy, this bundle is your complete roadmap to succeeding in the age of AI.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Strategy and Risk Management by Pragmatic Programmers</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-strategy-and-risk-management-pragmatic-programmers-books</link>
      <description>Solutions for every problem</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Even the most efficient, streamlined, and well-ordered teams hit a snag once in a while. Whether it’s software issues, gaps in work structuring, or any number of other things, this bundle of workplace strategy resources from The Pragmatic Programmers is here to help you find a solution to every problem you encounter. In this bundle of 19 ebooks you’ll find breakdowns of the Kanban board method, instructions on running experiments with A/B testing that’ll get you real results, advice on how to use free and open source software, tons of strategies for building an accomplished, motivated team, and more! Build the kind of team that works for everyone and get stuff done—and support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black+Decker Home Improvement How-To Guides Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/blackdecker-home-howto-guides-books-2025-encore</link>
      <description>Get Black &amp; Decker The Complete Guide to Lower South Gardening and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We've teamed up with Quarto Publishing for our newest bundle! Get ebooks like <em>Black and Decker The Complete Guide to Bathrooms 6th Edition</em>, <em>Black & Decker The Complete Guide to Lower South Gardening</em>, <em>Black & Decker The Complete Guide to Carpentry for Homeowners</em>, <em>Black and Decker The Complete Guide to Plumbing Updated 8th Edition</em>, <em>Black & Decker The Complete Guide to Landscape Projects, 2nd Edition</em>, and <em>Black & Decker The Complete Photo Guide to Home Repair, 4th Edition</em>. Plus, your purchase will support It Gets Better!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Cybersecurity Career by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-cybersecurity-career-packt-books-encore</link>
      <description>Jump-start your cybersecurity career</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to build the foundation for a new career in cybersecurity—the pros at Packt are giving you the expert insights you need to succeed in a variety of cybersecurity subsectors. Gain insights from courses like <em>Automating Security Detection Engineering</em>, <em>AWS Certified Security</em>, <em>Pentesting Active Directory and Windows-based Infrastructure</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coding Challenges and Interview Prep / Mammoth</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/coding-challenges-and-interview-prep-mammoth-books</link>
      <description>Hands-on training for every skill</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learning can be tough in any discipline, but especially in tech. The digital world is changing so fast it can be hard to figure out what you need to know, let alone where to even start—so bundles like this compilation of coding and interview prep resources from Mammoth Club will come in mighty handy. Inside this 26-ebook library you’ll find AI-powered training for learning Python, Java, and C++ on the go, coding challenges and interview prep for navigating algorithms and AI programs, and all the machine learning and engineering guides you need to master any problem an interview can throw at you. This bundle is meant for coders of all skill levels, so grab it while you can and help support Children’s Miracle Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thundercats &amp; Friends by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/thundercats-friends-dynamite-books</link>
      <description>Sugar, spice, and really nice comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Enjoy your favorite network TV Golden Era cartoon characters like Lion-O and the ThunderCats, Bubbles and The Powerpuff Girls, and more in all-new ways with this enormous 90+ comic bundle from Dynamite Entertainment! Kick off your comics era with The Powerpuff Girls #1—the origin story of everyone’s favorite superhero sisters with attitude—or follow Lion-O, Panthro, and Cheetara as they battle the evil eternal entity Mumm-Ra in ThunderCats #1. Unlock awesome comics and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survive Everything Handbooks by Skyhorse ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/survive-everything-handbooks-skyhorse-books-encore</link>
      <description>Be ready for disaster and everything after</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Foraging. Trapping. Canning. Bushcraft. While this collection from Skyhorse is meant to prepare you to survive any situation, disaster or otherwise, there are skills everyone should know. With titles like <em>Trapper’s Bible</em>,<em>Complete Guide to Edible Wild Plants</em>, <em>Ultimate Book of Everyday Knots</em>, and over three dozen more books, you won’t just learn to survive in whatever situation you find yourself in—you’ll thrive. Plus, your purchase goes on to support the charity of your choice!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-architecture-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Discover how everything fits together</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A software system is only as good as its architecture—all of the building blocks that make the system work—allows it to function. In order to build better software, you’ll need to understand the fundamentals of how everything fits together, and that’s where this handy ebook bundle of textbooks from Pearson comes in. Learn the importance of coupling in everyday software architecture, how to make your software shift and flow depending on the needs of the system, how to use the fundamentals of software architecture to build your software more efficiently, and much more in this 19-book library. Get a foothold on the basics so that your future projects are foolproof. Every purchase at the price of your choice supports Code.org, ensuring every student has access to computer science.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math and Physics for Dummies 2025 Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/math-and-physics-for-dummies-books-2025-encore</link>
      <description>Math, physics &amp; more… For Dummies</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Need some help wrapping your head around complex subjects in math and physics? This bundle of books in the popular <em>For Dummies</em> series is here to help with fun and approachable lessons across a number of tricky topics! <em>Statistics All-in-One For Dummies</em> will teach you how to interpret graphs, determine probability, critique data and more! Bone up on the fundamentals and move onto the advanced stuff like graphing functions and approximating area with <em>Calculus For Dummies</em>. <em>Thermodynamics For Dummies</em> will help you wrap your head around complex concepts like entropy and the laws of thermodynamics in an easily digestible and approachable manner. Pay what you want for all these and more—a total of 16 books—and help support buildOn with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Language, Culture, and Travel by Stone Bridge Press Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/japanese-language-culture-and-travel-stone-bridge-press-books-encore</link>
      <description>Japanese language, culture, and travel</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepping for a trip to Japan? Or are you simply interested in learning the ins and outs of this beautiful country? This bundle of books will help you brush up on your language skills, appreciate Japan’s culture, and plan an itinerary for your future journeys. <em>Kanji Pict-o-Graphix</em> will help you wrap your head around the hardest parts of the Japanese written language with helpful mnenomic techniques. Full of useful guides and photos, <em>Tokyo Stroll: A Guide to City Sidetracks and Easy Explorations</em> encourages unstructured exploration of this exciting city. <em>Just Enough</em> provides valuable insights on living fully and sustainably, inspired by lessons learned in Japan’s past. Pay what you want for all these books and more and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georges Simenon&#39;s Inspector Maigret Series by Picador</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/georges-simenons-inspector-maigret-series-picador-books</link>
      <description>A new look at France’s great detective</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Earlier this year, readers of detective fiction got some great news: Belgian author Georges Simenon’s iconic Inspector Maigret novels are getting a brand-new reissue from Picador. We have some equally great news: a bundle of all 18 of Simenon’s Maigret novels that have been republished thus far, to read along with PBS’s currently running Maigret series! Start at the very beginning of Maigret’s adventures with Pietr the Latvian, a manhunt for a notorious gangster who happens to have a number of mysterious doubles. Board a yacht and solve a murder with The Carter of “La Providence”. That’s only the tip of the Maigret iceberg, so grab this timeless library while you can, and support Come Back Alive with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Call for Lankhmar by Goodman Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/last-call-for-lankhmar-goodman-games-books</link>
      <description>Welcome to Lankhmar</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your party and take a trip to a city full of adventure and surprise with this bundle of Lankhmar tabletop RPG resources from Dungeon Crawl Classics! Get the entire Lankhmar saga and 15 distinct adventures set within the legendary city, including fan favorites like “The Greatest Thieves in Lankhmar,” “Gang Lords of Lankhmar,” “Blasphemy and Larceny in Lankhmar,” and more! Bring your story to life with the Lankhmar Printed Boxed Set & Adventure Bundle, which features printed maps, the Compendium of Secret Knowledge, and more new material with all the twists and turns needed to satisfy newcomers and veteran players alike. Grab everything you need for your next adventure at the price of your choice, and all purchases support the No Kid Hungry campaign from nonprofit Share Our Strength.<br><em><strong><span style="color: #ef9741;"><br>Note: Due to limited quantities, the $40 physical tier is no longer available.</span></strong></em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering &amp; Science by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-engineering-science-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>The ins and outs of data science</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[With the world becoming more and more digitized, knowing how to use data is the way of the future. This bundle of valuable resources from O’Reilly is a Rosetta stone for aspiring data scientists everywhere, chock-full of information and tools to help you learn the skills you need to become a data engineer. This 20-book library will teach you how to integrate data science into software coding, use data science to design data-driven financial products, use streaming databases to process continuous inputs of data in real time, and more! Whether you’re new to the world of data science or an old hand at building data software of all kinds, this bundle will deepen your knowledge no matter your skill set. You choose what you pay, and all purchases support the federal aid organization Code for America!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux for Professionals by Apress/Springer</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/linux-for-professionals-apressspringer-books</link>
      <description>Live the Linux lifestyle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Humble Tech Book Bundles got you covered. Level up your Linux skills, learn to bend its unmatched power to your will, and create the most optimized operating systems around using the expertly crafted tools by Apress and Springer. This curated library of courses includes<em>Supercomputers for Linux SysAdmins</em>, <em>CompTIA Linux+ Certification Companion</em>, <em>Using and Administering Linux: Volume 1-2</em>, and more. Pay what you want and help support Room To Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>