<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 20:45:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Best of Humble Bundle: The Witcher + Cyberpunk by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/best-humble-bundle-witcher-cyberpunk-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Silver swords and cyber psychos</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking for awesome stories set in two of the most exciting universes around? This bundle of <em>The Witcher</em> and <em>Cyberpunk 2077</em> books and comics from Dark Horse has the goods for stone cold monster hunters and chromed-out netrunners alike! <em>The Witcher Volume 1: House of Glass</em> sends Geralt on one of most harrowing adventures yet, replete with human drama and haunting terror in equal measures. <em>Cyberpunk 2077: Your Voice</em> is full of dazzling action and corpo intrigue—the hallmarks of a killer Night City tale. You’ll also get deep looks into these awesome universes with books like <em>The World of Cyberpunk 2077</em> and <em>The World of the Witcher</em>, and much more! Pay what you want for this action-packed bundle and help support SpecialEffect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive-Verse by Image Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/massiveverse-image-comics-books</link>
      <description>A Massive-Verse sized Image Comics Bundle </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in a library of fantastic graphic fiction with this out-of-this-world bundle of comics by acclaimed author Kyle Higgins. Pay what you want for <em>Across the Massive-Verse TP, Vol. 1</em>, the epic first-issues anthology collection of Image’s biggest stars: <em>Radiant Black</em>, <em>Rogue Sun</em>, <em>The Dead Lucky</em>, and <em>Inferno Girl Red</em>, plus 15+ additional awesome titles. You’re going to love what we’ve assembled—explore Higgins’ best works at Image Comics and help support The BINC Foundation when you shop comics from Humble Bundle!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pianos, Music, and More for Dummies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pianos-music-and-more-for-dummies-books</link>
      <description>From dummy to genius (almost) instantly!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Inherited a piano from a long-lost relative but have no idea how to play? Determined to make sense of all that sheet music you have lying around? Got a song in your heart but no way to write it down? This bundle of music instruction books from the team at For Dummies will have you tickling the ivories and composing your symphony in no time! Start simple with some easy piano exercises, get into the weeds a little with music theory, learn the ancient arts of composition, songwriting, and vinyl collecting, or start living that record mogul life with a crash course in music business! Anything a beginner musician or music enthusiast could need is right here, so get these books while you can at the price of your choice, and support Music Will’s efforts to get music education to students in need with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPRINGFLING 2026 Physical Tabletop RPG Core Book Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/springfling-2026-physical-tabletop-rpg-core-book-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Start your unforgettable roleplaying adventure</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Make some space on your bookshelves, because we’ve got a very special book bundle for all the TTRPG enthusiasts out there: a library of physical copies of roleplaying game rulebooks to kick off your next tabletop adventure! Hunt down replicants and have an existential crisis or two in Blade Runner The Roleplaying Game! Save the Mortal Realms from the evil Nagash in Warhammer Age of Sigmar: Soulbound! Master the arts of elemental bending and unite the Four Nations in Avatar Legends: The Roleplaying Game! Grab this collection of roleplaying tomes while you can, and support the ACLU with every purchase at the price of your choice!<br><br><strong><em><span style="color: #ef9741;">Limited Quantities Available! In the US Only.<br><br>Keys expire, redeem before March 31st, 2026. Items ship from the Magpie Games Store after March 1st.</span></em></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>- Linux for Seasoned Admins by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/linux-for-seasoned-admins-oreilly-books-encore-2026</link>
      <description>Become a DevOps powerhouse 💪</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master the Linux command line, bootstrap yourself into DevOps competency, and gain a whole bunch of other skills to make you a better sysadmin with this bundle of books from O’Reilly! Included are 15 books covering a range of topics that’ll boost your qualifications and hone your skillset in security, containerization, version control, and much more. Pay what you want for the knowledge and confidence to succeed in a collection of in-demand disciplines, and help support Code for America with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Forgotten Realms Vault by Wizards of the Coast</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/forgotten-realms-vault-wizards-coast-books</link>
      <description>Enter the Forgotten Realms</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’re a Dungeons and Dragons fan, you’ve likely heard of the Forgotten Realms, fantastical lands of magical creatures and powerful deities that exist in the shadows of our world. But have you ever traveled out into these dangerous places hoping to unearth their secrets, and perhaps have an adventure or two? Now you can, thanks to our newest bundle of 40 fantasy ebooks that comes courtesy of none other than Wizards of the Coast! Here you’ll find thrilling tales of devils, dark elves, mercenaries, and mages from all your favorite authors, including Erin M. Evans, Richard Lee Byers, and Forgotten Realms’ creator Ed Greenwood himself. Spend all the coin you wish and dive right into one of fantasy literature’s most exciting worlds, and help support the education of children in need with First Book!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Charlie Jane Anders &amp; Annalee Newitz by TOR</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/charlie-jane-anders-annalee-newitz-tor-books</link>
      <description>Speculative fiction like you’ve never seen before</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[You’ve never read sci-fi quite like this. We’ve joined forces with TOR for our latest ebook bundle, which features no less than 21 fantastic ebooks and digital shorts written by acclaimed authors Charlie Jane Anders and Annalee Newitz, co-founders of io9 and co-hosts of the Hugo-winning podcast <em>Our Opinions Are Correct</em>. Survive the dystopian corporate controlled future of Annalee Newitz’s <em>Autonomous</em>! Journey to the dark side of an alien planet in Charlie Jane Anders’ <em>The City in the Middle of the Night</em>! Follow the exploits of a vengeful mother-daughter witch duo in Anders’ <em>Lessons in Magic and Disaster</em>! Explore a post-war San Francisco with the sentient food service robots of Newitz’s <em>Automatic Noodle</em>! If you’ve been looking for a wealth of imaginative speculative fiction to add to your library, grab this bundle while you can, and support Miss Major and Alexander L. Lee’s TGIJP Black Trans Cultural Center with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Solutions Architect Cloud Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-solutions-architect-cloud-bundle-packt-books</link>
      <description>Become a solutions-based mastermind</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The cloud computing bundle you’ve been waiting for has finally arrived—pay what you want for the ultimate collection of solutions-based cloud architecture and take your knowledge to the next level. We’ve teamed up with the experts at Packt to curate a library of courses specially designed to help you master cloud architecture. Get <em>Azure Cloud Projects</em>, <em>AWS for Solutions Architects 3rd Edition</em>, <em>Solutions Architect's Handbook 3rd Edition</em>, and 10+ additional lessons today, and help support the Make-A-Wish Foundation when you shop with Humble!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Who Audio Adventures by Big Finish</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/doctor-who-audio-adventures-big-finish-books</link>
      <description>All of time and space in your headphones</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Travel through the cosmos alongside the universe’s friendliest Time Lord with this bundle of Doctor Who audiobooks from Big Finish! Featuring your favorite Doctor Who stars and full cast recordings, this bundle is a treasure trove of adventures for superfans and newbies both. Join the likes of Christopher Eccleston’s Ninth Doctor, John Hurt’s War Doctor, and Alex Kingston’s time-warped archaeologist River Song on their quests through time and space to save the universe from Time Eddies, intergalactic criminals, and those pesky Daleks. There’s so much more to explore in this audio bundle, so act now to grab it at the price of your choice, and support the BBC’s Children in Need charity with your purchase! No running required. Well—maybe a little bit of running. You never know.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Tech Career Playbook Bundle by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/high-tech-career-playbook-bundle-manning-books</link>
      <description>Big time savings on high tech teachings</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking for a new role in tech? Take control of your career and learn the skills you need to succeed with the High Tech Career Playbook Bundle by Manning Publications. Unlock volumes 1–2 of the acclaimed <em>Acing the CCNA</em> series, the savvy <em>Investing for Programmers</em> course, the C-suite–ready <em>Think Like a CTO</em> lesson, and much more. Pay what you want to flip the script on your career prospects and help support Feeding America with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quilting and Embroidery by C &amp; T Publishing</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/quilting-and-embroidery-c-t-publishing-books</link>
      <description>Become a craft master</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking to take up a new hobby but don’t know where to start? Already mastered the basics but need some tips to expand your skill set? If you find yourself in either situation and happen to be into quilting and embroidery, we’ve got good news: a whole bundle of 25 ebook resources from C&T Publishing that’ll help you sew the quilts of your dreams!! Learn techniques like quilt-as-you-go, sashiko stitching, turning fabric scraps into patchwork, embroidering fun doodles or pictures of your beloved pet, and more! Master the art of fabric crafts with this ebook bundle, and support One Tree Planted with your purchase at the price of your choice!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBM Graphic Novels 50th Anniversary Collection by NBM Graphic Novels</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/nbm-graphic-novels-50th-anniversary-bundle-nbm-graphic-novels-books</link>
      <description>Stories you won’t find anywhere else</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate 50 years of incredible graphic novels with NBM! To mark this anniversary, we’ve partnered with the Eisner Award-winning publisher to collect 40 amazing graphic novels hailing from all over North America and Europe—and bring them straight to your inbox. Enjoy the sumptuously illustrated <em>Fairy Tales of Oscar Wilde</em>, dive into biographies of Rosa Parks and the Beatles, seek adventure with <em>Hasib and the Queen of Serpents</em>, and ride the thrills of the monster theme park at the heart of <em>Zombillenium</em>. If you’re a fan of graphic novels, great literature, or even just good storytelling, grab this bundle while you can and support hospitalized kids with Starlight Children's Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knit Happens! Knitting for Creative Knitter Critters by Abrams Books</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/knit-happens-knitting-for-creative-knitter-critters-abrams-books-books</link>
      <description>Knockout knitting knowledge </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Already got the knack for knitting but unsure where to take your skills? Ready to pick up a new hobby in the new year and already planning out ambitious projects? Look no further than this bundle of ebooks from Abrams Books full of inspiration and instructions for every creative knitting project under the sun! Here you’ll find tips and templates to turn simple knits into professional-grade garments, traditional sweater patterns with modern twists, hundreds of stitches to add to your knitting lexicon, and so much more! Get started on your knitting projects today with this ebook bundle available for the price of your choosing, and support indie bookstore and comic shop charity organization BINC with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamite Character Crossover Comics by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dynamite-character-crossover-comics-dynamite-books</link>
      <description>Killer character crossovers for the new year</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve assembled Dynamite Entertainment’s hottest eComics into a bundle you won’t want to miss. Vampirella, John Carter of Mars, Red Sonja, and the universe’s greatest heroes collide in an epic series of battles across <em>DIE!NAMITE Vols. 1–6</em>. Grab your boomstick for the action-packed mayhem of <em>Army of Darkness: Ash vs. the Classic Monsters, Vols. 1–6</em>. Bad guys beware—the femme fatales of Dynamite unite to stop a legendary evil in <em>Swords of Sorrow: The Complete Saga</em>. Pay what you want and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>