<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 01:47:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Ellis by Image Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/warren-ellis-image-comics-books</link>
      <description>Introducing an award-winning graphic novelist</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the renowned stories of Image Comics with our latest Humble Comics Bundle featuring 10+ graphic novels showcasing the award-winning works of Warren Ellis. This collection includes gripping noir like <em>Fell</em>, slow-burning sci-fi like <em>Trees</em>, and suspenseful horror like <em>Injection</em>. Discover worlds beyond the familiar, add iconic graphic novels to your personal collection, and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualization by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-visualization-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Imagine limitless possibilities in data visualization </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become your office’s Microsoft Suite whiz—or simply sharpen your skills for fun—with the all-new Data Visualization Bundle from O’Reilly. Improve your productivity, increase your work speed, and collaborate more effectively with your team using the valuable tools in our latest bundle. Sit down and learn from professional-quality courses like <em>Data Visualization with Microsoft Power BI</em>, <em>Excel Cookbook</em>, <em>ColorWise</em>, and more. Plus, your purchase helps support Code for America!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math and Physics for Dummies Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/math-and-physics-for-dummies-books-encore</link>
      <description>Math, physics &amp; more… For Dummies</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Need some help wrapping your head around complex subjects in math and physics? This bundle of books in the popular <em>For Dummies</em> series is here to help with fun and approachable lessons across a number of tricky topics! <em>Statistics All-in-One For Dummies</em> will teach you how to interpret graphs, determine probability, critique data and more! Bone up on the fundamentals and move onto the advanced stuff like graphing functions and approximating area with <em>Calculus For Dummies</em>. <em>Thermodynamics For Dummies</em> will help you wrap your head around complex concepts like entropy and the laws of thermodynamics in an easily digestible and approachable manner. Pay what you want for all these and more—a total of 16 books—and help support buildOn with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bushcraft &amp; Homestead Handbook Series by Adams Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/bushcraft-homestead-handbook-series-adams-media-books</link>
      <description>The skills to keep you alive</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t just survive in the wild—thrive. The Bushcraft & Homestead Handbook Bundle by Adams Media is our newest collection of nature books designed to teach you valuable life and survival skills. Get the latest and most useful bushcraft ebooks around including <em>Bushcraft Essentials Field Guide</em>, <em>Disaster Survival 101</em>, <em>Bushcraft Field Guide to Trapping, Gathering, and Cooking in the Wild</em>, and many more. Conquer the outdoors, develop a new sense of confidence, and help support World Reader with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampirella XOXO by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/vampirella-xoxo-dynamite-encore-books</link>
      <description>A bloody good time</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Uncover a macabre library featuring one of horror’s most enduring comic-book heroines in our latest bundle from Dynamite! Unearth classic Vampirella tales and discover modern interpretations in volumes like <em>Vampirella: Hollywood Horror</em> and the <em>Vampirella Masters Series</em>, featuring stories from some of comics’ most celebrated writers including Grant Morrison, Mark Millar, Kate Leth, and more. Plus, your purchase helps support NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# and .NET Mega Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/c-and-net-mega-bundle-packt-books</link>
      <description>The programmer &amp; developer dream bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Transform your .NET development career with the C# & .NET Mega Bundle, featuring 20+ cutting‑edge titles by industry‑leading authors like Mark J. Price, Gabriel Baptista, and Jimmy Engström. You'll gain access to bestselling books such as "C# 13 and .NET 9 – Modern Cross-Platform Development Fundamentals," "Software Architecture with C# 12 and .NET 8," and "Web Development with Blazor," all designed to guide you from core C# fundamentals through .NET architecture, cross‑platform development, and modern API design. Whether you're a newcomer eager to learn the basics or a seasoned architect building enterprise‑scale solutions, this bundle delivers clear, step‑by‑step guidance at every level—plus, a portion of every purchase supports Save the Children. Grab your ultimate roadmap before the deal ends!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript, Scripting, and Web Development by Pragmatic</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/javascript-scripting-and-web-development-pragmatic-books</link>
      <description>A pot of JavaScript courses &amp; more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pour yourself a hot cup of JavaScript and open up our latest Humble Tech Book Bundle—it’s time to improve your web development and scripting skills. Unlock the latest coding techniques with this library of tech courses highlighted by <em>Clojure Brain Teasers</em>, <em>Serverless Apps on Cloudflare</em>, and <em>Test-Driven React, Second Edition</em>. Get elite resources for novice coders and seasoned pros alike, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Star Wars Insider Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/essential-star-wars-insider-collection-books</link>
      <description>The definitive Star Wars publication bundle.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Since 1987, <em>Star Wars Insider</em> has been the definitive source for all things <em>Star Wars</em> and we’re pleased to offer our members exclusive access to The Essential <em>Star Wars</em> Insider Collection! Go behind-the-scenes of your favorite <em>Star Wars</em> movies and TV shows--including all three trilogies and the standalone films <em>Rogue One: A Star Wars Story</em> and <em>Solo: A Star Wars Story</em>--and TV epics including <em>The Clone Wars</em> and <em>The Mandalorian</em>. These volumes are packed with cast and crew interviews, concept art and photography from the Lucasfilm Archives. There's even fiction from the first phase of The High Republic publishing initiative, written by New York Times bestselling authors Justina Ireland, Cavan Scott, and Charles Soule. This bundle is your essential companion to nearly 50 years of <em>Star Wars</em>. Become one with The Force and help support First Book with your purchase!<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition Asian Fantasy Bundle by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-asian-fantasy-bundle-paizo-books</link>
      <description>Become the hero of Golarion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A world of adventure & magic awaits, and the only thing missing is your hero’s courage. Gather your party of trusty companions for epic adventures with our latest <em>Pathfinder</em> bundle from Paizo Inc. The new Pathfinder Second Edition Asian Fantasy Bundle contains countless hours of new campaigns and guides like <em>Pathfinder Adventure Path: Fists of the Ruby Phoenix</em> and <em>Pathfinder Lost Omens: Tian Xia Character Guide</em>. Get everything you need to embark on an epic high fantasy journey together, and help support Stop AAPI Hate with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Trust, Risk, and Security by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ai-trust-risk-and-security-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Get familiar with defensive AI techniques</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Defend your personal and professional networks from digital harm with the AI Trust, Risk, and Security Bundle by Pearson. Learn how to fortify your online valuables with machine learning with courses like <em>The AI Revolution in Networking, Cybersecurity, and Emerging Technologies</em> and <em>Beyond the Algorithm: AI, Security, Privacy, and Ethics</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding of digital risk and security whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support the charity The Malala Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival From the Margins by Microcosm</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/survival-from-margins-microcosm-books</link>
      <description>Uber useful skills IRL &amp; online</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve teamed up with Microcosm Publishing for an eclectic blend of awesome DIY, self-help, and home-improvement books for you to soak up as summer kicks off. Learn how to do—well—just about anything with titles like <em>An Urban Field Guide to the Plants, Trees, and Herbs in Your Path</em>, <em>How to Get Off Social Media and Still Keep in Touch with Your Friends</em>, <em>Household Hiding Places & How to Make Them</em>, and much more. Get the ultimate collection of useful ebooks and support the BINC Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amigurumi, Crochet, and More by Open Road Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/amigurumi-crochet-and-more-open-road-media-books</link>
      <description>Yearn for yarn</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take a step away from the digital world and relax with a cozy new hobby—start your crochet and crafting journey today with the all-new Amigurumi, Crochet, and More Bundle by Open Road Media! Get awesome ebooks jam-packed with the cutest critters and more like <em>Crochet Zodiac Dolls</em>, <em>Funny Amigurumi</em>, <em>Little Happy Circus</em>, and <em>Crochet Animal Slippers</em>. Wear, display, or cuddle with the cutest pals around—plus—your purchase helps support No Kid Hungry!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DevOps 2025 by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/devops-2025-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Complex infrastructures made easy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Need to change your career prospects? Then acquire new skills—we’ve partnered with the pros at O’Reilly for a 10+ course collection of hot tech guides! Our latest bundle is tailored for DevOps professionals and rookies alike—learn from a diverse library of hot courses like <em>Terraform Cookbook</em>, <em>Continuous Deployment</em>, <em>Policy as Code</em> and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Cosplay Library</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-cosplay-library-books</link>
      <description>Start crafting your own cosplays</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The cosplay community is enormous and passionate, but the barrier to entry can feel overwhelming to newcomers. Remove the stress of buying an expensive, poorly fitting costume and create your own looks with The Ultimate Cosplay Library Bundle! Learn to design awesome cosplays with foam, textiles, and more from 30+ ebooks like <em>Perfect Plan of a Cosplayer</em>, <em>Creative Cosplay</em>, and <em>Cosplay Foundations</em>. Make your cosplay dreams a reality and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Jordan&#39;s The Wheel of Time</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/robert-jordans-wheel-time-books</link>
      <description>Now extended through May 22nd!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Enter the world of The Wheel of Time, a fantasy series like no other. Our latest bundle includes every volume of the international bestselling The Wheel of Time and connected titles, a groundbreaking epic fantasy series by Robert Jordan and completed by Brandon Sanderson. The Wheel of Time turns and Ages come and pass, leaving memories that become legend. Legend fades to myth, and even myth is long forgotten when the Age that gave it birth returns again. What was, what will be, and what is, may yet fall under the Shadow.<br><br>Since its debut in 1990, The Wheel of Time has captivated millions of readers around the globe with its scope, originality, and compelling characters, and is the basis for the original series on Prime Video. The last six books in series were all instant #1 New York Times bestsellers, and The Eye of the World was named one of America's best-loved novels by PBS's The Great American Read. Robert Jordan's epic saga traces an entire world's struggle to deal with war and destruction while one man prepares to face the embodiment of pure evil.<br><br>Enjoy these amazing titles and help support the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) with your purchase.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>