<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 20:26:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Roll Big or Go Home RPG Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/roll-big-or-go-home-rpg-megabundle-books</link>
      <description>Roll big or go home!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for the ultimate TTRPG adventure with the Roll Big or Go Home RPG Megabundle. This legendary 50+ title bundle is jam-packed with rulebooks, auxiliary resources, soundtracks, and more for you to enjoy. Help Aang bring elemental balance to the world in Magpie Games’ <em>Avatar Legends: The Roleplaying Game</em>, use your best chrome to smoke Corpos in R. Talsorian Games’ <em>Cyberpunk RED</em>, and roleplay as a robot in disguise in Renegade Game Studios’ <em>Transformers Roleplaying Game</em>. Play the best games from the best publishers within our biggest TTRPG bundle ever! Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Extra Life.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Numenera RPG Collection by Monte Cook Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/numenera-rpg-collection-monte-cook-games-books</link>
      <description>Numenera awaits, adventurer </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the Ninth World with your companions in this engrossing futuristic TTRPG. Unlock the ultimate tabletop role-playing bundle for epic adventures in the world of <em>Numenera</em>. This massive collection from Monte Cook Games includes new rulebooks, maps, campaigns, and more—adding unrivaled value and depth to your existing library. Get everything you need to embark on an unforgettable journey, and help support the ACLU!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clover Press: The Art of Storytelling</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/clover-press-art-storytelling-books</link>
      <description>Curated comics + more by Clover Press</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve partnered with Clover Press to deliver members a lesson in the art of storytelling. Lose yourself in outstanding graphic novels and ebooks rich with narrative depth and striking visuals. Follow the mystery of Jay Gatsby in a vivid reimagining of the Roaring Twenties in <em>The Great Gatsby</em>, experience a modern retelling of an ancient classic in <em>Dracula of Transylvania</em>, and explore a cautionary tale of corporate greed in <em>BILLI 99</em>. Plus, your purchase helps support The Hero Initiative.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scarlett St. Clair Romantasy Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/scarlett-st-clair-romantasy-collection-books</link>
      <description>Hot and exciting romantasy novels</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fall in love with the hot and steamy fantasy novels of renowned romance author Scarlett St. Clair. This all-new ebook bundle features a rich mix of her best works including <em>A Touch of Darkness</em>, <em>A Game of Fate</em>, and <em>King of Battle and Blood</em>. Lose yourself in the love and lust of this expansive romantasy library. Plus—a portion of your purchase helps support Native Forward Scholars Fund!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sybex Certification by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/sybex-certification-wiley-books</link>
      <description>Sybex prep for IT pros</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dominate your IT certification exams with the latest Sybex prep bundle by Wiley. For over 200 years, Wiley has empowered individuals with the tools to succeed in the digital world. Their Sybex prep series offers top-tier training to help you keep your skillset current in the ever-changing IT landscape. Get study guides like <em>CompTIA Security+ Practice Tests: Exam SY0-701, 3rd Edition</em>, and access industry-leading resources today—plus, help support The Hidden Genius Project with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serial Killers: Murder and Mayhem</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/serial-killers-murder-and-mayhem-books</link>
      <description>Murder, mayhem, madness, ‘n’ more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Grab the all-new Murder and Mayhem Bundle if you love a bloody good time. Pay what you want for captivating and gruesome tales from hot true crime ebooks. Read about the famous killings of the late 1960s in <em>The Michigan Murders</em>, cannibals of the Florida Gulf Coast in <em>Flesh Collectors</em>, and so much more. Stimulate your scary side and help support Room to Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Midsummer Magick &amp; Witchcraft by Adams Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/midsummer-magick-witchcraft-adams-media-books</link>
      <description>Master magick, witchcraft, and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A world of witchcraft and helpful rituals awaits! Summon an amazing library of mystical ebooks and get the Midsummer Magick & Witchcraft Bundle today. This collection is perfect for budding Green Witches, mixologists, and Moon Witches. Master spells, herbology, and potion-making with books like <em>Green Witch's Garden</em>, <em>Modern Witchcraft Book of Astrology</em>, <em>Hex Your Ex</em>, and more—pay what you want and help support Worldreader!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lilo &amp; Stitch, Gargoyles, and More Disney Comics!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/lilo-stitch-gargoyles-and-more-disney-comics-books</link>
      <description>A constellation of star-studded Disney Comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all Disney fans! Step into the magical world of Disney Comics with our latest collaboration with Dynamite Entertainment. All your favorite critters, heroes, and goofballs are here to entertain fans of all ages. Dive into a vibrant library featuring 50 comics starring beloved characters like <em>Lilo & Stitch</em>, <em>Gargoyles</em>, <em>Hercules</em>, and more. Discover amazing page-turners based on your favorite stories—and help support First Book with every purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Back End Web Development by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/modern-back-end-web-development-packt-books</link>
      <description>Build scalable apps &amp; APIs with Python, Java, Node.js &amp; Go.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unlock the art of backend development with this all-in-one bundle! Featuring over 20 powerful books, you'll master essential tech stack including Python, Node.js, Go, and Java to craft robust APIs and microservices. Explore frameworks like Django, Spring Boot, FastAPI and more through hands-on guides and cookbooks. Whether you’re starting out or scaling up, this bundle delivers the tools and knowledge to create production-ready, scalable applications. Ideal for developers and tech enthusiasts ready to dive into modern backend technologies and best practices]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rick Remender Collection from Image Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/rick-remender-collection-from-image-comics-books</link>
      <description>Remember the name—Rick Remender</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the renowned works of comic book writer and animator Rick Remender with the latest Humble Comics Bundle. Get 30+ volumes of amazing Image Comics titles like <em>SEVEN TO ETERNITY, Vol. 1</em>, <em>DEADLY CLASS, Vol. 1</em>, <em>BLACK SCIENCE, Vol. 1</em>, and more. Read the very best from this legendary creator and help support The BINC Foundation with your purchase. Style, story, and mystique—this bundle has it all!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fresh Ink: IDW&#39;s Latest and Greatest Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/fresh-ink-idws-latest-and-greatest-comics-books</link>
      <description>Fresh ink from the pages to you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want and get the latest and greatest comics from world-renowned publisher IDW. The ink’s still fresh on hot new titles like <em>Dark Spaces: Wildfire</em>, <em>Beneath the Trees Where Nobody Sees</em>, <em>Earthdivers, Vol. 1: Kill Columbus</em>, and more! If you love graphic novels and comics, this is the perfect way to expand your digital comic collection with 20+ outstanding titles. Plus—your purchase helps support The Hero Initiative!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Usagi Yojimbo: The Rabbit Ronin Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/usagi-yojimbo-rabbit-rnin-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Read the Rabbit Rōnin’s journey today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ready yourself for the most unique and original story set in classic Japan. The Usagi Yojimbo: The Rabbit Rōnin Bundle is unlike any other, focusing on the life and journey of a legendary anthropomorphic rōnin, Miyamoto Usagi. Set in the Edo period and based on a real-life masterless samurai, this series created by Stan Sakai is thrilling and perfect for readers of all ages. Move with haste—read 20 <em>Usagi Yojimbo</em> comics and help support the Hero Initiative with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>