<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jan 2026 20:36:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Doctor Who Audio Adventures by Big Finish</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/doctor-who-audio-adventures-big-finish-books</link>
      <description>All of time and space in your headphones</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Travel through the cosmos alongside the universe’s friendliest Time Lord with this bundle of Doctor Who audiobooks from Big Finish! Featuring your favorite Doctor Who stars and full cast recordings, this bundle is a treasure trove of adventures for superfans and newbies both. Join the likes of Christopher Eccleston’s Ninth Doctor, John Hurt’s War Doctor, and Alex Kingston’s time-warped archaeologist River Song on their quests through time and space to save the universe from Time Eddies, intergalactic criminals, and those pesky Daleks. There’s so much more to explore in this audio bundle, so act now to grab it at the price of your choice, and support the BBC’s Children in Need charity with your purchase! No running required. Well—maybe a little bit of running. You never know.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>High Tech Career Playbook Bundle by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/high-tech-career-playbook-bundle-manning-books</link>
      <description>Big time savings on high tech teachings</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking for a new role in tech? Take control of your career and learn the skills you need to succeed with the High Tech Career Playbook Bundle by Manning Publications. Unlock volumes 1–2 of the acclaimed <em>Acing the CCNA</em> series, the savvy <em>Investing for Programmers</em> course, the C-suite–ready <em>Think Like a CTO</em> lesson, and much more. Pay what you want to flip the script on your career prospects and help support Feeding America with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quilting and Embroidery by C &amp; T Publishing</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/quilting-and-embroidery-c-t-publishing-books</link>
      <description>Become a craft master</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking to take up a new hobby but don’t know where to start? Already mastered the basics but need some tips to expand your skill set? If you find yourself in either situation and happen to be into quilting and embroidery, we’ve got good news: a whole bundle of 25 ebook resources from C&T Publishing that’ll help you sew the quilts of your dreams!! Learn techniques like quilt-as-you-go, sashiko stitching, turning fabric scraps into patchwork, embroidering fun doodles or pictures of your beloved pet, and more! Master the art of fabric crafts with this ebook bundle, and support One Tree Planted with your purchase at the price of your choice!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NBM Graphic Novels 50th Anniversary Collection by NBM Graphic Novels</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/nbm-graphic-novels-50th-anniversary-bundle-nbm-graphic-novels-books</link>
      <description>Stories you won’t find anywhere else</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate 50 years of incredible graphic novels with NBM! To mark this anniversary, we’ve partnered with the Eisner Award-winning publisher to collect 40 amazing graphic novels hailing from all over North America and Europe—and bring them straight to your inbox. Enjoy the sumptuously illustrated <em>Fairy Tales of Oscar Wilde</em>, dive into biographies of Rosa Parks and the Beatles, seek adventure with <em>Hasib and the Queen of Serpents</em>, and ride the thrills of the monster theme park at the heart of <em>Zombillenium</em>. If you’re a fan of graphic novels, great literature, or even just good storytelling, grab this bundle while you can and support hospitalized kids with Starlight Children's Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CompTIA AI Certification Prep and Practice Tests by Mammoth</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/comptia-ai-certification-prep-and-practice-tests-mammoth-books</link>
      <description>Don’t just learn material, master exams</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Mammoth Club is here with the complete roadmap for your entire IT career. From the foundational 'Trifecta' (A+, Network+, Security+) to advanced specialized roles in Cybersecurity, Cloud, and Data, this bundle covers every inch of the industry-standard CompTIA pathway. Whether you are looking to land your first help desk job or pivot into a high-level security role, this collection gives you the resources to get certified and get hired. Fast-track your IT career and start certifying today.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Knit Happens! Knitting for Creative Knitter Critters by Abrams Books</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/knit-happens-knitting-for-creative-knitter-critters-abrams-books-books</link>
      <description>Knockout knitting knowledge </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Already got the knack for knitting but unsure where to take your skills? Ready to pick up a new hobby in the new year and already planning out ambitious projects? Look no further than this bundle of ebooks from Abrams Books full of inspiration and instructions for every creative knitting project under the sun! Here you’ll find tips and templates to turn simple knits into professional-grade garments, traditional sweater patterns with modern twists, hundreds of stitches to add to your knitting lexicon, and so much more! Get started on your knitting projects today with this ebook bundle available for the price of your choosing, and support indie bookstore and comic shop charity organization BINC with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-wiley-books-2025</link>
      <description>Keep your digital ecosystem secure</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The best way to keep your network secure, whether it’s your own or your company’s, is to think like whoever might try to break into it. Learning to spot weak points in your security systems is the first step to crafting an ironclad defense, and our newest bundle will teach you the ways of the hacker, so that you can use them to keep your stuff safe. These 24 cybersecurity ebooks from Wiley have everything you need to become an expert in IT security testing, fighting malicious code, incident response, cryptography, and much more! Whether you’re giving your home computer network a security boost or managing an entire IT team, this bundle has the knowledge you need to succeed. Every purchase at the price of your choosing helps Hello World charity get connectivity and tech education resources to communities in need.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So You Wanna Try Out Call of Cthulhu by Chaosium</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/so-you-wanna-try-out-call-cthulhu-chaosium-inc-books</link>
      <description>Invite eldritch terror to your table</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bring a taste of terror to your game nights with this bundle from Chaosium, complete with everything you need to run the dreaded (yet beloved) <em>Call of Cthulhu</em> RPG system! On top of the <em>Call of Cthulhu Starter Set</em>, you’ll get the <em>Investigator Handbook</em>, replete with expanded rules for creating player characters, as well as the <em>Keeper Rulebook</em>, brimming with all the information you need to keep things orderly as your table descends into madness. You’ll also get tons of adventures, including some aimed at first-time game masters, as well as entire campaigns! Pay what you want for over 25 books and game aids for this seminal RPG and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!<br><br><strong><span style="color: #ef9741;">Codes are redeemable through the DriveThruRPG website.</span></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applied Machine Learning Mastery by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/applied-machine-learning-mastery-packt-books</link>
      <description>Applied machine learning made easy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Never stop growing—learn the latest computer science techniques with the Applied Machine Learning Mastery Bundle by Packt. Machine learning continues to be one of the fastest-growing industries in technology, and this bundle is designed to teach you the fundamentals on a variety of commonly used platforms. Get the hottest courses like <em>Machine Learning with PyTorch</em>, <em>Mathematics of Machine Learning</em>, <em>Python Machine Learning by Example</em>, and more—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the Against Malaria Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fierce Women of Science Fiction, Fantasy &amp; Horror by Open Road Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/fierce-women-science-fiction-fantasy-horror-open-road-media-books</link>
      <description>Female fronted fiction for every genre fan</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Male-dominated genre fiction? Not in this bundle. There are tons of talented women working within the realms of sci-fi, fantasy, and horror, and for our latest deal we’ve teamed up with Open Road Media to offer over 60 of the best, most unique, and most unforgettable books from icons of female written fiction. In this ebook collection, you’ll meet an immortal water witch who dreams of releasing the great Leviathan in Cherie Priest’s <em>Fathom</em>. You’ll run from zombies with intrepid news reporters in Mira Grant’s <em>Feedback</em>. You’ll puzzle over an elderly woman’s dual sets of memories (and children) in Jo Walton’s <em>My Real Children</em>. You’ll immerse yourself in stories of Caribbean folklore and fantasy in Nalo Hopkinson’s <em>Skin Folk</em>. There’s so much more to enjoy in this great bundle, so grab it now at the price of your choosing, and support young adult mental health charity Active Minds with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Designing Game Play by Taylor &amp; Francis</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/designing-game-play-taylor-francis-books</link>
      <description>Build games from the ground up</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want to become a bona fide game developer with the Designing Gameplay Bundle from the experts at Taylor & Francis! Start formulating your own one-off board games, design custom VR experiences, learn to publish video games, and so much more. Soak up all the good stuff from informative and entertaining game design ebooks like <em>We Deserve Better Villains</em>, <em>Passion and Play</em>, and <em>Making It HUGE in Video Games</em> when you shop with Humble.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamite Character Crossover Comics by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dynamite-character-crossover-comics-dynamite-books</link>
      <description>Killer character crossovers for the new year</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve assembled Dynamite Entertainment’s hottest eComics into a bundle you won’t want to miss. Vampirella, John Carter of Mars, Red Sonja, and the universe’s greatest heroes collide in an epic series of battles across <em>DIE!NAMITE Vols. 1–6</em>. Grab your boomstick for the action-packed mayhem of <em>Army of Darkness: Ash vs. the Classic Monsters, Vols. 1–6</em>. Bad guys beware—the femme fatales of Dynamite unite to stop a legendary evil in <em>Swords of Sorrow: The Complete Saga</em>. Pay what you want and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adulting for Dummies by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/adulting-for-dummies-wiley-books</link>
      <description>Adulting is hard—let’s help</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Need some cheat codes for life? We’re here to help you figure out adulting with a little help from our latest For Dummies Bundle. The experts at Wiley can prepare you for anything with their award-winning series of ebooks, including <em>Renting For Dummies</em>, <em>Modern Dating For Dummies</em>, <em>How to Fix Everything For Dummies</em>, and much more. Make 2026 the best year of your adult life and help support Worldreader when you learn new skills and save big.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Guide to AI APIs by Mammoth</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-guide-to-ai-apis-mammoth-books</link>
      <description>Accelerate your advancement in AI today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Want to learn new tech skills? Make your New Year’s resolution a fresh goal that’ll revolutionize your life with the Ultimate Guide to AI APIs Bundle by Mammoth Club. Get serious about the next frontier of technology and make AI a focal point of your 2026 development plan with hot courses like <em>The Self-Hosted AI Handbook – Guidebook to Building Local LLMs</em> and <em>AI-Powered Career Mastery – Transform Your Personal Brand and Job Search</em>. Pay what you want for industry-leading instruction and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lone Wolf &amp; Cub and Other Manga Classics by Koike ENCORE by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/lone-wolf-cub-and-more-koike-encore-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Formative manga curated for you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the sprawling, epic story of a swordsman and his son in our popular <em>Lone Wolf and Cub</em> bundle from Dark Horse Comics—back again for a limited time! This formative 1970s’ manga series, written by the brilliant Kazuo Koike and featuring the breathtaking visuals of Goseki Kojima, is widely regarded as one of the most influential works of graphic fiction ever created, inspiring countless storytellers, artists, and filmmakers across Japan and beyond. Read these and other classic Koike series like <em>Crying Freeman</em> and <em>Lady Snowblood</em>, and help support the Hero Initiative too.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year, Fiercely You! by Berret-Koehler</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/new-year-fiercely-you-berretkoehler-books</link>
      <description>New Year’s resolutions made simple…and fun!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The cusp of a new year is a time to reflect and a time to plan. Who do you want to be in 2026? Do you want to hit the gym more? Improve your finances? Make new friends? Whatever your goals, real change starts from the inside out, and this bundle of self improvement ebooks from Berret-Koehler has everything you need to learn how to better yourself while still being you! <em>Fiercely You: Be Fabulous and Confident While Thinking Like a Drag Queen</em> uses the trade secrets of drag culture to teach confidence and self-worth. <em>Eat That Frog! 21 Great Ways to Stop Procrastinating</em> will teach you mental tricks to be more productive. <em>Flux: 8 Superpowers for Thriving in Constant Change</em> will help you master the art of going with the flow, no matter where it takes you. Becoming the best version of yourself is easy with this bundle, and every purchase supports Worldreader’s efforts to keep kids reading!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>