<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 08:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Glen Cook&#39;s Chronicles of The Black Company &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/glen-cooks-chronicles-black-company-more-books</link>
      <description>From the Godfather of Grimdark, read the series that started it all!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Welcome the most legendary Book Bundle across the Sixteen Worlds—Glen Cook's bestselling Chronicles of The Black Company & More! The Black Company is Cook's acclaimed epic fantasy series following a group of hard-bitten mercenaries waging war on behalf of The Lady, who may be the very manifestation of evil itself. <br><br>"With the Black Company series Glen Cook single-handedly changed the face of fantasy."— Steven Erikson, New York Times bestselling author <br><br>Get Glen Cook's finest works, headlined by the complete Black Company collection—and gear up for the next installment arriving in late 2025! Pay what you want and help support the Call of Duty Endowment with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World of Darkness: Month of Darkness 2025 Digital Bundle by Renegade Game Studios</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/world-darkness-month-darkness-2025-digital-bundle-renegade-game-studios-books</link>
      <description>A masquerade of blood &amp; intrigue</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create your own original vampire, torn between survival, supremacy, and your unquenchable thirst for mortal blood with the Month of Darkness 2025 Digital Bundle by Renegade Game Studios! Fifth Edition marks a triumphant return to Vampire: The Masquerade’s original vision—boldly modernized for the 21st century with streamlined gameplay and quality-of-life updates. The rules have been reimagined, yet the deep lore remains, advancing the metaplot and revealing the latest twists in the World of Darkness. Host the bloodiest, most unforgettable TTRPG nights—and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World of Darkness: Month of Darkness 2025 Physical Book Bundle by Renegade Game Studios</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/world-darkness-month-darkness-2025-physical-book-bundle-renegade-game-studios-books</link>
      <description>Embrace the World of Darkness, Physically</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create an original vampire character, torn between survival, supremacy, and your unquenchable thirst for mortal blood with the Month of Darkness 2025 Physical Bundle by Renegade Game Studios! This collection of Fifth Edition tomes marks a triumphant return to Vampire: The Masquerade’s original vision—boldly modernized for the 21st century with streamlined gameplay and quality-of-life updates. The rules have been reimagined, yet the deep lore remains, advancing the metaplot and revealing the latest twists in the World of Darkness. Host the bloodiest, most unforgettable TTRPG nights—and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Month by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-month-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Buckle up for Cybersecurity Month</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Online scams and malware are everywhere in 2025—what are you doing to protect yourself? Prevent security breaches before they happen with the techniques and tools from the Humble Tech Book Bundle: Cybersecurity Month by O’Reilly. Top titles from this curated library include <em>Intelligent Continuous Security</em> and <em>Attack Surface Management</em>. Learn software supply chain security and DevSecOps, build an original cyber risk management program, and more. Pay what you want to gain essential digital defense skills and help support Code for America with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Mignola&#39;s Hellboy, Witchfinder and More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mike-mignolas-hellboy-witchfinder-and-more-books</link>
      <description>Some of the strangest chapters from the Hellboy Universe in one bundle!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate the iconic works of comic book author Mike Mignola with great titles starring Hellboy—the half-demon, half-human paranormal investigator who spotlights the latest Humble Comics Bundle.   Get the very best titles from <em>Hellboy</em> and <em>Witchfinder</em> in one curated library of 30+ badass comic—read <em>Young Hellboy: Assault on Castle Death</em>, <em>Hellboy: The Silver Lantern Club</em>, <em>Witchfinder Volume 1: In the Service of Angels</em>, and more. Pay what you want for more than 3 decades of amazing characters and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Heroes in a Half-Shell</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/teenage-mutant-ninja-turtles-heroes-in-halfshell-books</link>
      <description>Leo, Don, Raph, and Mike in one bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Follow the iconic adventures of the legendary <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</em> with our latest Humble Comics Bundle! The <em>TMNT</em> team of Leonardo, Donatello, Raphael, and Michelangelo has been kicking butt and protecting New York City since 1984—across the big screen, TV, and comics. Order a pizza (without anchovies) and read the very best <em>TMNT</em> comics like <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles, Vol. 1: Return to New York</em>, <em>Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: The Last Ronin</em>, and more. Save some green on awesome comics with Humble Bundle, and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase—COWABUNGA! <br><br><a style="color: #EF9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account. </em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cisco Networking and Certification by Cisco Press/Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cisco-networking-and-certification-cisco-presspearson-books</link>
      <description>Ace networking certs with ease</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ready to take your Cisco networking certification exams seriously? Then you need the latest Humble Tech Book Bundle from Pearson. Learn everything you need from IT support to security identity management within one curated library of courses. <br><br>Get the hottest and most comprehensive official certification guides like <em>CCNP SPCOR 350-501</em>, <em>CCNP and CCIE Security Core SCOR 350-701</em>, and more—plus, the prep guide, <em>31 Days Before your CCNA Exam</em>. Dominate your exams and help support Active Minds with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer RPG Starter Bundle by Cubicle7</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/warhammer-rpg-starter-bundle-cubicle7-books</link>
      <description>Bring glory to the Imperium</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with our latest tabletop role-playing game collection, Warhammer RPG Starter Bundle by Cubicle7. No two conquests for the Imperium of Man are the same with endless fun ahead.   This expansive TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources based in the <em>Warhammer 40,000</em> universe like <em>Warhammer Age of Sigmar: Soulbound</em>, <em>Warhammer 40;000: Wrath & Glory</em>, <em>Warhammer Fantasy Roleplay</em>, and more. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support Children's Health Foundation with your purchase.<br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The ebooks in this bundle are available through the DriveThru RPG website.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XCrawl Xtreme Dungeon Crawl Superbundle by Goodman Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/xcrawl-xtreme-dungeon-crawl-superbundle-goodman-games-books</link>
      <description>Xtreme fun with Xcrawl</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Xtreme fun awaits with the all-new XCrawl Xtreme Dungeon Crawl Superbundle by Goodman Games! Explore a world that’s a twisted reflection of our own—roleplay as a hero in a live-streaming-obsessed society where fame, power, and survival are always on the line. This library includes thrilling campaigns like <em>Xcrawl Classics #6: Dooms 2 Go</em>, <em>Xcrawl Classics #2: Tropicrawl Cataclysm</em>, and more. Everything you need to embark on epic adventures is packed into these <em>Xcrawl</em> gamebooks and beyond. Pay what you want for a fresh twist on the classic tabletop role-playing formula and help support It Gets Better with your purchase.  <br><br><a style="color: #EF9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through two partners: some on DTRPG, and some with Goodman.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Boys Vs. Everyone</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/boys-vs-everyone-books</link>
      <description>End summer with Homelander </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bloody good graphic novels are here—follow the gruesome adventures of Billy Butcher and The Boys as they take on Vought and Homelander with our latest Humble Comics Bundle: The Boys Vs. Everyone! This collection of graphic novels is not for the faint of heart—but if you enjoy hyper-violence, action, suspense, and a gritty take on the superhero genre, then this series is for you. Get all 12 volumes of <em>The Boys</em>, plus <em>Evil Ernie</em>, <em>Sacred Six</em>, and more. Get ahead of the streaming series before the new season drops and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Electronics for the Curious by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/electronics-for-the-curious-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Make new connections with tech </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expand your horizons or pick up new hobbies with our latest Tech Book Bundle: Electronics for the Curious. This expansive ebook library from No Starch is a curated collection of titles designed to make technology approachable and fun to learn. Dive into engaging reads like <em>The Game Console 2.0</em>—a visual homage to video game consoles throughout history, <em>Open Circuits</em>—a photographic journey into the beautiful design inside everyday electronics, <em>Arduino for Arduinians</em>—a hands-on guide to mastering this versatile microcontroller platform, and more! Pay what you want to level up your personal library and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall in Love With Shojo by Kodansha</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/fall-in-love-with-shojo-kodansha-bookbundle</link>
      <description>Fall in love with Shojo </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fill up on shojo manga this fall as Kodansha and Humble team-up to offer fans digital volumes of dramatic, heartwarming, and surprising sagas during the Fall In Love With Shojo Bundle! Just $30 gets you more than 80 digital volumes and over $900 worth of manga. This includes all volumes of modern classics like the love story steeped in trauma and healing, MARS, the magical girl adventure Shugo Chara!, the frenemies and lovers high school rom-com, Peach Girl, and more. Not only that but fans can catch up on nearly all volumes of the ongoing tender and wholesome school days romance, A Condition Called Love. It’s a perfect bundle for anyone who loves shojo or is curious to try some of Kodansha’s best. Explore amazing shojo manga from Kodansha and help support The BINC Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>