<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 06:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies and Games for Dummies by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hobbies-and-games-for-dummies-wiley-books</link>
      <description>Read up before hitting the courts</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to pick up a new hobby? Learn how to play sports and create using your hands with help from our latest For Dummies Bundle. The experts at Wiley can prepare you for anything with ebooks like <em>Manga For Dummies</em>, <em>Pickleball For Dummies</em>, <em>Welding For Dummies</em>, and much more. Impress your friends and stay active alongside them today with our Hobbies and Games for Dummies bundle. Plus, your purchase helps support Safe In Our World. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elfquest: The Dark Horse Collection Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/elfquest-dark-horse-collection-encore-books</link>
      <description>Journey to the World of Two Moons</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the saga of Cutter, chief of the elfin tribe of the Wolfriders, and his epic quest across the World of Two Moons in <em>ElfQuest</em>, Wendy and Richard Pini’s long-running fantasy graphic novel series. This expansive collection, published by Dark Horse, includes <em>The Complete ElfQuest Volumes 1 - 7</em>, <em>The Final Quest</em>, and <em>Stargazer’s Hunt</em>. Celebrate 45 years of <em>ElfQuest</em>, and support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux from Beginner to Professional by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/linux-from-beginner-to-professional-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Make Linux your second language</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Break into the powerful world of Linux with this insightful collection of courses by O’Reilly. Our latest bundle will teach you the fundamentals to build upon so you can master Linux in no time. Start learning today from amazing courses like <em>Learning Modern Linux</em>, <em>Practical Linux System Administration</em>, and <em>Python for DevOps</em>. Get the resources you need to go from a novice coder and to a seasoned pro with a budding career—and help support Code For America!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witchblade and Darkness 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/witchblade-and-darkness-2025-books</link>
      <description>Discover your new favorite comic series</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Addicting page-turning comics are only a click away with our latest bundle. Within our Witchblade and Darkness Bundle, you’ll find amazing graphic novel-style storytelling catering to an adult audience. Experience rich stories of pain, power, and triumph in 100 issues of the original <em>Witchblade</em>, <em>Witchblade 2024 #1-#6</em>, <em>Artifacts #0</em>, <em>Darkness #1-#20</em>, and more! Top Cow Comics offers some of the best indie comics—take a leap and try them today. Your purchase helps support the Hero Initiative too!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masters at Work Career Guides by Simon &amp; Schuster</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/masters-at-work-career-guides-simon-schuster-books</link>
      <description>Your next career is only a bundle away</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unlock your potential and learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed in a variety of desirable industries. Our Masters at Work Career Guide Bundle by Simon & Schuster contains 25+ ebooks that can help transform your professional pursuits with outstanding books including <em>Becoming a Video Game Designer</em>, <em>Becoming an Ethical Hacker</em>, <em>Becoming a Crime Scene Investigator</em>, and more! Begin your new career journey today and help support Worldreader with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Every Database by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mastering-every-database-packt-books</link>
      <description>Become a database mastermind</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to master every database with this curated collection by the professionals at Packt. Inside this 15+ course library, you’ll get pro quality lessons like <em>Mastering PostgreSQL 17</em>, <em>Amazon DynamoDB - The Definitive Guide</em>, <em>Database Design and Modeling with Google Cloud</em>, and more! Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support the International Medical Corps with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sports Trailblazers: Legends Who Changed the Game</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/sports-trailblazers-legends-who-changed-game-books</link>
      <description>You won’t believe these sports stories</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get a collection of amazing sports tales with our latest book bundle in partnership with Sports Publishing. Read the untold stories of sports greatest giants at highest, lowest, and most shocking. Gripping titles like <em>Banned: How I Squandered An All-Star NBA Career Before Finding My Redemption</em>, <em>Champions Of The Octagon: One-On-One With MMA And UFC Greats</em>, and <em>Tomlin: The Soul Of A Football Coach</em>. Help support the BINC Foundation and get great books too!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Terry Moore Collection by Abstract Studios Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-terry-moore-collection-abstract-studios-tbc-books-encore</link>
      <description>Tales of love, murder, and hi-tech battle suits</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover some of comics’ most indelible characters in the universe of Eisner Award–winning artist & writer Terry Moore! Get caught up in the lives of Katchoo, Francine, and David in the complete run of the groundbreaking series <em>Strangers in Paradise</em>. Meet Julie, whose life changes forever when liquid metal rains from the sky in <em>Echo</em>. Unravel the mystery of a woman who wakes up in her own grave in <em>Rachel Rising</em>. Plus, your purchase helps support The Hero Initiative!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5th Edition Adventures, Crafting, Monsters and VTT Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/5th-edition-adventures-crafting-monsters-and-vtt-assets-books</link>
      <description>Elevate your next D&amp;D adventure </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for new takes on classic adventures within the <em>Dungeons & Dragons</em> universe—this action-packed bundle supports one of the most iconic games ever! Our 5th Edition-centric TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources like <em>Endless Encounters: Dungeons</em>, <em>Ultimate Bestiary - The Dreaded Accursed</em>, <em>Deck of Dirty Tricks Vol 1.</em>, and more! Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey alongside your closest allies and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Engineer Masterclass by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/machine-learning-engineer-masterclass-packt-books</link>
      <description>Machine learning solutions for the future</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master machine learning with this comprehensive bundle of in-depth lessons from Packt. Inside this expertly curated library of 21 books, you'll uncover industry-leading insights from our newest resources like LLM Engineer's Handbook, Python Machine Learning By Example, The Machine Learning Solutions Architect Handbook, and many more! Whether you're starting your journey or advancing your expertise, this bundle offers everything you need to excel in areas like natural language processing, neural networks, and real-world ML applications. Transform your understanding of machine learning and help support Direct Relief, providing life-saving medical aid across the globe, with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Piano and More for Dummies by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/piano-and-more-for-dummies-wiley-books</link>
      <description>Piano playing made easy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hit all the right keys with our latest music bundle from Wiley! Get ebooks to teach you piano and other general musical skills like <em>Piano & Keyboard All-in-One For Dummies</em>, <em>Music Composition For Dummies</em>, <em>Songwriting For Dummies</em>, and <em>Piano Exercises For Dummies</em>. The experts behind the <em>For Dummies</em> series have been helping with reading and learning a variety of skills for more than 30 years, and their lessons will have you creating original music with ease. Plus, your purchase directly helps support Music Will— a nonprofit supporting future generations of musicians.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>