<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 08:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Electronics for the Curious by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/electronics-for-the-curious-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Make new connections with tech </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expand your horizons or pick up new hobbies with our latest Tech Book Bundle: Electronics for the Curious. This expansive ebook library from No Starch is a curated collection of titles designed to make technology approachable and fun to learn. Dive into engaging reads like <em>The Game Console 2.0</em>—a visual homage to video game consoles throughout history, <em>Open Circuits</em>—a photographic journey into the beautiful design inside everyday electronics, <em>Arduino for Arduinians</em>—a hands-on guide to mastering this versatile microcontroller platform, and more! Pay what you want to level up your personal library and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swords and Wizardry RPG Mega Bundle by Necromancer Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/swords-and-wizardry-rpg-mega-bundle-necromancer-games-books</link>
      <description>Unleash the Legends of Old-School Fantasy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[For fifteen years, Frog God Games and Necromancer Games have been the torchbearers of sword-and-sorcery adventure, bringing Swords & Wizardry players hundreds of sprawling dungeons, haunted wildernesses, and perilous towns to explore. Now, for the first time ever, you can claim a  colossal treasure trove of 60+ titles, all in PDF form, spanning adventures, campaign settings, monsters, and rule expansions. Whether you’re a grizzled dungeon-crawling veteran or a new initiate to the OSR, this collection arms you with everything needed to run years of campaigns dripping with danger, discovery, and dark fantasy.  But the bundle doesn’t stop with digital loot. At the highest tier, you’ll also receive a true collector’s prize: <em>Heart of the Razor</em> in hardcover print-a legendary adventure book nearly out of circulation. <b>Only 500 copies remain, and once they’re gone, they’re gone forever.</b> This is your last chance to hold a piece of Swords & Wizardry history in your hands, straight from the Frog God vault. Every dollar supports both the publishers who have carried the OSR flame and Child’s Play. You’ll get classic adventures, rare treasures, and a seat at the fire with the gods of old-school gaming.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fall in Love With Shojo by Kodansha</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/fall-in-love-with-shojo-kodansha-bookbundle</link>
      <description>Fall in love with Shojo </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fill up on shojo manga this fall as Kodansha and Humble team-up to offer fans digital volumes of dramatic, heartwarming, and surprising sagas during the Fall In Love With Shojo Bundle! Just $30 gets you more than 80 digital volumes and over $900 worth of manga. This includes all volumes of modern classics like the love story steeped in trauma and healing, MARS, the magical girl adventure Shugo Chara!, the frenemies and lovers high school rom-com, Peach Girl, and more. Not only that but fans can catch up on nearly all volumes of the ongoing tender and wholesome school days romance, A Condition Called Love. It’s a perfect bundle for anyone who loves shojo or is curious to try some of Kodansha’s best. Explore amazing shojo manga from Kodansha and help support The BINC Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Programming Languages Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-programming-languages-bundle-packt-books</link>
      <description>The Ultimate Programming Bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unlock the world of programming with Packt’s Ultimate Programming Languages Bundle. Whether you’re writing your very first line of code or levelling up your professional skills, this collection of 35 expert books will guide you through today’s most important languages. Start at the foundation with accessible guides to Python and JavaScript, perfect for beginners who want to grasp the essentials quickly. Move up a tier to expand your toolkit with Java, C++, and Go, plus deeper dives into object-oriented programming and clean software design. Pay a little more and gain full access to the complete library of 26 additional titles, covering Rust, Kotlin, Swift, TypeScript, PHP, and Haskell alongside advanced Python, C++, and Java resources. Explore cookbooks, design pattern handbooks, and in-depth problem solvers that help you write cleaner, faster, and more professional code. This bundle is your passport to mastering the full spectrum of modern programming. Whether your goal is to build software from scratch, explore functional and object-oriented paradigms, or sharpen your craft with advanced techniques, you’ll find the resources here. Best of all, your purchase helps support charity while you expand your coding skills.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image in the 2000s</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/image-in-2000s-books</link>
      <description>Open the Image Comics vault </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Head back to the turn of the millennium, courtesy of Image Comics! Pick up acclaimed series including <em>Chew</em>, <em>I Kill Giants</em>, <em>Age of Bronze</em>, and more. Plus, expand your collection with the continued adventures of legendary characters like Spawn, Savage Dragon, and Witchblade. Thousands of pages await your virtual bookshelf, and each purchase supports The Book Industry Charitable Foundation!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Primer Bundle by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-primer-bundle-paizo-books</link>
      <description>Forge your own high-fantasy adventures</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A world of adventure and danger awaits—and the only thing missing is your heroism. Gather your party of trusty companions for countless quests with our latest <em>Pathfinder</em> bundle from Paizo. Mix up your fun with the hottest <em>Pathfinder</em> TTRPG campaigns and expansions like <em>Pathfinder Second Edition Beginner Box: Remastered Edition</em>, <em>Pathfinder Player Core</em>, <em>Sky King’s Tomb Player’s Guide</em>, and more. Get everything you need to embark on an epic high-fantasy journey together, and help support Take This! with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create the Future Now! MEAP Early Access Program Books and liveProjects by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/create-future-now-meap-early-access-program-books-and-liveprojects-manning-books</link>
      <description>Create the future now with early access to these Manning books!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills of the future and beyond with the latest Humble Tech Learning Bundle. This comprehensive library of Manning Early Access Program books and hands-on liveProjects will give you a head start on your next big thing. This bundle includes AI Applications Made Easy, Learn Docker in a Monty of Lunches, Python Workout, Second Edition, Secrets of the JavaScript Ninja, Third Edition, and other bestsellers. Start a new career using AI, learn to program in Python or C,  and more today! The future is yours—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the charity of your choice.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Master’s Guild Top Content from the D&amp;D Community</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dungeon-masters-guild-bestselling-tabletop-dd-community-books</link>
      <description>Jump-start your next campaign</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your party and unleash the full might of Dungeons & Dragons with this ultimate D&D accessories bundle! Forged in partnership with the Dungeon Masters Guild and authorized by Wizards of the Coast, this legendary collection spills over with challenging adventures, groundbreaking rule expansions, and must-have player options. Brave sprawling modern epics like <em>Call From the Deep</em> and <em>The Haunt</em>, or level up your campaign with treasure troves of character options from <em>Xanathar’s Lost Notes to Everything Else</em>. Whether you’re a shapeshifting Druid, relentless Barbarian, or iron-willed Monk, this bundle is a veritable loot table of D&D treasures. Expand your table, ignite your imagination, and join the fight for good — every purchase supports Extra Life! <br><br><a style="color: #EF9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through two partners: some on DMsGuild, and some with Roll20.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Guide to Tabletop RPGs, Worldbuilding, and Folklore by Adams Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-guide-to-tabletop-rpgs-worldbuilding-and-folklore-adams-media-books</link>
      <description>Level up your TTRPG life-stats (+10)</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add new tabletop RPG skills, techniques, and knowledge to your gaming toolbelt with the all-new Humble Book Bundle: The Ultimate Guide to Tabletop RPGs, Worldbuilding, and Folklore. This massive library of curated titles from Adams Media is perfect for TTRPG mega-fans and newcomers alike. Discover exciting insights from ebooks like <em>Ultimate RPG Game Master's Guide</em>, <em>Norse Mythology: The Gods, Goddesses, and Heroes Handbook</em>, and more. Level up your TTRPG life-stats (+10) and help support Worldreader with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Infrastructure and DevOps Toolkit by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cloud-infrastructure-and-devops-toolkit-packt-books</link>
      <description>Live in the clouds with AWS &amp; Azure</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become a 21st-century superstar with the latest Humble Tech Book Bundle: Cloud Infrastructure and DevOps Toolkit. Learn the intricacies of Amazon Web Services with industry-leading courses like <em>AWS for Solutions Architects</em> and <em>AWS Cloud Projects</em>—master Microsoft Azure with professional-quality lessons like <em>Hands-On MLOps on Azure</em> and <em>Azure for Developers</em>. This comprehensive library includes lessons, practice tests, and resources perfect for novices and seasoned professionals alike—build strong foundations in cloud infrastructure and help support No Kid Hungry with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Martha Wells&#39; Murderbot and More by TOR</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/martha-wells-murderbot-and-more-tor-books</link>
      <description>Martha Wells&#39; Murderbot &amp; More</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fall for the series that inspired the Apple TV+ hit with the all-new Martha Wells' Murderbot & More Bundle! Wells' Murderbot Diaries series tells the on-going story of an artificial Security Unit that hacks its governor module, enabling it to rebel against its programming. Unlike most constructs, Murderbot just wants to be left alone to stream the tens of thousands of hours of streaming media it's downloaded to its memory banks. But as much as it wants to avoid the human drama around it, Murderbot just keeps getting dragged back in. <br><br>This multi-Hugo Award-winning series includes standout titles like <em>All Systems Red</em> and <em>Artificial Condition</em>. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support World Central Kitchen.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture 2025 by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-architecture-2025-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Software architecture made easy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your skills in software architecture with the latest Humble Tech Book Bundle. Unlock hundreds of hours of valuable information inside this 25 course library. Gain expert insights from professional-quality lessons like <em>Cloud Application Architecture Patterns</em>, <em>Facilitating Software Architecture</em>, and more—pay what you want to deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>