<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 06:27:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sex, Love, and Everything In Between</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/sex-love-and-everything-in-between-books</link>
      <description>Our hottest and steamiest bundle yet</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Spice up your sex life with a little help from the experts at Adams Media. Don’t be shy—this Sex, Love, and Everything In Between Bundle is perfect for everyone. Teach yourself new tricks or delve into something adventurous and unknown, the sensual choices are yours. Explore the contents of titillating titles like <em>365 Questions For Couples</em>, <em>1001 Sexcapades to Do If You Dare</em>, and more. Add a little something to your love life and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!  <br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences. User discretion is advised.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Cybersecurity Career by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-cybersecurity-career-packt-books</link>
      <description>Jump-start your cybersecurity career</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to build the foundation for a new career in cybersecurity—the pros at Packt are giving you the expert insights you need to succeed in a variety of cybersecurity subsectors. Gain insights from courses like <em>Automating Security Detection Engineering</em>, <em>AWS Certified Security</em>, <em>Pentesting Active Directory and Windows-based Infrastructure</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder &amp; Starfinder Comics by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-starfinder-comics-dynamite-books</link>
      <description>A curated collection of elite comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in a library of fantastic graphic fiction in this bundle of comics from Dynamite Entertainment! Delve into <em>Pathfinder: Runescars #1-5</em>, <em>Starfinder: Angels of the Drift #1-5</em>, <em>Pathfinder: Spiral of Bones #1-5</em>, and 70+ more amazing titles all within one bundle. This curated collection is perfect for fans of high fantasy, scifi, and everything in between. Act now—get amazing comics and help a charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MORE Tabletop RPG Resources by Dicegeeks</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/more-tabletop-rpg-resources-dicegeeks-books</link>
      <description>D&amp;D resources suited for any style</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing books from Dicegeeks. This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains an amazing variety of rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources that enhance your favorite <em>Dungeons & Dragons</em> games—we’ve included standouts like <em>The Book of Random Tables: Festivals and Fairs</em> and <em>The Book of Random Tables: Superheroes</em>. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support Children's Miracle Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Programming by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/game-programming-pearson-books</link>
      <description>The perfect toolbox for game creation</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Let’s start building games—level up your coding skills with our Gaming Programming by Pearson Bundle! Learn the basics and advanced techniques needed to develop original games that are only limited by your imagination. This 20+ library of extremely useful courses includes standouts like <em>Roblox Game Development in 24 Hours: The Official Roblox Guide</em>, <em>Fundamentals of Game Design</em>, and more. Get the resources you need to start a new career, and help support Girls Make Games Scholarship Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hobbies and Games for Dummies by Wiley</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hobbies-and-games-for-dummies-wiley-books</link>
      <description>Read up before hitting the courts</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Have you ever wanted to pick up a new hobby? Learn how to play sports and create using your hands with help from our latest For Dummies Bundle. The experts at Wiley can prepare you for anything with ebooks like <em>Manga For Dummies</em>, <em>Pickleball For Dummies</em>, <em>Welding For Dummies</em>, and much more. Impress your friends and stay active alongside them today with our Hobbies and Games for Dummies bundle. Plus, your purchase helps support Safe In Our World. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elfquest: The Dark Horse Collection Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/elfquest-dark-horse-collection-encore-books</link>
      <description>Journey to the World of Two Moons</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the saga of Cutter, chief of the elfin tribe of the Wolfriders, and his epic quest across the World of Two Moons in <em>ElfQuest</em>, Wendy and Richard Pini’s long-running fantasy graphic novel series. This expansive collection, published by Dark Horse, includes <em>The Complete ElfQuest Volumes 1 - 7</em>, <em>The Final Quest</em>, and <em>Stargazer’s Hunt</em>. Celebrate 45 years of <em>ElfQuest</em>, and support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux from Beginner to Professional by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/linux-from-beginner-to-professional-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Make Linux your second language</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Break into the powerful world of Linux with this insightful collection of courses by O’Reilly. Our latest bundle will teach you the fundamentals to build upon so you can master Linux in no time. Start learning today from amazing courses like <em>Learning Modern Linux</em>, <em>Practical Linux System Administration</em>, and <em>Python for DevOps</em>. Get the resources you need to go from a novice coder and to a seasoned pro with a budding career—and help support Code For America!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Witchblade and Darkness 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/witchblade-and-darkness-2025-books</link>
      <description>Discover your new favorite comic series</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Addicting page-turning comics are only a click away with our latest bundle. Within our Witchblade and Darkness Bundle, you’ll find amazing graphic novel-style storytelling catering to an adult audience. Experience rich stories of pain, power, and triumph in 100 issues of the original <em>Witchblade</em>, <em>Witchblade 2024 #1-#6</em>, <em>Artifacts #0</em>, <em>Darkness #1-#20</em>, and more! Top Cow Comics offers some of the best indie comics—take a leap and try them today. Your purchase helps support the Hero Initiative too!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Masters at Work Career Guides by Simon &amp; Schuster</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/masters-at-work-career-guides-simon-schuster-books</link>
      <description>Your next career is only a bundle away</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unlock your potential and learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed in a variety of desirable industries. Our Masters at Work Career Guide Bundle by Simon & Schuster contains 25+ ebooks that can help transform your professional pursuits with outstanding books including <em>Becoming a Video Game Designer</em>, <em>Becoming an Ethical Hacker</em>, <em>Becoming a Crime Scene Investigator</em>, and more! Begin your new career journey today and help support Worldreader with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering Every Database by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mastering-every-database-packt-books</link>
      <description>Become a database mastermind</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to master every database with this curated collection by the professionals at Packt. Inside this 15+ course library, you’ll get pro quality lessons like <em>Mastering PostgreSQL 17</em>, <em>Amazon DynamoDB - The Definitive Guide</em>, <em>Database Design and Modeling with Google Cloud</em>, and more! Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support the International Medical Corps with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Engineer Masterclass by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/machine-learning-engineer-masterclass-packt-books</link>
      <description>Machine learning solutions for the future</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master machine learning with this comprehensive bundle of in-depth lessons from Packt. Inside this expertly curated library of 21 books, you'll uncover industry-leading insights from our newest resources like LLM Engineer's Handbook, Python Machine Learning By Example, The Machine Learning Solutions Architect Handbook, and many more! Whether you're starting your journey or advancing your expertise, this bundle offers everything you need to excel in areas like natural language processing, neural networks, and real-world ML applications. Transform your understanding of machine learning and help support Direct Relief, providing life-saving medical aid across the globe, with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>