<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 20:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Python: From Beginner to Advanced by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/python-from-beginner-to-advanced-packt-books</link>
      <description>Perfect your skills in Python</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills with the Python: From Beginner to Advanced Bundle by Packt. Learn to code using one of the most popular and widely used formats within the industry and gain amazing insights from courses like <em>Learn Python Programming</em>, <em>Building AI Intensive Python Applications</em>, <em>Modern Time Series Forecasting with Python</em>, and more. This library of 20+ programming guides are perfect for novice coders and seasoned pros in growing your career. Plus, your purchase helps support the Python Software Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iron Kingdoms Collection by Steamforged</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/iron-kingdoms-collection-steamforged-books</link>
      <description>Journey to the fabled Iron Kingdoms</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your friends for countless hours of adventure with the Iron Kingdoms Collection by Steamforged Games. Our TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources for the Iron Kingdoms Roleplaying Game and Iron Kingdoms 5e. Explore rich lands powered by steam and magic, encounter beasts and constructs, and engage in epic battles in a full metal fantasy universe. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support Child’s Play Charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megadungeon Megabundle for DCC &amp; 5E by Goodman Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/megadungeon-megabundle-for-dcc-5e-goodman-games-books</link>
      <description>D&amp;D, DCC, and an amazing mega bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Mages and Elves rejoice! Gather up your party for endless adventure with this mega bundle of tabletop role-playing games by Goodman Games! This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources for <em>Dungeons & Dragons</em> and <em>Dungeon Crawl Classics</em>. Play hot campaigns like <em>Dungeon Crawl Classics - Dark Tower</em>, <em>Dungeon Crawl Classics #83: The Chained Coffin</em> and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase. Embark on new quests with your friends and make your ordinary night extraordinary.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Science the Fun Way by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/computer-science-fun-way-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Master computer science the fun way</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed when you take on computer science the fun way. Our latest bundle by No Starch features 15+ books with expert insights on the foundational and advanced skills you need to start a new career in computer science. Standout books like <em>Graph Algorithms the Fun Way</em> and <em>Data Structures the Fun Way</em> will help deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or seasoned professional. Plus, your purchase helps support the Electronic Frontier Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warhammer 40,000 Roleplay: Wrath &amp; Glory by Cubicle 7</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/warhammer-40000-roleplay-wrath-glory-cubicle-7-books</link>
      <description>Bring the wrath—earn the glory</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Our latest <em>Warhammer 40,000</em> bundle gives you the freedom to roleplay your way! Sit down with your friends, decide what kind of story you want to tell, and host an awesome <em>Warhammer 40,000 Roleplay: Wrath &amp; Glory</em> adventure. Download the core rulebook and additional campaigns like <em>Space Marine 2 - Purge the Swarm</em>, <em>Threat Assessment: Xenos</em> PDF, and more! Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey in the darkness of the 41st Millennium, and help support Children's Health Ireland with your purchase!<br><br><em><sub>Warhammer 40,000 Roleplay: Wrath &amp; Glory © Copyright Games Workshop Limited 2025. Warhammer 40,000 Roleplay, the Warhammer 40,000 Roleplay logo, Wrath &amp; Glory, the Wrath &amp; Glory logo, GW, Games Workshop, Space Marine, 40k, Warhammer, Warhammer 40,000, 40,000, the ‘Aquila’ Doubleheaded Eagle logo, and all associated logos, illustrations, images, names, creatures, races, vehicles, locations, weapons, characters, and the distinctive likeness thereof, are either ® or ™, and/or © Games Workshop Limited, variably registered around the world, and used under licence. Cubicle 7 Entertainment and the Cubicle 7 Entertainment logo are trademarks of Cubicle 7 Entertainment Limited. All rights reserved.</sub></em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Marvel Guidebook Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-marvel-guidebook-collection-books</link>
      <description>The Marvel universe from A-Z</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[With great power comes great responsibility, and with great comics comes great lore. Go beyond the movies, TV, and comics and dive into The Ultimate Marvel Guidebook Collection. This 20 book collection is perfectly curated for new Marvel fans and longtime brand loyalists. Read amazing books like <em>Marvel Year By Year A Visual History New Edition</em>, <em>Marvel Myths and Legends</em>, and <em>Ultimate Marvel</em>—and help support First Book with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering and Management by Pragmatic</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-engineering-and-management-pragmatic-books</link>
      <description>Step up your data engineering game</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become a pro or lead the pros in data engineering and management with our latest bundle from Pragmatic. Learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed inside this 15+ course library. You’ll get expert insights from programs like <em>Machine Learning in Elixir</em>, <em>Practical A/B Testing</em>, <em>Designing Data Governance from the Ground Up</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RuneQuest ENCORE by Chaosium</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/runequest-encore-chaosium-books</link>
      <description>Your gateway to a TTRPG classic</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the legendary and beloved tabletop RPG <em>RuneQuest</em>, where heroes are forged in the fires of myth and magic. This bundle includes everything you need to treat your group to endless adventure in the rich, storied world of Glorantha. The <em>RuneQuest Starter Set</em> will get you up and running, including rulebooks, adventures, pre-generated characters, and more. <em>The Red Book of Magic</em> is an essential sourcebook packed with new rules for magic and a wizard’s library of spells to add to your campaign. <em>The Pegasus Plateau & Other Stories</em> contains 7 adventures that’ll transport your group to some of Glorantha’s most thrilling locales. Pay what you want for all these books and more, and help support Code.org with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quality Comics From Top Shelf</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/quality-comics-from-top-shelf-books</link>
      <description>Top quality comics for all</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Great comics come in a wide variety of styles and flavors—so take a bite from a library of fantastic titles! Dive into our Quality Comics Bundle from Top Shelf and get familiar with iconic stories like <em>The League of Extraordinary Gentlemen Volume III & IV</em>, engaging spinoffs like <em>Nemo: River of Ghosts</em>, and compelling dark tales like <em>From Hell: Master Edition</em>. Get a curated collection of amazing comics and help support the BINC Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Stack Development with Apress</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/full-stack-development-with-apress-books</link>
      <description>Comprehensive full stack development tools</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Our latest bundle offers everything you need for comprehensive web development—from front-end to back-end. Learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed in web application creation with this bundle of elite courses from Apress. Inside this 20+ program library, you’ll get expert insights from <em>Master Vue.js in just 6 Days</em>, <em>Angular For Business</em>, <em>Mastering MYSQL Administration</em>, and much more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Steven Erikson&#39;s Malazan Book of the Fallen ENCORE by TOR Publishing Group</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/steven-eriksons-malazan-book-fallen-encore-tor-publishing-group-books</link>
      <description>Lose yourself in an epic fantasy masterpiece</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the sweeping saga of gods, mages, mortals, and warring nations in <em>New York Times</em>–bestselling author Steven Erikson’s Malazan Book of the Fallen, heralded as one of the most ambitious, complex, and masterful epic fantasy series of all time. This epic ebook bundle features the complete main 10-volume saga (from <em>Gardens of the Moon</em> to the gripping final volume <em>The Crippled God</em>), as well as seven additional titles that further explore the history and conflicts of the Malazan Empire. Journey deep into one of fantasy literature’s most celebrated worlds, and help support Covenant House and Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Kingmaker Bundle from Paizo Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-kingmaker-bundle-from-paizo-inc-books</link>
      <description>Elevate your Pathfinder campaigns </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your party of trusty friends for countless adventures with our latest <em>Pathfinder</em> bundle from Paizo Inc. Enhance your existing <em>Pathfinder</em> collection with new rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources. Highlights from the Pathfinder Kingmaker Bundle include <em>Pathfinder: Kingmaker Enhanced Plus Edition</em> and <em>Pathfinder Kingmaker Companion Guide</em>. Get everything you need to embark on an epic high fantasy journey together, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Cybersecurity Career by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-cybersecurity-career-packt-books</link>
      <description>Jump-start your cybersecurity career</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn the skills and knowledge you need to build the foundation for a new career in cybersecurity—the pros at Packt are giving you the expert insights you need to succeed in a variety of cybersecurity subsectors. Gain insights from courses like <em>Automating Security Detection Engineering</em>, <em>AWS Certified Security</em>, <em>Pentesting Active Directory and Windows-based Infrastructure</em>, and more. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>