<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Apr 2025 20:22:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Hellboy Expanded Universe 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hellboy-expanded-universe-2025-books</link>
      <description>That&#39;s all for you!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive deeper into Mike Mignola’s Hellboy with even more escapades of the Right Hand of Doom. Get 30+ comics and graphic novels exploring the rich, dark, hilarious and action-packed world of the demonic superhero, Hellboy. Read red hot Hellboy titles including <em>Hellboy in Love</em>, <em>Hellboy in Mexico</em>, and Hellboy: 25 Years of Covers</em>. Explore the expansive Hellboy Universe and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Jordan&#39;s The Wheel of Time</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/robert-jordans-wheel-time-books</link>
      <description>Enter the world of The Wheel of Time, a fantasy series like no other</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Our latest bundle includes every volume of the international bestselling The Wheel of Time and connected titles, a groundbreaking epic fantasy series by Robert Jordan and completed by Brandon Sanderson. The Wheel of Time turns and Ages come and pass, leaving memories that become legend. Legend fades to myth, and even myth is long forgotten when the Age that gave it birth returns again. What was, what will be, and what is, may yet fall under the Shadow.<br><br>Since its debut in 1990, The Wheel of Time has captivated millions of readers around the globe with its scope, originality, and compelling characters, and is the basis for the original series on Prime Video. The last six books in series were all instant #1 New York Times bestsellers, and The Eye of the World was named one of America's best-loved novels by PBS's The Great American Read. Robert Jordan's epic saga traces an entire world's struggle to deal with war and destruction while one man prepares to face the embodiment of pure evil.<br><br>Enjoy these amazing titles and help support the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU) with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking and Security Cert Prep by Pearson IT Certification &amp; Exam Cram</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/networking-and-security-cert-prep-pearson-it-certification-exam-cram-books</link>
      <description>In a jam? Time to cram!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t stress the test—to prepare for your networking and security exams with confidence all you need are the right teachers. Our latest exam cram bundle by Pearson is bursting with timely courses designed to help you ace your tests in record time. Soak in the knowledge from lessons like <em>31 Days Before your CCNA Exam</em>, <em>CISSP Cert Guide</em>, and more. Study with efficiency and help support Xperience Studios with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampire Hunter D by Dark Horse Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/vampire-hunter-d-dark-horse-encore-books</link>
      <description>Read the novels that inspired the anime</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the origins of Vampire Hunter D! You may know it from the classic film, the beloved manga, or an upcoming animated series, but the saga started back in the 80s as a series of light novels by author Hideyuki Kikuchi with illustrations by legendary artist Yoshitaka Amano. Together, they tell the story of D, a human-vampire hybrid intent on righting wrongs in a supernatural, post-apocalyptic world governed by the ruling Vampire Nobility class. Read the first 29 volumes of the epic series translated into English by Dark Horse, and help support World Central Kitchen!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Writing Guides by Adams Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/essential-writing-guides-adams-media-books</link>
      <description>Win with elite writing guides</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A gripping script and great gameplay are the winning ingredients to a memorable project—master the written portion with the Essential Writing Guide Bundle by Adams Media. Tackle proper grammar, plot formatting, and other cornerstone skills that define the art of writing and content. Learn from the best with professional quality courses like <em>Only Grammar Book You'll Ever Need</em>, <em>Big Book Of Words You Should Know To Sound Smart</em>, and more. Master the art of the pen and help support Worldreader with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gardening Mastery by Quarto</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/gardening-mastery-quarto-books</link>
      <description>Happiness is a garden away</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Spring is on the horizon, and the perfect way to celebrate is to finally start that home garden project you’ve been talking about. Say hello to the new Gardening Mastery Bundle by Quarto! Get ebooks like <em>Garden Pest Handbook</em>, <em>Containers in the Garden</em>, <em>Terrariums - Gardens Under Glass: Designing, Creating, and Planting Modern Indoor Gardens</em>, and more. Succeed in cultivating your dream garden in any climate today—plus, your purchase helps support the charity of your choice!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedded Intelligence by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/embedded-intelligence-packt-books</link>
      <description>Reflect on technological brilliance</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Expand your automation toolkit with the exciting field of Embedded Intelligence through this bundle of ebooks from Packt. This package features twenty guides and manuals including <em>The FPGA Programming Handbook</em>, <em>Embedded Systems Architecture</em>, <em>Artificial Intelligence for Robotics</em>, plus more. These are the perfect materials regardless of whether you're a software developer looking to learn about embedded programming, or a less experienced programmer on a quest to expand your knowledge on embedded systems. Each purchase also supports Room to Read, who endeavor to create a world free from illiteracy and gender inequality!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The BattleTech RPG Collection by Catalyst Game Labs</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/battletech-rpg-collection-catalyst-game-labs-books</link>
      <description>Become a legend of mechanized mayhem</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Quick—jump in the cockpit and fire up your mech—we’ve got some butt to kick! Feel the rush and excitement of roleplaying in <em>BattleTech</em>’s Aurigan Reach—a broken, futuristic, Earth-like land. It’s time to gather your party for The BattleTech Collection Bundle by Catalyst Game Labs and experience new adventures in awesome robots. This comprehensive bundle offers everything you need to enjoy the BattleTech experience, including lore books and new campaigns. Get <em>BattleTech Universe</em>, <em>BattleTech: MechWarrior: Destiny</em>, and much more—plus, your purchase helps support No Kid Hungry.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Shonen Special by Kodansha</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/spring-shonen-special-kodansha-books</link>
      <description>Modern shonen’s biggest &amp; brightest series </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Say goodbye to winter and welcome the warmer weather with Spring Shonen Special Bundle by Kodansha. The shonen genre is full of action-packed stories, with amazing world building, memorable characters and exciting battles&mdash;including the series found in this bundle. Witness Yoh Asakura&rsquo;s journey challenging adversaries around the world to win the Shaman Tournament and become <em>SHAMAN KING</em>, Shinra Kusakabe and his pyro powered comrades fight demons and shadowy organizations in <em>Fire Force</em>, and follow Yato, a down-on-his-luck god struggling to find worshipers in <em>Noragami</em>. This bundle offers nearly 100 digital volumes, giving you every volume of these outstanding series to the very last one. Act now&mdash;get the Spring Shonen Special Bundle and help support The BINC Foundation.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head First Programming and Patterns by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/head-first-programming-and-patterns-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Try the Head First approach to programming</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive in Head First—learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed in modern programming and patterns with this bundle of courses from O’Reilly. Inside this in-depth library, you’ll get expert insights from courses like <em>Head First JavaScript Programming</em>, <em>Head First C#</em>, <em>Head First Software Architecture</em>, and more. Develop the skills you need to test the waters of this fruitful career field today. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Delta Green RPG, VTT, &amp; Fiction Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/delta-green-rpg-vtt-fiction-collection-books</link>
      <description>Delta Green’s very best</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing and fiction books where horror meets conspiracy. This TTRPG explorer’s kit from the legendary Delta Green Partnership contains campaign resources and more for the dark and mysterious game Delta Green -- from VTT adaptations to <em>The King in Yellow: Annotated<em> to the newest revelation, God's Hunt for the dark and mysterious game—<em>Delta Green</em>. Get everything you need to fend off the unnatural, undead, and misunderstood on an epic journey together. Plus, your purchase helps support Direct Relief!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The World of Dragonlance by Wizards of the Coast</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/world-dragonlance-wizards-coast-books</link>
      <description>Feel the strength of Dragonlance </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Embark on an epic adventure through the land of Krynn with the ultimate <em>Dragonlance</em> Collection from Wizards of the Coast.   Follow the perilous journey to protect the mystical Blue Crystal Staff from an evil dragon goddess in <em>Dragons of Autumn Twilight</em>. Untangle dwarven political tensions, hidden dangers, and long-lost secrets with The Companions in <em>Dragons of the Dwarven Depths</em>. The battle of the gods comes to a dramatic climax in <em>Amber and Ashes</em>. Get 25+ amazing page-turners and help support Room to Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>