<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 16:26:13 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters, Traps, &amp; DM Tricks For DnD &amp; DCC</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/monsters-traps-dm-tricks-for-dnd-dcc-books</link>
      <description>Monsters, traps, tricks, and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Teach an old Dungeon Master new tricks with our most epic DM bundle yet! Surprise your companions and foes with new techniques, traps, and tactics from hot books and guides. Create your own original campaigns, get inspired by <em>How to Write Adventure Modules That Don't Suck</em>, and gain access to a limited-quantity supply of <em>Grimtooth's Trapsylvania</em> hardback books! Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support The Trevor Project with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity and Forensics by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-and-forensics-pearson-books</link>
      <description>The best in cybersecurity &amp; prevention</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master the skills and techniques you need to succeed in protecting your online networks with our latest Humble Tech Book Bundle: Cybersecurity and Forensics! This 15+ ebook library from the experts at Pearson covers a diverse array of platforms and techniques. Learn from hot ebooks like <em>Zero Trust Architecture</em>, <em>Cybersecurity Myths and Misconceptions</em>, <em>Network Security</em>, and more. Pay what you want and help support First Book with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPG Game Master Book Series</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/rpg-game-master-book-series-books</link>
      <description>Teach a Game Master new tricks</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[What makes a great Game Master? Experience, knowledge, resources, and excitement! Become a legendary GM with our all-new RPG Game Master Book Bundle. Elevate your skillset with endless insights from robust ebooks like <em>The Game Master's Book of Random Encounters</em>, <em>The Game Master's Book of Traps, Puzzles and Dungeons</em>, and <em>The Game Master's Book of Astonishing Random Tables</em>. Pay what you want and help support the Breast Cancer Research Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Witcher X Cyberpunk 2025 by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/witcher-x-cyberpunk-2025-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Silver swords and cyber psychos</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Silver swords and cyber psychos. Looking for awesome stories set in two of the most exciting universes around? This bundle of Witcher and Cyberpunk books and comics from Dark Horse has the goods for stone cold monster hunters and chromed-out netrunners alike! The Witcher Volume 1: House of Glass sends Geralt on one of most harrowing adventures yet, replete with human drama and haunting terror in equal measures. Cyberpunk 2077: Your Voice is full of dazzling action and corpo intrigue—the hallmarks of a killer Night City tale. You’ll also get deep looks into these awesome universes with books like The World of Cyberpunk 2077 and The World of the Witcher, and much more! Pay what you want for this action-packed bundle and help support SpecialEffect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning, AI, and Bots by O&#39;Reilly 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/machine-learning-ai-and-bots-oreilly-2025-books</link>
      <description>Master Machine Learning</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills and build your own bots with this comprehensive library from the pros at O’Reilly. Harness the power of machine learning to create digital agents and more with hot courses like <em>Learning LangChain</em>, <em>The Developer's Playbook for Large Language Model Security</em>, <em>Designing Large Language Model Applications</em>, and more. Get elite resources for both novice coders and seasoned pros to grow your career—and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Michael Bendis&#39; Jinxworld Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/brian-michael-bendis-jinxworld-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Bendis’ best indie works</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Want to expand your graphic novel library? Discover the complex characters, worlds, and stories of Brian Michael Bendis in the all-new Jinxworld Bundle, in partnership with Dark Horse Comics. Bendis’s catalog spans more than a quarter century and includes timeless comics and graphic novels, including <em>Jinx</em>, <em>Powers</em>, and <em>Murder Inc</em>. Lose yourself in these unforgettable works and help support Charity: Water with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadlands Reloaded Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/deadlands-reloaded-megabundle-books</link>
      <description>The ultimate Western TTRPG</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your posse for an awesome TTRPG party with <em>Deadlands: Reloaded</em>. Roleplay as a squinty-eyed gunfighter or card-chucking hexslinger in this alternate-history, fantasy-based retelling of the American West before the end of the 19th century. Our Deadlands: Reloaded Megabundle offers countless hours of action-packed adventures, expansions, and more—like <em>Deadlands Reloaded: The Flood</em> and <em>Deadlands Reloaded: Stone and a Hard Place</em>. Pay what you want and help support the American Cancer Society with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Program 2025 by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/learn-to-program-2025-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Unlock your programming superpower!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Start coding with confidence using our latest programming bundle. This 25+ course library will help you master Python, JavaScript, C, C++, SQL, and many other essential languages. Whether you're writing your first line of code or refining your logic, you’ll build real skills with guidance from programming experts featured in <em>Learn Python the Hard Way</em>, <em>Absolute Beginner's Guide to Algorithms</em>, <em>Captain Code</em>, and more. Get outstanding programming resources, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black+Decker Home How-To Guides-Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/blackdecker-home-howto-guides-books-encore-2025</link>
      <description>The ultimate home improvement resource</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Empower yourself with the skills to do what needs doing around the house with this bundle of handy how-to guides from Black+Decker! You’ll get a comprehensive library of detailed instructions covering anything that might come up around the house. Need to lay pipe for a new bathroom? Looking for a step-by-step guide on how to frame a wall? Are you at a loss trying to set up your patios and walkways? You’re covered for all these topics and more. Pay what you want for a lifetime of home improvement confidence and help support It Gets Better with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>