<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Adventure Time by Oni Press ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/adventure-time-oni-press-encore-books</link>
      <description>The Land of Ooo awaits</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Join Finn, Jake, and the rest of your faves from the Land of Ooo on a series of new adventures in this bundle of Adventure Time comics from Oni Press. You’ll get 75 issues of wild quests, magical mishaps, and hilarious hijinks, featuring a rogues gallery of beloved baddies familiar to longtime fans as well as unexpected alliances and plenty of whimsical chaos, as only <em>Adventure Time</em> can provide. Plus, your purchase helps the Hero Initiative and the Book Industry Charitable Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript and TypeScript Mastery by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/javascript-and-typescript-mastery-packt-books</link>
      <description>Flip the script on programming languages</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills before the new year strikes with the JavaScript and TypeScript Mastery Bundle by Packt. Flip the script on what you typically do and learn how to speak standard languages used by computer experts with approachable lessons like <em>Responsive Web Design with HTML5 and CSS</em>, <em>Learn React with TypeScript</em>, and <em>JavaScript from Beginner to Professional</em>. Start a new career in tech or sharpen your existing toolset, and help support Safe In Our World with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shadows, Stars &amp; Screams: Epic Audiobooks &amp; Dramas by Realm</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/shadows-stars-screams-epic-audiobooks-dramas-realm-books</link>
      <description>Epic audiobooks and sensational series</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Embark on an amazing journey this holiday through our latest curated collection -- from Realm and Serial Box -- with their award-winning audiobooks, series, and podcasts. Choose from a wide variety of vibes and genres, from calm and relaxing to high-octane action. Lose hours listening to standout titles like Ellen Kushner’s <em>Swordspoint</em> prequel series, the contemporary fantasy drama, <em>Gods & Lies Season 1</em>, and more! Pay what you want for great audiobooks and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Tchaikovsky&#39;s Epic Fantasy by Macmillan</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/adrian-tchaikovskys-epic-fantasy-pan-macmillan-books</link>
      <description>Fantasy like you’ve never seen before</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’ve been looking for an expansive book series from one of genre fiction’s greatest living authors, we’ve got you covered with this giant bundle of fantasy epics by Arthur C. Clarke Award winner Adrian Tchaikovsky! This 14-ebook bundle from Pan Macmillan includes all ten books in Tchaikovsky’s Shadows of the Apt series, set in an alternate world where human races who share characteristics with insects must unite against the threat of the Wasp Empire. You’ll also get all three books in the Echoes of the Fall trilogy as well as Tchaikovsky’s “flintlock fantasy” standalone novel Guns of the Dawn, so act now and grab this bundle while you can! All purchases at the price of your choosing support Cancer Research UK!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition Holiday Haul Bundle by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-holiday-haul-bundle-paizo-books</link>
      <description>A holiday haul of fantasy adventures</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A vast world of adventure and danger awaits—the only piece missing is your heroism. Gather your party of friends-turned-trusty companions for countless adventures with our latest <em>Pathfinder 2e</em> bundle from Paizo Inc., filled with epic new campaigns like <em>Pathfinder Rage of Elements</em> and <em>Pathfinder Adventure Path: Pactbreaker</em>. Plus, the first 2,500 purchasers receive Pathfinder Elemental Stones! Get everything you need to embark on an epic high-fantasy journey together and help support ComicBooks for Kids.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monstrous Mignolaverse Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/monstrous-mignolaverse-bundle-books</link>
      <description>To Hell and back</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wanted to immerse yourself in the worlds of the legendary Mike Mignola but have no clue where to start, well, we can’t tell you where to start either, but we <em>can</em> give you the option to start anywhere you’d like with this enormous 166 title collection! Check out everything Mignola—the whole Mignolaverse, if you will—from the vampire hunting adventures of Lord Baltimore and Frankenstein’s New World miniseries to the occult detective stories of Joe Golem and, of course, the saga of Hellboy and his B.P.R.D. buddies. This bundle includes iconic titles for the Mignola novices and deep cuts for the Mignola superfans, so grab it while it’s red-hot and support World Central Kitchen’s food relief efforts with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Certification Prep by Microsoft Press and Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/microsoft-certification-prep-microsoft-press-and-pearson</link>
      <description>Become a Certified Microsoft expert</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Not sure where to start with Microsoft certifications? Want to go beyond the basics and prove your skills? This official Exam Ref eBook bundle has everything you need to prep smarter—from Azure fundamentals and data analytics to security, identity, and hybrid infrastructure. Each guide is packed with real‑world scenarios, exam tips, and focused review notes so you can skip the fluff and study what matters. Grab these eBooks while you can, and support the connectivity and sustainable power efforts of Hello World with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking by No Starch</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/hacking-no-starch-books</link>
      <description>Hack for good—never for harm.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Turn your curiosity about computer hacking into a fast-paced, proven, and practical career with our latest collaboration with tech experts at No Starch. Pay what you want for industry-leading instruction from courses like <em>Black Hat Bash</em>, <em>Microcontroller Exploits</em>, and <em>The Art of Cyberwarfare</em>, all designed to help you combat bad hackers and secure your cyberspace. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Comics in the &#39;10s</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/image-comics-in-10s-books</link>
      <description>Bold and expressive comics by Image</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepare for a bundle of can’t-miss digital comics with the attitude cranked all the way up—this powerhouse collection delivers iconic Image Comics stories like <em>SAGA, Vol. 1, Sex Criminals, Vol. 1, Paper Girls, VOL. 1</em>, and more. This 100+ title library doesn’t pull any punches—explore the full spectrum of the femme experience with the women-in-prison sci-fi exploitation riff <em>BITCH PLANET</em>. Pay what you want for some of the hottest comics from Image, and support the BINC Foundation with your purchase.</p> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences.</strong></a><br><br>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate AI: Algorithms and LLMs by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-ai-algorithms-and-llms-manning-books</link>
      <description>Transform Your Tech Future</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive deep into the world of Artificial Intelligence with this essential collection of books, covering everything from core concepts to cutting-edge applications in generative AI, financial modeling, software testing, and more. Whether you're a developer looking to integrate AI into your workflow, a data scientist exploring large language models, or a business professional seeking to understand AI strategy, this bundle is your complete roadmap to succeeding in the age of AI.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>