<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 22:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Linux for Professionals by Apress/Springer</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/linux-for-professionals-apressspringer-books</link>
      <description>Live the Linux lifestyle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Humble Tech Book Bundles got you covered. Level up your Linux skills, learn to bend its unmatched power to your will, and create the most optimized operating systems around using the expertly crafted tools by Apress and Springer. This curated library of courses includes<em>Supercomputers for Linux SysAdmins</em>, <em>CompTIA Linux+ Certification Companion</em>, <em>Using and Administering Linux: Volume 1-2</em>, and more. Pay what you want and help support Room To Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Infinite - Celebration of Kingmaker by Roll20</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-infinite-celebration-kingmaker-roll20-books</link>
      <description>Create your kingdom</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Stolen Lands are yours for the claiming, and all you need is our new bundle offering everything you need to launch your own Pathfinder Infinite Kingmaker Adventure Path campaign! This comprehensive kit includes the full Kingmaker Player’s Guide to get things, ahem, rolling; all the occult knowledge contained within the pages of Frontiers of Magic; the Boosted Bestiary to update your favorite Pathfinder creatures across multiple levels; the expanded Player Core 2, and much more! Gather your comrades and prepare to embark on the adventure of a lifetime, and help support Extra Life charity with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The (Nearly) Complete Nagatoro Collection by Kodansha</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dont-toy-with-me-miss-nagatoro-manga-collection-kodansha-books</link>
      <description>Rom-com shenanigans in manga form </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[High school romance is rough—especially when you’re falling in love with your upperclassman mentor. Follow protagonist Hayase Nagatoro as she learns to drop her bullish facade and embrace her softer side in Don't Toy with Me, Miss Nagatoro. This popular web manga series by author Nanashi embodies everything great about modern manga—dynamic art, relatable characters, and addictive storylines. Pay what you want for this nearly complete collection of fantastic manga, and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Data Analytics &amp; Business Intelligence (BI) Mastery Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/modern-data-analytics-business-intelligence-bi-mastery-bundle-packt-books</link>
      <description>Calling all data driven business specialists </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Keep up in an ever-evolving world of tech and finance with a curated bundle of practical lessons from the experts at Packt. Rooted in modern data analytics and business intelligence, this collection will help you become a Python master in no time with fundamentals-based courses like Python Machine Learning by Example, Causal Inference and Discovery in Python, and Modern Time Series Forecasting with Python. Deepen your understanding—whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional—and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Role Comics Collection by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/critical-role-comics-collection-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Exandria awaits you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the world of Exandria and meet your favorite heroes with the acclaimed Critical Role comics collection from Dark Horse! This bundle expands on the adventures and tragic backstories you already know and love from Critical Role's Vox Machina and Mighty Nein campaigns. The collection includes volumes I - IV of prequel series Vox Machina Origins, two Mighty Nein art books, and character-specific graphic novel origin stories for Mighty Nein members like Caleb Widogast, Jester Lavorre, and Yasha Nydoorin. Every purchase at the price of your choice supports the non-profit Critical Role Foundation!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampirella Sinks Her Teeth Into Comics Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/vampirella-sinks-her-teeth-into-comics-bundle-books</link>
      <description>The strongest and sexiest super vampire</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Minimal clothing—maximum vampiric action. Sink your teeth into the Vampirella Comics Bundle by Dynamite Entertainment! Born the daughter of Lilith, the wife of Adam, Vampirella uses her talents for good against her family’s wishes. Read 40+ comics starring the blood-sucking vixen who lights up the night with her supernatural powers and standout looks, including <em>Vampirella 1969</em>, <em>Vampirella Master Series Vol. 3–8</em>, <em>Vampirella: Seduction of the Innocent Vol. 1–2</em>, and more. Fall in love with the daughter of Lilith, and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Human Side of AI by MIT Press</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/human-side-ai-mit-press-books</link>
      <description>Explore The Human Side of AI</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Deepen your understanding of humanity and artificial intelligence so our relationship with machines doesn’t seem so daunting. This curated collection of award-winning titles from MIT Press asks important questions surrounding modern computer science, machine learning, and technology. Featuring insightful authors and scientists, this bundle has the power to change the way you think about AI. Pay what you want for thought-provoking books like AI & I, The Line, and Bots and Beasts—and help support Sandy Hook Promise with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All Things Raspberry Pi by Raspberry Pi Press</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/all-things-raspberry-pi-raspberry-pi-press-books</link>
      <description>A slice of the pi</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Love computers but wish you knew more about them? Interested in making something yourself one day but don't know where to start? Sounds like you’d better check out our latest bundle of the best educational toolbooks and tech manuals from Raspberry Pi. Learn the ins and outs of coding your favorite retro games and build one of your own with <em>Code the Classics Volume II</em>. Become an expert on the history of everything digital with <em>The Computers that Made the World</em>. Give your tech-savvy kids a head start in computer coding with <em> Unplugged Tots</em>. The 16-book library also includes just-released editions of <em>The Official Raspberry Pi Handbook 2026</em>, <em>Book of Making 2026</em>, and much more! Whether you’re just getting into coding or want to deepen your knowledge about something more specific, this pay-what-you-want bundle has everything you need, and support Raspberry Pi Foundation North America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rick and Morty Everything Comics Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/rick-and-morty-everything-comics-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Wubba lubba dub dub</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’ve ever wanted to dive into the comic universe of beloved animated comedy series Rick and Morty, now is your chance, because we’ve got absolutely everything you need to get started! Jump straight into the official <em>Rick and Morty</em> comic series, beginning with <em>Rick and Morty Vol. 1</em>, or just dip a toe into the <em>Rick and Morty: Pocket Like You Stole It</em> miniseries and the <em>Rick and Morty Presents</em> one-shots. Bend genres with <em>Rick and Morty vs. Cthulhu</em>, <em>Rick and Morty: The Manga</em>, and more! There are more than 150 comics to choose from, so grab this bundle while you can and support BINC with your purchase to pay it forward to bookstores and comic stores everywhere! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll for Initiative with Kieron Gillen by Image Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/roll-for-initiative-with-kieron-gillen-image-comics-books</link>
      <description>Worlds of gods and monsters</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into the imagination of one of comics’ most ambitious and creative minds with our Kieron Gillen bundle! The collection includes complete sets of Gillen’s best series: <em>The Wicked + The Divine</em> gives a contemporary spin to ancient mythology from around the world. <em>Die</em> follows a group of friends attempting to free their comrade from a roleplaying game. Britpop-influenced <em>Phonogram</em> follows magicians who use music to alter reality. And that’s barely the tip of the iceberg! As always, choose what you want to pay for this great bundle, and a portion of the proceeds will go to BINC to help bookstores and comic stores with their emergency needs.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Programming by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/python-programming-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Perfect your skills in Python</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Build websites and software, automate tasks, analyze data, and more using Python—the star of our latest Tech Book Bundle with Pearson. Get building-block courses like Effective Python, Python for Programmers, and Learn Python the Hard Way, 5th Edition from this 10+ title library! Python’s easy-to-use interface is approachable yet powerful enough to tackle a wide range of complex tasks. Everything you need to dip your toes into programming languages is here in one bundle—pay what you want and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete AI &amp; GPT Book Bundle with 7,000 Prompts by Mammoth FLASH SALE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/complete-ai-gpt-book-bundle-with-7000-prompts-mammoth-flash-sale-books</link>
      <description>The blueprints to ask AI anything </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0cosWK5yGs4?si=YSoiFnRG1KnDFkRy" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> <br></br> Optimize your life with a little help from direct and easy-to-execute AI and GPT prompts from the pros at Mammoth Club. Choose from a massive library of topic-specific ebooks like The Complete GPT-5 App Development & Prompt Engineering Cookbook: Master AI with ChatGPT 5 and 1,001 Money-Making Prompts: The Complete AI & ChatGPT Guide to Business, Investing & Passive Income. This fantastic deal won’t last long—pay what you want for 7,000+ prompts within one bundle and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magpie Games Extravaganza</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/magpie-games-extravaganza-books</link>
      <description>The tastiest TTRPGs by Magpie</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather the gang—it’s TTRPG night with the Magpie Games Extravaganza Bundle! Get Magpie’s hottest titles in one collection, like Root: The Roleplaying Game, a 3–6 player adventure centered on woodland creatures fighting for money, justice, and freedom from powers far greater than themselves. Or join Aang in Avatar Legends: The Roleplaying Game, a grand adventure set in the world of water, earth, fire, and air. Try these and other standout modern TTRPGs, like Masks: A New Generation, for a price you can’t beat!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Novels: Go Beyond the Films</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/star-wars-novels-go-beyond-films-books</link>
      <description>Read the untold story….</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[There are a lot of Star Wars movies out there, but the tale told in the films is nowhere close to the whole story. To fill in all the gaps, you’ll want to check out our newest book bundle, featuring all the best Star Wars novels that take place between the movies! Catch up with Anakin and Obi-Wan during the Clone Wars in <em>Star Wars: Brotherhood</em>. Witness the beginnings of the Death Star in <em>Star Wars: Catalyst</em>. See how the galaxy recovers post-Empire in <em>Star Wars: Bloodline</em> and <em>Star Wars: Aftermath</em>, and the looming threat of the Dark Side in <em>Star Wars: Shadow of the Sith</em>. All purchases help support the charity First Book!<br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>