<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 01:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Thundercats &amp; Friends by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/thundercats-friends-dynamite-books</link>
      <description>Sugar, spice, and really nice comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Enjoy your favorite network TV Golden Era cartoon characters like Lion-O and the ThunderCats, Bubbles and The Powerpuff Girls, and more in all-new ways with this enormous 90+ comic bundle from Dynamite Entertainment! Kick off your comics era with The Powerpuff Girls #1—the origin story of everyone’s favorite superhero sisters with attitude—or follow Lion-O, Panthro, and Cheetara as they battle the evil eternal entity Mumm-Ra in ThunderCats #1. Unlock awesome comics and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survive Everything Handbooks by Skyhorse ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/survive-everything-handbooks-skyhorse-books-encore</link>
      <description>Be ready for disaster and everything after</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Foraging. Trapping. Canning. Bushcraft. While this collection from Skyhorse is meant to prepare you to survive any situation, disaster or otherwise, there are skills everyone should know. With titles like <em>Trapper’s Bible</em>,<em>Complete Guide to Edible Wild Plants</em>, <em>Ultimate Book of Everyday Knots</em>, and over three dozen more books, you won’t just learn to survive in whatever situation you find yourself in—you’ll thrive. Plus, your purchase goes on to support the charity of your choice!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math and Physics for Dummies 2025 Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/math-and-physics-for-dummies-books-2025-encore</link>
      <description>Math, physics &amp; more… For Dummies</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Need some help wrapping your head around complex subjects in math and physics? This bundle of books in the popular <em>For Dummies</em> series is here to help with fun and approachable lessons across a number of tricky topics! <em>Statistics All-in-One For Dummies</em> will teach you how to interpret graphs, determine probability, critique data and more! Bone up on the fundamentals and move onto the advanced stuff like graphing functions and approximating area with <em>Calculus For Dummies</em>. <em>Thermodynamics For Dummies</em> will help you wrap your head around complex concepts like entropy and the laws of thermodynamics in an easily digestible and approachable manner. Pay what you want for all these and more—a total of 16 books—and help support buildOn with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Software Architecture by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/software-architecture-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Discover how everything fits together</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A software system is only as good as its architecture—all of the building blocks that make the system work—allows it to function. In order to build better software, you’ll need to understand the fundamentals of how everything fits together, and that’s where this handy ebook bundle of textbooks from Pearson comes in. Learn the importance of coupling in everyday software architecture, how to make your software shift and flow depending on the needs of the system, how to use the fundamentals of software architecture to build your software more efficiently, and much more in this 19-book library. Get a foothold on the basics so that your future projects are foolproof. Every purchase at the price of your choice supports Code.org, ensuring every student has access to computer science.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Language, Culture, and Travel by Stone Bridge Press Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/japanese-language-culture-and-travel-stone-bridge-press-books-encore</link>
      <description>Japanese language, culture, and travel</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepping for a trip to Japan? Or are you simply interested in learning the ins and outs of this beautiful country? This bundle of books will help you brush up on your language skills, appreciate Japan’s culture, and plan an itinerary for your future journeys. <em>Kanji Pict-o-Graphix</em> will help you wrap your head around the hardest parts of the Japanese written language with helpful mnenomic techniques. Full of useful guides and photos, <em>Tokyo Stroll: A Guide to City Sidetracks and Easy Explorations</em> encourages unstructured exploration of this exciting city. <em>Just Enough</em> provides valuable insights on living fully and sustainably, inspired by lessons learned in Japan’s past. Pay what you want for all these books and more and help support the Book Industry Charitable Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Georges Simenon&#39;s Inspector Maigret Series by Picador</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/georges-simenons-inspector-maigret-series-picador-books</link>
      <description>A new look at France’s great detective</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Earlier this year, readers of detective fiction got some great news: Belgian author Georges Simenon’s iconic Inspector Maigret novels are getting a brand-new reissue from Picador. We have some equally great news: a bundle of all 18 of Simenon’s Maigret novels that have been republished thus far, to read along with PBS’s currently running Maigret series! Start at the very beginning of Maigret’s adventures with Pietr the Latvian, a manhunt for a notorious gangster who happens to have a number of mysterious doubles. Board a yacht and solve a murder with The Carter of “La Providence”. That’s only the tip of the Maigret iceberg, so grab this timeless library while you can, and support Come Back Alive with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Last Call for Lankhmar by Goodman Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/last-call-for-lankhmar-goodman-games-books</link>
      <description>Welcome to Lankhmar</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your party and take a trip to a city full of adventure and surprise with this bundle of Lankhmar tabletop RPG resources from Dungeon Crawl Classics! Get the entire Lankhmar saga and 15 distinct adventures set within the legendary city, including fan favorites like “The Greatest Thieves in Lankhmar,” “Gang Lords of Lankhmar,” “Blasphemy and Larceny in Lankhmar,” and more! Bring your story to life with the Lankhmar Printed Boxed Set & Adventure Bundle, which features printed maps, the Compendium of Secret Knowledge, and more new material with all the twists and turns needed to satisfy newcomers and veteran players alike. Grab everything you need for your next adventure at the price of your choice, and all purchases support the No Kid Hungry campaign from nonprofit Share Our Strength.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Engineering &amp; Science by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-engineering-science-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>The ins and outs of data science</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[With the world becoming more and more digitized, knowing how to use data is the way of the future. This bundle of valuable resources from O’Reilly is a Rosetta stone for aspiring data scientists everywhere, chock-full of information and tools to help you learn the skills you need to become a data engineer. This 20-book library will teach you how to integrate data science into software coding, use data science to design data-driven financial products, use streaming databases to process continuous inputs of data in real time, and more! Whether you’re new to the world of data science or an old hand at building data software of all kinds, this bundle will deepen your knowledge no matter your skill set. You choose what you pay, and all purchases support the federal aid organization Code for America!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Sci-Fi Classics: Charles Soule, Joseph Fink, Hugh Howey, and Neal Stephenson by HarperCollins</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/modern-scifi-classics-charles-soule-joseph-fink-hugh-howey-and-neal-stephenson-harpercollins-books</link>
      <description>Collect science fiction classics </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve teamed up with HarperCollins Publishers to make cool fall days a little warmer with the hottest science fiction ebooks. This curated collection is packed with certified modern classics—<em>Seveneves</em>, <em>Welcome to Night Vale</em>, <em>The Oracle Year</em>, and more! Think deeply, laugh, and cry at novels inspired by hit podcasts, stories that explore the nature of Homo sapiens, and tales of suddenly inheriting power. Elevate your home library and help support Room to Read with your purchase!<br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Comics in the &#39;90s</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/image-comics-in-90s-books</link>
      <description>Image Comics coming in hot</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Collect the hottest titles from Image Comics with a mix of retro and modern hits! This 30+ issue collection has it all—imagine life in a hero-filled world from the perspective of an everyday mortal in the anthology series <em>Astro City</em>, return from hell with demonic powers to extract justice and save your wife in <em>SPAWN</em>, and so much more. Pay what you want to bolster your personal comic collection and help support The BINC Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux for Professionals by Apress/Springer</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/linux-for-professionals-apressspringer-books</link>
      <description>Live the Linux lifestyle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Humble Tech Book Bundles got you covered. Level up your Linux skills, learn to bend its unmatched power to your will, and create the most optimized operating systems around using the expertly crafted tools by Apress and Springer. This curated library of courses includes<em>Supercomputers for Linux SysAdmins</em>, <em>CompTIA Linux+ Certification Companion</em>, <em>Using and Administering Linux: Volume 1-2</em>, and more. Pay what you want and help support Room To Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Infinite - Celebration of Kingmaker by Roll20</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-infinite-celebration-kingmaker-roll20-books</link>
      <description>Create your kingdom</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Stolen Lands are yours for the claiming, and all you need is our new bundle offering everything you need to launch your own Pathfinder Infinite Kingmaker Adventure Path campaign! This comprehensive kit includes the full Kingmaker Player’s Guide to get things, ahem, rolling; all the occult knowledge contained within the pages of Frontiers of Magic; the Boosted Bestiary to update your favorite Pathfinder creatures across multiple levels; the expanded Player Core 2, and much more! Gather your comrades and prepare to embark on the adventure of a lifetime, and help support Extra Life charity with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The (Nearly) Complete Nagatoro Collection by Kodansha</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dont-toy-with-me-miss-nagatoro-manga-collection-kodansha-books</link>
      <description>Rom-com shenanigans in manga form </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[High school romance is rough—especially when you’re falling in love with your upperclassman mentor. Follow protagonist Hayase Nagatoro as she learns to drop her bullish facade and embrace her softer side in Don't Toy with Me, Miss Nagatoro. This popular web manga series by author Nanashi embodies everything great about modern manga—dynamic art, relatable characters, and addictive storylines. Pay what you want for this nearly complete collection of fantastic manga, and help support the Comic Book Legal Defense Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Modern Data Analytics &amp; Business Intelligence (BI) Mastery Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/modern-data-analytics-business-intelligence-bi-mastery-bundle-packt-books</link>
      <description>Calling all data driven business specialists </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Keep up in an ever-evolving world of tech and finance with a curated bundle of practical lessons from the experts at Packt. Rooted in modern data analytics and business intelligence, this collection will help you become a Python master in no time with fundamentals-based courses like Python Machine Learning by Example, Causal Inference and Discovery in Python, and Modern Time Series Forecasting with Python. Deepen your understanding—whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional—and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critical Role Comics Collection by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/critical-role-comics-collection-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Exandria awaits you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the world of Exandria and meet your favorite heroes with the acclaimed Critical Role comics collection from Dark Horse! This bundle expands on the adventures and tragic backstories you already know and love from Critical Role's Vox Machina and Mighty Nein campaigns. The collection includes volumes I - IV of prequel series Vox Machina Origins, two Mighty Nein art books, and character-specific graphic novel origin stories for Mighty Nein members like Caleb Widogast, Jester Lavorre, and Yasha Nydoorin. Every purchase at the price of your choice supports the non-profit Critical Role Foundation!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>