<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 16:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Guide to AI APIs by Mammoth</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-guide-to-ai-apis-mammoth-books</link>
      <description>Accelerate your advancement in AI today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Want to learn new tech skills? Make your New Year’s resolution a fresh goal that’ll revolutionize your life with the Ultimate Guide to AI APIs Bundle by Mammoth Club. Get serious about the next frontier of technology and make AI a focal point of your 2026 development plan with hot courses like <em>The Self-Hosted AI Handbook – Guidebook to Building Local LLMs</em> and <em>AI-Powered Career Mastery – Transform Your Personal Brand and Job Search</em>. Pay what you want for industry-leading instruction and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lone Wolf &amp; Cub and Other Manga Classics by Koike ENCORE by Dark Horse</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/lone-wolf-cub-and-more-koike-encore-dark-horse-books</link>
      <description>Formative manga curated for you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover the sprawling, epic story of a swordsman and his son in our popular <em>Lone Wolf and Cub</em> bundle from Dark Horse Comics—back again for a limited time! This formative 1970s’ manga series, written by the brilliant Kazuo Koike and featuring the breathtaking visuals of Goseki Kojima, is widely regarded as one of the most influential works of graphic fiction ever created, inspiring countless storytellers, artists, and filmmakers across Japan and beyond. Read these and other classic Koike series like <em>Crying Freeman</em> and <em>Lady Snowblood</em>, and help support the Hero Initiative too.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bob&#39;s Dungeon Crawl Classics RPG Megabundle Presented by Bob World Builder</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/bobs-dungeon-crawl-classics-rpg-megabundle-presented-bob-world-builder-books</link>
      <description>Instantly upgrade your campaigns</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Humble is bringing the heat to start off 2026 with Bob’s Big Dungeon Crawl Classics RPG Megabundle from tabletop RPG content creator Bob World Builder! Add nearly 100 unique assets, campaigns, and more to your home collection, including the latest <em>DCC RPG Core Rulebook</em>, the <em>DCC Dying Earth Boxed Set</em>, the epic adventure of <em>Dungeon Crawl Classics #102: Dweller Between the Worlds</em>, and beyond. Plus, the first 7,500 purchasers are eligible to receive a printed pack of four DCC floppy adventures! Get this legendary collection before it’s gone and help support Child’s Play when you do.<br><br><strong><span style="color: #ef9741;">Codes are redeemable through the DriveThruRPG website.</span></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Year, Fiercely You! by Berret-Koehler</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/new-year-fiercely-you-berretkoehler-books</link>
      <description>New Year’s resolutions made simple…and fun!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The cusp of a new year is a time to reflect and a time to plan. Who do you want to be in 2026? Do you want to hit the gym more? Improve your finances? Make new friends? Whatever your goals, real change starts from the inside out, and this bundle of self improvement ebooks from Berret-Koehler has everything you need to learn how to better yourself while still being you! <em>Fiercely You: Be Fabulous and Confident While Thinking Like a Drag Queen</em> uses the trade secrets of drag culture to teach confidence and self-worth. <em>Eat That Frog! 21 Great Ways to Stop Procrastinating</em> will teach you mental tricks to be more productive. <em>Flux: 8 Superpowers for Thriving in Constant Change</em> will help you master the art of going with the flow, no matter where it takes you. Becoming the best version of yourself is easy with this bundle, and every purchase supports Worldreader’s efforts to keep kids reading!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adventure Time by Oni Press ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/adventure-time-oni-press-encore-books</link>
      <description>The Land of Ooo awaits</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Join Finn, Jake, and the rest of your faves from the Land of Ooo on a series of new adventures in this bundle of Adventure Time comics from Oni Press. You’ll get 75 issues of wild quests, magical mishaps, and hilarious hijinks, featuring a rogues gallery of beloved baddies familiar to longtime fans as well as unexpected alliances and plenty of whimsical chaos, as only <em>Adventure Time</em> can provide. Plus, your purchase helps the Hero Initiative and the Book Industry Charitable Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript and TypeScript Mastery by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/javascript-and-typescript-mastery-packt-books</link>
      <description>Flip the script on programming languages</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills before the new year strikes with the JavaScript and TypeScript Mastery Bundle by Packt. Flip the script on what you typically do and learn how to speak standard languages used by computer experts with approachable lessons like <em>Responsive Web Design with HTML5 and CSS</em>, <em>Learn React with TypeScript</em>, and <em>JavaScript from Beginner to Professional</em>. Start a new career in tech or sharpen your existing toolset, and help support Safe In Our World with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adrian Tchaikovsky&#39;s Epic Fantasy by Macmillan</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/adrian-tchaikovskys-epic-fantasy-pan-macmillan-books</link>
      <description>Fantasy like you’ve never seen before</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’ve been looking for an expansive book series from one of genre fiction’s greatest living authors, we’ve got you covered with this giant bundle of fantasy epics by Arthur C. Clarke Award winner Adrian Tchaikovsky! This 14-ebook bundle from Pan Macmillan includes all ten books in Tchaikovsky’s Shadows of the Apt series, set in an alternate world where human races who share characteristics with insects must unite against the threat of the Wasp Empire. You’ll also get all three books in the Echoes of the Fall trilogy as well as Tchaikovsky’s “flintlock fantasy” standalone novel Guns of the Dawn, so act now and grab this bundle while you can! All purchases at the price of your choosing support Cancer Research UK!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>