<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 13:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning, AI, and Bots by O&#39;Reilly 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/machine-learning-ai-and-bots-oreilly-2025-books</link>
      <description>Master Machine Learning</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills and build your own bots with this comprehensive library from the pros at O’Reilly. Harness the power of machine learning to create digital agents and more with hot courses like <em>Learning LangChain</em>, <em>The Developer's Playbook for Large Language Model Security</em>, <em>Designing Large Language Model Applications</em>, and more. Get elite resources for both novice coders and seasoned pros to grow your career—and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Michael Bendis&#39; Jinxworld Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/brian-michael-bendis-jinxworld-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Bendis’ best indie works</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Want to expand your graphic novel library? Discover the complex characters, worlds, and stories of Brian Michael Bendis in the all-new Jinxworld Bundle, in partnership with Dark Horse Comics. Bendis’s catalog spans more than a quarter century and includes timeless comics and graphic novels, including <em>Jinx</em>, <em>Powers</em>, and <em>Murder Inc</em>. Lose yourself in these unforgettable works and help support Charity: Water with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deadlands Reloaded Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/deadlands-reloaded-megabundle-books</link>
      <description>The ultimate Western TTRPG</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your posse for an awesome TTRPG party with <em>Deadlands: Reloaded</em>. Roleplay as a squinty-eyed gunfighter or card-chucking hexslinger in this alternate-history, fantasy-based retelling of the American West before the end of the 19th century. Our Deadlands: Reloaded Megabundle offers countless hours of action-packed adventures, expansions, and more—like <em>Deadlands Reloaded: The Flood</em> and <em>Deadlands Reloaded: Stone and a Hard Place</em>. Pay what you want and help support the American Cancer Society with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Program 2025 by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/learn-to-program-2025-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Unlock your programming superpower!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Start coding with confidence using our latest programming bundle. This 25+ course library will help you master Python, JavaScript, C, C++, SQL, and many other essential languages. Whether you're writing your first line of code or refining your logic, you’ll build real skills with guidance from programming experts featured in <em>Learn Python the Hard Way</em>, <em>Absolute Beginner's Guide to Algorithms</em>, <em>Captain Code</em>, and more. Get outstanding programming resources, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Black+Decker Home How-To Guides-Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/blackdecker-home-howto-guides-books-encore-2025</link>
      <description>The ultimate home improvement resource</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Empower yourself with the skills to do what needs doing around the house with this bundle of handy how-to guides from Black+Decker! You’ll get a comprehensive library of detailed instructions covering anything that might come up around the house. Need to lay pipe for a new bathroom? Looking for a step-by-step guide on how to frame a wall? Are you at a loss trying to set up your patios and walkways? You’re covered for all these topics and more. Pay what you want for a lifetime of home improvement confidence and help support It Gets Better with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warren Ellis by Image Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/warren-ellis-image-comics-books</link>
      <description>Introducing an award-winning graphic novelist</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in the renowned stories of Image Comics with our latest Humble Comics Bundle featuring 10+ graphic novels showcasing the award-winning works of Warren Ellis. This collection includes gripping noir like <em>Fell</em>, slow-burning sci-fi like <em>Trees</em>, and suspenseful horror like <em>Injection</em>. Discover worlds beyond the familiar, add iconic graphic novels to your personal collection, and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Visualization by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/data-visualization-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Imagine limitless possibilities in data visualization </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become your office’s Microsoft Suite whiz—or simply sharpen your skills for fun—with the all-new Data Visualization Bundle from O’Reilly. Improve your productivity, increase your work speed, and collaborate more effectively with your team using the valuable tools in our latest bundle. Sit down and learn from professional-quality courses like <em>Data Visualization with Microsoft Power BI</em>, <em>Excel Cookbook</em>, <em>ColorWise</em>, and more. Plus, your purchase helps support Code for America!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Math and Physics for Dummies Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/math-and-physics-for-dummies-books-encore</link>
      <description>Math, physics &amp; more… For Dummies</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Need some help wrapping your head around complex subjects in math and physics? This bundle of books in the popular <em>For Dummies</em> series is here to help with fun and approachable lessons across a number of tricky topics! <em>Statistics All-in-One For Dummies</em> will teach you how to interpret graphs, determine probability, critique data and more! Bone up on the fundamentals and move onto the advanced stuff like graphing functions and approximating area with <em>Calculus For Dummies</em>. <em>Thermodynamics For Dummies</em> will help you wrap your head around complex concepts like entropy and the laws of thermodynamics in an easily digestible and approachable manner. Pay what you want for all these and more—a total of 16 books—and help support buildOn with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bushcraft &amp; Homestead Handbook Series by Adams Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/bushcraft-homestead-handbook-series-adams-media-books</link>
      <description>The skills to keep you alive</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t just survive in the wild—thrive. The Bushcraft & Homestead Handbook Bundle by Adams Media is our newest collection of nature books designed to teach you valuable life and survival skills. Get the latest and most useful bushcraft ebooks around including <em>Bushcraft Essentials Field Guide</em>, <em>Disaster Survival 101</em>, <em>Bushcraft Field Guide to Trapping, Gathering, and Cooking in the Wild</em>, and many more. Conquer the outdoors, develop a new sense of confidence, and help support World Reader with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vampirella XOXO by Dynamite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/vampirella-xoxo-dynamite-encore-books</link>
      <description>A bloody good time</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Uncover a macabre library featuring one of horror’s most enduring comic-book heroines in our latest bundle from Dynamite! Unearth classic Vampirella tales and discover modern interpretations in volumes like <em>Vampirella: Hollywood Horror</em> and the <em>Vampirella Masters Series</em>, featuring stories from some of comics’ most celebrated writers including Grant Morrison, Mark Millar, Kate Leth, and more. Plus, your purchase helps support NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>C# and .NET Mega Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/c-and-net-mega-bundle-packt-books</link>
      <description>The programmer &amp; developer dream bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Transform your .NET development career with the C# & .NET Mega Bundle, featuring 20+ cutting‑edge titles by industry‑leading authors like Mark J. Price, Gabriel Baptista, and Jimmy Engström. You'll gain access to bestselling books such as "C# 13 and .NET 9 – Modern Cross-Platform Development Fundamentals," "Software Architecture with C# 12 and .NET 8," and "Web Development with Blazor," all designed to guide you from core C# fundamentals through .NET architecture, cross‑platform development, and modern API design. Whether you're a newcomer eager to learn the basics or a seasoned architect building enterprise‑scale solutions, this bundle delivers clear, step‑by‑step guidance at every level—plus, a portion of every purchase supports Save the Children. Grab your ultimate roadmap before the deal ends!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JavaScript, Scripting, and Web Development by Pragmatic</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/javascript-scripting-and-web-development-pragmatic-books</link>
      <description>A pot of JavaScript courses &amp; more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pour yourself a hot cup of JavaScript and open up our latest Humble Tech Book Bundle—it’s time to improve your web development and scripting skills. Unlock the latest coding techniques with this library of tech courses highlighted by <em>Clojure Brain Teasers</em>, <em>Serverless Apps on Cloudflare</em>, and <em>Test-Driven React, Second Edition</em>. Get elite resources for novice coders and seasoned pros alike, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Second Edition Asian Fantasy Bundle by Paizo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-second-edition-asian-fantasy-bundle-paizo-books</link>
      <description>Become the hero of Golarion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A world of adventure & magic awaits, and the only thing missing is your hero’s courage. Gather your party of trusty companions for epic adventures with our latest <em>Pathfinder</em> bundle from Paizo Inc. The new Pathfinder Second Edition Asian Fantasy Bundle contains countless hours of new campaigns and guides like <em>Pathfinder Adventure Path: Fists of the Ruby Phoenix</em> and <em>Pathfinder Lost Omens: Tian Xia Character Guide</em>. Get everything you need to embark on an epic high fantasy journey together, and help support Stop AAPI Hate with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amigurumi, Crochet, and More by Open Road Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/amigurumi-crochet-and-more-open-road-media-books</link>
      <description>Yearn for yarn</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take a step away from the digital world and relax with a cozy new hobby—start your crochet and crafting journey today with the all-new Amigurumi, Crochet, and More Bundle by Open Road Media! Get awesome ebooks jam-packed with the cutest critters and more like <em>Crochet Zodiac Dolls</em>, <em>Funny Amigurumi</em>, <em>Little Happy Circus</em>, and <em>Crochet Animal Slippers</em>. Wear, display, or cuddle with the cutest pals around—plus—your purchase helps support No Kid Hungry!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>