<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 22:08:41 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Unofficial Harry Potter Reference Library Presented by MuggleNet</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/unofficial-harry-potter-reference-library-presented-mugglenet-books</link>
      <description>Read enchanting Potterverse ebooks</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Love a certain Boy Who Lived? Become spellbound with awesome Potterverse ebooks designed to explore the far reaches of the Wizarding World. This unofficial collection of iconography, history, and spells is presented by MuggleNet, the #1 Wizarding World resource since 1999! This magical collaboration includes <em>The Unofficial Harry Potter Hogwarts Handbook: MuggleNet's Complete Guide to the Most Famous School for Wizards and Witches</em> and <em>The Ultimate Wizarding World History of Magic: A comprehensive chronicle of the Harry Potter universe through the ages</em>. Pay what you want and help support The Trevor Project with your purchase! <br><br><strong><em>The Trevor Project was not involved in the selection of the content in this promotion and the views, opinions, and ideas expressed in the books are not endorsed by, and do not reflect or represent the views and opinions of The Trevor Project.</em></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dynamite 20th Anniversary 20,000-Page Mega Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/dynamite-20th-anniversary-20000page-mega-bundle-books-encore</link>
      <description>Explosive action, unforgettable heroes</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[This unbelievably massive bundle of comics from Dynamite Entertainment is bursting with amazing stories from some of the most iconic, pulp-infused series out there! Get dozens of volumes— thousands of pages in all!—including fan favorites like <em>Red Sonja</em>, <em>Project Superpowers</em>, <em>Army of Darkness</em>, <em>Vampirella</em>, and many more. Whether your tastes run to gritty sword and sorcery, thrilling horror-tinged tales, or anything in between, this mammoth library will keep you riveted. Pay what you want for over $1,600 worth of comics and help support The Hero Initiative with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Frightening and Fantastic Worlds of James Tynion IV</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/frightening-and-fantastic-worlds-james-tynion-iv-books</link>
      <description>The most frightening and fantastic graphic novels</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take a walk off the beaten literary path and explore the eerie, frightening worlds of James Tynion IV. Our latest comics bundle offers atmospheric and unique ebooks that will surely spice up your summer reading—dive into acclaimed series like <em>The Nice House on the Lake </em>, <em>Something is Killing the Children</em>, <em>The Oddly Pedestrian Life of Christopher Chaos</em>, and more. Don’t be scared—explore the frightening and fantastic worlds of James Tynion IV and help support The BINC Foundation with your purchase!<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>The Nice House on the Lake Vol. 1 and 2 will be avliable to redeem in August 2025.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serious Web Development with React, JavaScript, and modern APIs by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/serious-web-development-with-react-javascript-and-modern-apis-manning-books</link>
      <description>Get serious about web dev</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bear down on your fields of expertise with these guides from Manning. Learn everything you need to know about React, JavaScript, and more modern APIs. Through a mix of how-to guides, and expert advice, you’ll learn key concepts and fundamentals, explore design patterns and best practices, and get a handle on a range of applications and scenarios. Plus, your purchase helps support Girls Who Code! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Trek Comics Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/star-trek-comics-megabundle-books</link>
      <description>Space: The final frontier—of comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Captain the Starship Enterprise from the comfort of your own home with the Star Trek Comics Megabundle! Since 1966, <em>Star Trek</em> has inspired generations with bold, scifi-defining stories told across TV, film, games—and comics. Now, explore nearly 100 titles in this epic library, including <em>Star Trek: Strange New Worlds—The Illyrian Enigma</em>, <em>Star Trek: Defiant, Vol. 1</em>, <em>Star Trek, Vol. 1: Godshock</em>, and many more. Pay what you want for stellar comics and help support The Comic Book Legal Defense Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return of the Leading Ladies by Image Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/return-leading-ladies-image-comics-books</link>
      <description>An electric lady-land of comics </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve teamed up with Image Comics for the Return of the Leading Ladies Bundle—a powerhouse collection of femme-led stories like <em>It’s Lonely at the Centre of the Earth</em>, <em>Paper Girls Vols. 1–6</em>, <em>Saga Vols. 1–10</em>, and more. This 30+ title library doesn’t pander—it celebrates the full spectrum of the femme experience without drowning it in pink. Pay what you want for these standout comics from Image and support BINC with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Pentesting &amp; Hacking Toolkit by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pentesting-hacking-toolkit-packt-books</link>
      <description>Build real-world hacking skills and stay ahead of cyber threats</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master the art of offensive security with The Pentesting & Hacking Toolkit. This curated bundle features hands-on guides and expert resources for ethical hackers, red teamers, and aspiring pentesters. Covering everything from vulnerability discovery to exploitation and post-exploitation techniques, these books provide practical skills to identify and fix security gaps before attackers do. Perfect for all skill levels aiming to level up in cybersecurity.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get Good with Money</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/get-good-with-money-books</link>
      <description>Level up your financial literacy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Stop wasting your money—start mastering it. Learn the financial skills you need to succeed with the all-new Get Good With Money Bundle. Shift your money mindset with top ebooks like <em>Money Hacks Handbook</em>, <em>Prepper's Financial Guide</em>, <em>Think Like a Self-Made Millionaire</em>, and more. You won’t get rich overnight, but you’ll gain the tools to flip your financial script. Pay what you want to level up your financial literacy and help support Child’s Play Charity!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fandom and Pop Culture Cookbooks</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/fandom-and-pop-culture-cookbooks-books</link>
      <description>From the big screen to your kitchen table</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn how to cook a wide variety of foods from your favorite shows, movies, games, and more with the all-new Pop Culture and Fandom Cookbook Bundle! Take your meals from block to plate with the <em>Minecrafter's Cookbook</em>. Craft food even a zombie would eat with the <em>The Walking Dead: The Official Cookbook and Survival Guide</em>. And ewww, David—you got the <em>Tastes Like Schitt: The Unofficial Schitt's Creek Cookbook</em>? Pay what you want for the most fun cookbook collection around and help support The Global FoodBanking Network with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roll Big or Go Home RPG Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/roll-big-or-go-home-rpg-megabundle-books</link>
      <description>Roll big or go home!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for the ultimate TTRPG adventure with the Roll Big or Go Home RPG Megabundle. This legendary 50+ title bundle is jam-packed with rulebooks, auxiliary resources, soundtracks, and more for you to enjoy. Help Aang bring elemental balance to the world in Magpie Games’ <em>Avatar Legends: The Roleplaying Game</em>, use your best chrome to smoke Corpos in R. Talsorian Games’ <em>Cyberpunk RED</em>, and roleplay as a robot in disguise in Renegade Game Studios’ <em>Transformers Roleplaying Game</em>. Play the best games from the best publishers within our biggest TTRPG bundle ever! Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Extra Life.<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through DriveThruRPG.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>