<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 20:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Witcher Tabletop RPG by R. Talsorian Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/witcher-tabletop-rpg-r-talsorian-games-books</link>
      <description>Spare a coin for The Witcher TTRPG</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Evil is evil—and great games are great games. Pay what you want to explore The Continent like never before. Will you fight with strength and valor like Geralt of Rivia? Or forge your own path as an elf, dwarf, gnome, werebbubb, or vran, and set off on unknown adventures with your party. Get the The Witcher Tabletop RPG core rulebook, the <em>The Witcher: Tome of Chaos</em> campaign, and more for a price you choose. Spare a coin and help support the Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase. <br><br><a style="color: #EF9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through: DriveThruRPG</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comfort Crochet, Amigurumi, and Knitting by Open Road Media</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/comfort-crochet-amigurumi-and-knitting-open-road-media-books</link>
      <description>Create cute friends from home</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Beat the heat and stay cool inside with the all-new Comfort Crochet, Amigurumi, and Knitting. Try new techniques and fall in love with Amigurumi—the Japanese art of cute crocheting small yarn creations. Unleash your creativity using the very best craft ebooks from Open Road Media like <em>Granny Square Flower Garden</em>, <em>Beyond the Square: Crochet Motifs</em>, <em>100 Micro Crochet Motifs</em>, and <em>200 Crochet Flowers, Embellishments & Trims</em>. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the Breast Cancer Research Foundation. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate C++ Developer Masterclass by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ultimate-c-developer-masterclass-packt-books</link>
      <description>Get smart in C++</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master the ultimate high-performance, general-purpose programming language with our C++ lessons bundle from the experts at Packt. C++ supports multiple programming paradigms—including procedural, object-oriented, and generic programming—making it the perfect starting point for your journey as a developer. Learn from top-rated courses like <em>C++ Memory Management</em>, <em>C++ in Embedded Systems</em>, <em>Asynchronous Programming with C++</em>, and more. Elevate your C++ skills and help support The Global FoodBanking Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Millarworld Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/millarworld-collection-books</link>
      <description>Mark Millar’s world of amazing comics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lose yourself in comic book legend Mark Millar’s exceptional catalog with our latest Humble Book Bundle: The Millarworld Collection. Headlined by the acclaimed <em>The Magic Order</em> series—following five secret wizard families protecting the world from dark forces—this bundle delivers hours of thrilling, high-stakes storytelling. Other standout titles include <em>Nemesis: Reloaded</em> and the <em>Wanted & Big Game Library Edition</em>. Pay what you want for these incredible Mark Millar comics and help support The Hero Initiative with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Award-Winning &amp; Nominated Tabletop RPGs presented by the ENNIE Awards</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/awardwinning-nominated-tabletop-rpgs-presented-ennie-awards-books</link>
      <description>Celebrate the ENNIE Awards with hot TTRPGs</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate the 2025 ENNIE Awards with a bundle of award-winning and nominated tabletop RPGs! We’ve teamed up with industry-leading publishers including Renegade Games, Free League, and Green Ronin to curate a library of awesome mainline campaigns and auxiliary materials. Play the very best games on the market like <em>Vampire: The Masquerade Auld Sanguine</em>, <em>Call of Cthulhu</em>, <em>The Fall of Delta Green</em>, <em>Dungeon Crawl Classics</em>, and more. Dip a toe or two into new TTRPGs and add the coolest titles to your games collection—pay what you want and help support Extra Life with your purchase!<br><br><a style="color: #EF9741;"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through two partners: some on DriveThruRPG, and some with Paizo.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security by Apress</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/security-apress-books</link>
      <description>Start securing your systems</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Let's be realistic—fraud isn’t slowing down. Start protecting your online systems in no time with the latest Humble Tech Book Bundle from the experts at Apress. This comprehensive library of cybersecurity courses is designed to streamline your security studies and save you money—with standout lessons like <em>The Business of Hacking</em>, <em>Firewalls Don't Stop Dragons</em>, and <em>Privacy in the Age of Innovation</em>. Learn to identify a phishing attack, fraudster, or security breach with ease and help support Worldreader with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Everything Works by DK</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/how-everything-works-dk-books</link>
      <description>The why behind your favorite topics</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Did you know it took Picasso 12 years to complete the Mona Lisa’s lips? Spoiler: It wasn't Picasso, it was Leonardo da Vinci! Uncover the <em>why</em> behind your favorite topics with the all-new How Everything Works Bundle by DK. Fill your summer reading list with a visually informative library that includes titles like <em>How Economics Works</em>, <em>How Art Works</em>, <em>How Space Works</em>, and <em>How Money Works</em>. Pay what you want to unlock a wealth of knowledge and help support First Book with your purchase! <br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The IGN SDCC Massive Comics Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/ign-sdcc-massive-comics-bundle-books</link>
      <description>Enjoy SDCC fun from home</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The intersection of video games and comics is a lively one with a rich history of epic partnership—celebrate IGN’s coverage of San Diego Comic-Con with a curated library of great comics and graphic novels!! Discover must-read titles like <em>Godzilla Half Century War</em>, <em>Lost Marvels No. 1: Tower of Shadows</em>, <em>Black Hammer Volume 1: Secret Origins</em>. Feel the excitement of SDCC from the comfort of your own home and help support The BINC Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tachyon 30th Anniversary: Smart Speculative Fiction for Everyone</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/tachyon-30th-anniversary-smart-speculative-fiction-for-everyone-books</link>
      <description>Celebrate 30 years of spectacular fiction</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Read smart, thought-provoking speculative fiction with the Tachyon and Tachyon authors 30th Anniversary Bundle! Celebrate three decades of bold storytelling with a curated library of standout titles—including ten-time Bram Stoker Award-winner Joe R. Lansdale’s <em>In the Mad Mountains: Stories Inspired by H. P. Lovecraft</em>, Samantha Mills’s <em>The Wings Upon Her Back</em>, Mia Tsai’s <em>Bitter Medicine</em>, and more. Elevate your home library with amazing fiction and help support the Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SQL and Databases by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/sql-and-databases-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>The scorching hot SQL bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your programming skills with the all-new SQL and Databases Bundle by O’Reilly! Learn the industry-standard language for managing and manipulating data in relational databases—and so much more. This expansive course library features essential titles like <em>Learning PHP, MySQL & JavaScript</em> and <em>DuckDB: Up and Running</em>. Whether you're a novice programmer or a seasoned pro, you'll find resources to sharpen your skills and open new doors in tech. Pay what you want and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Frightening and Fantastic Worlds of James Tynion IV</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/frightening-and-fantastic-worlds-james-tynion-iv-books</link>
      <description>The most frightening and fantastic graphic novels</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take a walk off the beaten literary path and explore the eerie, frightening worlds of James Tynion IV. Our latest comics bundle offers atmospheric and unique ebooks that will surely spice up your summer reading—dive into acclaimed series like <em>The Nice House on the Lake </em>, <em>Something is Killing the Children</em>, <em>The Oddly Pedestrian Life of Christopher Chaos</em>, and more. Don’t be scared—explore the frightening and fantastic worlds of James Tynion IV and help support The BINC Foundation with your purchase!<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>The Nice House on the Lake Vol. 1 and 2 will be available to redeem in August 2025.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serious Web Development with React, JavaScript, and modern APIs by Manning</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/serious-web-development-with-react-javascript-and-modern-apis-manning-books</link>
      <description>Get serious about web dev</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bear down on your fields of expertise with these guides from Manning. Learn everything you need to know about React, JavaScript, and more modern APIs. Through a mix of how-to guides, and expert advice, you’ll learn key concepts and fundamentals, explore design patterns and best practices, and get a handle on a range of applications and scenarios. Plus, your purchase helps support Girls Who Code! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>