<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:07:33 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Roll for Initiative with Kieron Gillen by Image Comics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/roll-for-initiative-with-kieron-gillen-image-comics-books</link>
      <description>Worlds of gods and monsters</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into the imagination of one of comics’ most ambitious and creative minds with our Kieron Gillen bundle! The collection includes complete sets of Gillen’s best series: <em>The Wicked + The Divine</em> gives a contemporary spin to ancient mythology from around the world. <em>Die</em> follows a group of friends attempting to free their comrade from a roleplaying game. Britpop-influenced <em>Phonogram</em> follows magicians who use music to alter reality. And that’s barely the tip of the iceberg! As always, choose what you want to pay for this great bundle, and a portion of the proceeds will go to BINC to help bookstores and comic stores with their emergency needs.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python Programming by Pearson</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/python-programming-pearson-books</link>
      <description>Perfect your skills in Python</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Build websites and software, automate tasks, analyze data, and more using Python—the star of our latest Tech Book Bundle with Pearson. Get building-block courses like Effective Python, Python for Programmers, and Learn Python the Hard Way, 5th Edition from this 10+ title library! Python’s easy-to-use interface is approachable yet powerful enough to tackle a wide range of complex tasks. Everything you need to dip your toes into programming languages is here in one bundle—pay what you want and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete AI &amp; GPT Book Bundle with 7,000 Prompts by Mammoth FLASH SALE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/complete-ai-gpt-book-bundle-with-7000-prompts-mammoth-flash-sale-books</link>
      <description>The blueprints to ask AI anything </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0cosWK5yGs4?si=YSoiFnRG1KnDFkRy" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> <br></br> Optimize your life with a little help from direct and easy-to-execute AI and GPT prompts from the pros at Mammoth Club. Choose from a massive library of topic-specific ebooks like The Complete GPT-5 App Development & Prompt Engineering Cookbook: Master AI with ChatGPT 5 and 1,001 Money-Making Prompts: The Complete AI & ChatGPT Guide to Business, Investing & Passive Income. This fantastic deal won’t last long—pay what you want for 7,000+ prompts within one bundle and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magpie Games Extravaganza</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/magpie-games-extravaganza-books</link>
      <description>The tastiest TTRPGs by Magpie</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather the gang—it’s TTRPG night with the Magpie Games Extravaganza Bundle! Get Magpie’s hottest titles in one collection, like Root: The Roleplaying Game, a 3–6 player adventure centered on woodland creatures fighting for money, justice, and freedom from powers far greater than themselves. Or join Aang in Avatar Legends: The Roleplaying Game, a grand adventure set in the world of water, earth, fire, and air. Try these and other standout modern TTRPGs, like Masks: A New Generation, for a price you can’t beat!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Star Wars Novels: Go Beyond the Films</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/star-wars-novels-go-beyond-films-books</link>
      <description>Read the untold story….</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[There are a lot of Star Wars movies out there, but the tale told in the films is nowhere close to the whole story. To fill in all the gaps, you’ll want to check out our newest book bundle, featuring all the best Star Wars novels that take place between the movies! Catch up with Anakin and Obi-Wan during the Clone Wars in <em>Star Wars: Brotherhood</em>. Witness the beginnings of the Death Star in <em>Star Wars: Catalyst</em>. See how the galaxy recovers post-Empire in <em>Star Wars: Bloodline</em> and <em>Star Wars: Aftermath</em>, and the looming threat of the Dark Side in <em>Star Wars: Shadow of the Sith</em>. All purchases help support the charity First Book!<br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are available through Kobo.com. To access the content, create or log in to your Kobo.com account.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essential AI and Tech for Business by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/essential-ai-and-tech-for-business-packt-books</link>
      <description>Lead the charge in AI &amp; Tech</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become a leader of man and machine with the Humble Tech Book Bundle: Essential AI and Tech for Business. This bundle is designed to help you manage systems and teams in the fast-growing AI sector. Choose from a curated library of expert-led resources from Packt, including The Chief AI Officer's Handbook, AI Product Manager's Handbook, Unlocking the Secrets of Prompt Engineering, and more. Pay what you want to gain the soft skills and technical knowledge you need to succeed—and help support Active Minds with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Glen Cook&#39;s Chronicles of The Black Company &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/glen-cooks-chronicles-black-company-more-books</link>
      <description>From the Godfather of Grimdark, read the series that started it all!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Welcome the most legendary Book Bundle across the Sixteen Worlds—Glen Cook's bestselling Chronicles of The Black Company & More! The Black Company is Cook's acclaimed epic fantasy series following a group of hard-bitten mercenaries waging war on behalf of The Lady, who may be the very manifestation of evil itself. <br><br>"With the Black Company series Glen Cook single-handedly changed the face of fantasy."— Steven Erikson, New York Times bestselling author <br><br>Get Glen Cook's finest works, headlined by the complete Black Company collection—and gear up for the next installment arriving in late 2025! Pay what you want and help support the Call of Duty Endowment with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World of Darkness: Month of Darkness 2025 Digital Bundle by Renegade Game Studios</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/world-darkness-month-darkness-2025-digital-bundle-renegade-game-studios-books</link>
      <description>A masquerade of blood &amp; intrigue</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create your own original vampire, torn between survival, supremacy, and your unquenchable thirst for mortal blood with the Month of Darkness 2025 Digital Bundle by Renegade Game Studios! Fifth Edition marks a triumphant return to Vampire: The Masquerade’s original vision—boldly modernized for the 21st century with streamlined gameplay and quality-of-life updates. The rules have been reimagined, yet the deep lore remains, advancing the metaplot and revealing the latest twists in the World of Darkness. Host the bloodiest, most unforgettable TTRPG nights—and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>World of Darkness: Month of Darkness 2025 Physical Book Bundle by Renegade Game Studios</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/world-darkness-month-darkness-2025-physical-book-bundle-renegade-game-studios-books</link>
      <description>Embrace the World of Darkness, Physically</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create an original vampire character, torn between survival, supremacy, and your unquenchable thirst for mortal blood with the Month of Darkness 2025 Physical Bundle by Renegade Game Studios! This collection of Fifth Edition tomes marks a triumphant return to Vampire: The Masquerade’s original vision—boldly modernized for the 21st century with streamlined gameplay and quality-of-life updates. The rules have been reimagined, yet the deep lore remains, advancing the metaplot and revealing the latest twists in the World of Darkness. Host the bloodiest, most unforgettable TTRPG nights—and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Month by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/cybersecurity-month-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Buckle up for Cybersecurity Month</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Online scams and malware are everywhere in 2025—what are you doing to protect yourself? Prevent security breaches before they happen with the techniques and tools from the Humble Tech Book Bundle: Cybersecurity Month by O’Reilly. Top titles from this curated library include <em>Intelligent Continuous Security</em> and <em>Attack Surface Management</em>. Learn software supply chain security and DevSecOps, build an original cyber risk management program, and more. Pay what you want to gain essential digital defense skills and help support Code for America with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mike Mignola&#39;s Hellboy, Witchfinder and More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/mike-mignolas-hellboy-witchfinder-and-more-books</link>
      <description>Some of the strangest chapters from the Hellboy Universe in one bundle!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate the iconic works of comic book author Mike Mignola with great titles starring Hellboy—the half-demon, half-human paranormal investigator who spotlights the latest Humble Comics Bundle.   Get the very best titles from <em>Hellboy</em> and <em>Witchfinder</em> in one curated library of 30+ badass comic—read <em>Young Hellboy: Assault on Castle Death</em>, <em>Hellboy: The Silver Lantern Club</em>, <em>Witchfinder Volume 1: In the Service of Angels</em>, and more. Pay what you want for more than 3 decades of amazing characters and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>