<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS BOOKS</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle books bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 16:26:29 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Spring Shonen Special by Kodansha</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/spring-shonen-special-kodansha-books</link>
      <description>Modern shonen’s biggest &amp; brightest series </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Say goodbye to winter and welcome the warmer weather with Spring Shonen Special Bundle by Kodansha. The shonen genre is full of action-packed stories, with amazing world building, memorable characters and exciting battles&mdash;including the series found in this bundle. Witness Yoh Asakura&rsquo;s journey challenging adversaries around the world to win the Shaman Tournament and become <em>SHAMAN KING</em>, Shinra Kusakabe and his pyro powered comrades fight demons and shadowy organizations in <em>Fire Force</em>, and follow Yato, a down-on-his-luck god struggling to find worshipers in <em>Noragami</em>. This bundle offers nearly 100 digital volumes, giving you every volume of these outstanding series to the very last one. Act now&mdash;get the Spring Shonen Special Bundle and help support The BINC Foundation.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Head First Programming and Patterns by O&#39;Reilly</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/head-first-programming-and-patterns-oreilly-books</link>
      <description>Try the Head First approach to programming</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive in Head First—learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed in modern programming and patterns with this bundle of courses from O’Reilly. Inside this in-depth library, you’ll get expert insights from courses like <em>Head First JavaScript Programming</em>, <em>Head First C#</em>, <em>Head First Software Architecture</em>, and more. Develop the skills you need to test the waters of this fruitful career field today. Deepen your understanding whether you’re a novice or a seasoned professional, and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Heroic Hoard of 5E Power by Kobold Press</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/heroic-hoard-5e-power-kobold-press-books</link>
      <description>Harness the Heroic Hoard’s strength</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for new adventures and endless fun with our latest <em>Dungeons & Dragons</em> bundle. The Heroic Hoard Bundle is a hot collection of tabletop role-playing books from Kobold Press! This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains new subclasses, awesome Eldritch innovations, rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources, and more. Get <em>Deep Magic Volume 1 & 2</em> and everything you need to embark on an epic journey together. Help support the Make-A-Wish Foundation with your purchase too!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Delta Green RPG, VTT, &amp; Fiction Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/delta-green-rpg-vtt-fiction-collection-books</link>
      <description>Delta Green’s very best</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather up your party for endless adventure with this bundle of tabletop role-playing and fiction books where horror meets conspiracy. This TTRPG explorer’s kit from the legendary Delta Green Partnership contains campaign resources and more for the dark and mysterious game Delta Green -- from VTT adaptations to <em>The King in Yellow: Annotated<em> to the newest revelation, God's Hunt for the dark and mysterious game—<em>Delta Green</em>. Get everything you need to fend off the unnatural, undead, and misunderstood on an epic journey together. Plus, your purchase helps support Direct Relief!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self-Reliance and Off-Grid Skills for Dummies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/selfreliance-and-offgrid-skills-for-dummies-books</link>
      <description>Thriving in nature &amp; beyond—For Dummies</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t just survive in the modern outdoors—thrive. Our newest <em>For Dummies</em> bundle features some of the hottest and most useful ebooks for individuals looking to have fun in the wild or start a craft career. Get amazing titles like <em>Home Maintenance For Dummies</em>, <em>Van Life For Dummies</em>, <em>How to Fix Everything For Dummies</em>, and <em>Bread Making For Dummies</em>. Plus, your purchase helps support Covenant House.</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The World of Dragonlance by Wizards of the Coast</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/world-dragonlance-wizards-coast-books</link>
      <description>Feel the strength of Dragonlance </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Embark on an epic adventure through the land of Krynn with the ultimate <em>Dragonlance</em> Collection from Wizards of the Coast.   Follow the perilous journey to protect the mystical Blue Crystal Staff from an evil dragon goddess in <em>Dragons of Autumn Twilight</em>. Untangle dwarven political tensions, hidden dangers, and long-lost secrets with The Companions in <em>Dragons of the Dwarven Depths</em>. The battle of the gods comes to a dramatic climax in <em>Amber and Ashes</em>. Get 25+ amazing page-turners and help support Room to Read with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Classic Pathfinder Mega Bundle 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/classic-pathfinder-mega-bundle-2025-books</link>
      <description>Forge your own legends</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A world of adventure & danger awaits, and the only thing missing is your heroism. Gather your party of trusty friends for countless adventures with our latest <em>Pathfinder</em> bundle from Frog God Games. Mix up your fun with hot <em>Pathfinder</em> TTRPG campaigns like <em>Adventures in Tehuatl</em>, <em>The Northlands Saga Complete</em>, <em>The Grey Citadel</em>, and more. Get everything you need to embark on an epic high fantasy journey together, and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Python: From Beginner to Advanced by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/python-from-beginner-to-advanced-packt-books</link>
      <description>Perfect your skills in Python</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your coding skills with the Python: From Beginner to Advanced Bundle by Packt. Learn to code using one of the most popular and widely used formats within the industry and gain amazing insights from courses like <em>Learn Python Programming</em>, <em>Building AI Intensive Python Applications</em>, <em>Modern Time Series Forecasting with Python</em>, and more. This library of 20+ programming guides are perfect for novice coders and seasoned pros in growing your career. Plus, your purchase helps support the Python Software Foundation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Iron Kingdoms Collection by Steamforged</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/iron-kingdoms-collection-steamforged-books</link>
      <description>Journey to the fabled Iron Kingdoms</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your friends for countless hours of adventure with the Iron Kingdoms Collection by Steamforged Games. Our TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources for the Iron Kingdoms Roleplaying Game and Iron Kingdoms 5e. Explore rich lands powered by steam and magic, encounter beasts and constructs, and engage in epic battles in a full metal fantasy universe. Get everything you need to embark on an epic journey together, and help support Child’s Play Charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Megadungeon Megabundle for DCC &amp; 5E by Goodman Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/megadungeon-megabundle-for-dcc-5e-goodman-games-books</link>
      <description>D&amp;D, DCC, and an amazing mega bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Mages and Elves rejoice! Gather up your party for endless adventure with this mega bundle of tabletop role-playing games by Goodman Games! This TTRPG explorer’s kit contains rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources for <em>Dungeons & Dragons</em> and <em>Dungeon Crawl Classics</em>. Play hot campaigns like <em>Dungeon Crawl Classics - Dark Tower</em>, <em>Dungeon Crawl Classics #83: The Chained Coffin</em> and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase. Embark on new quests with your friends and make your ordinary night extraordinary.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>