<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 22:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Award Nominations Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/award-nominations-bundle-2025</link>
      <description>Award winners and nominees await</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gaming award season is around the corner—kick off the festivities with our curated bundle of award-nominated video games! Play the deeply story-driven and gorgeous indie RPG, <em>A Space for the Unbound</em>, the action-adventure/FPS fusion frenzy <em>Bright Memory: Infinite</em>, and the ghastly good time <em>Ghostrunner 2</em>. Create your own award-winning memories with friends, family, and great games—and help support charity when you shop with Humble Bundle!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 31st, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return to Metroidvania Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/return-to-metroidvania-encore</link>
      <description>Get GRIME, BioGun, Berserk Boy, Monster Sanctuary and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore some great games keeping the Metroidvania genre thriving! Jump, shoot, and sneak your way through some amazing game worlds in our latest bundle! Our all-new Return to Metroidvania Bundle offers 8 modern search action titles that keep the genre’s spirit alive with compelling gameplay and endless replayability. Slay your foes with living weapons in <em>GRIME</em>, platform for your life in <em>Berserk Boy</em>, defeat microscopic viral threats in <em>BioGun</em>, and more—and help support Cool Effect with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before Dec 12th, 2026. Monster Sanctuary keys expire June 12th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesome Snack 2025: Showcase Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wholesome-snack-2025-showcase-bundle</link>
      <description>Celebrate cozy season with Wholesome Snack</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="350" height="300" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kYwGSLM8lsQ?si=Y71Iftxi65ZM-KwS" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Now is the perfect time of year to snuggle up at home with a fun, cozy game or two. If that’s your vibe, we and our friends at Wholesome Snack have just the bundle for you! Dive into the perfectly pleasant games celebrating Wholesome Snack’s 2025 Showcase, like <em>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</em>, in which you assist Snufkin in protecting Moominvalley from an ambitious interloper. Or, send nice letters and swap compliments with your neighbors in <em>Kind Words 2 (lofi city pop)</em>. Build your ideal beach cottage or coastal mansion in <em>Summerhouse</em>, and your perfect garden in <em>Botany Manor</em>. Relax and unwind with this extra-wholesome bundle, and support the good work of the ACLU with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Shashingo: Learn Japanese with Photography and Snufkin keys before June 30th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before December 30th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case &amp; Consequence Collection Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/case-and-consequence-collection-2025-encore</link>
      <description>Play marquee mystery &amp; thriller titles</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Put on your thinking caps, gather clues, and solve mysteries from the humid lowlands of the swamp to the depths of space with the Case &amp; Consequence Collection. Experience a wide range of settings and situations—embark on an Ace Attorney-like detective adventure in <em>Murders on the Yangtze River</em>, play as a literal clue-collecting alligator in <em>BROK the InvestiGator</em>, or go the sci-fi detective route in <em>Between Horizons</em>. Pay what you want and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gear Up For Borderlands 4: Borderlands X Wonderlands Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/gear-up-for-borderlands-4-borderlands-x-wonderlands-bundle-encore</link>
      <description>Insanity, guns, fun—it’s Borderlands</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into the chaotic world of Pandora with the Borderlands &amp; Tiny Tina Bundle from Gearbox Software—one of the most stylish franchises in gaming history. A pioneer of the looter-shooter genre, the Borderlands series perfected the weapon-grind loop with addicting gunplay and over-the-top rewards—aka bigger, badder, crazier guns. Pay what you want and unlock Tiny Tina's Wonderlands: Chaotic Great Edition, Borderlands 1–3, New Tales from the Borderlands, and more. Get the ultimate Borderlands experience—and help support Covenant House with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 10th, 2026. <br/><br/></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upload VR Winter 2025 Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/upload-vr-winter-2025-bundle</link>
      <description>Escape reality with VR games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whether you just got your first VR headset and are ready for whatever the VR universe has to throw at you, or you’re an old hand looking to expand their collection of games, we’ve got a great bundle of post-apocalyptic adventures and hellish horrors inspired by UploadVR’s Winter Showcase! Descend deep into literal hell and fight off its most twisted demons in <em>Hellsweeper VR</em>. Survive the battlegrounds of <em>Ghosts of Tabor</em>. Puzzle your way out of the action-packed escape rooms of <em>I Expect You to Die 3: Cog in the Machine</em>. There’s so much more to enjoy in this VR bundle, so grab it while you can and support the digital privacy defenders at Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 26th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rawfury: Rawcember to Remember 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/rawfury-rawcember-to-remember-2025</link>
      <description>RAWcember to Remember with a vengeance</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ho ho hooray for epic savings—get into the holiday spirit with a curated collection of unique and exciting indie games! Play awesome indie titles like the addicting puzzle-platformer, <em>American Arcadia</em>; the point-and-click thriller, <em>Kathy Rain 2: Soothsayer</em>; the retro-inspired RPG adventure, <em>SKALD: Against the Black Priory</em>; and more with Raw Fury’s RAWcember to Remember Bundle. Experience new games and help support Save the Children with your purchase when you game with Humble Bundle!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before June 24th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony: Adventures in Equestria Deck-Building Game Physical Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/my-little-pony-adventures-in-equestria-deckbuilding-game-physical-bundle</link>
      <description>Friendship is magic</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gallop through the land of Equestria in the <em>My Little Pony: Adventures in Equestria</em> deck-building game, now available along with multiple expansions all in one convenient bundle! Choose your pony, gather your pals, and complete challenges to build up your deck and help out the residents of Ponyville. This bundle also includes the <em>Princess Pageantry</em> expansion, the <em>True Talents</em> expansion, the Meeple Pack, and more! Every purchase at the price of your choice helps end childhood hunger with No Kid Hungry.<br><br><strong><em><span style="color: #ef9741;">Limited Quantities Available!</span></em></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Entertainment: Full Send Bundle!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/maximum-entertainment-full-send-bundle</link>
      <description>Explore unique worlds, play great games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into whole universes of immersive storytelling and gameplay with this bundle of all the great stuff from Maximum Entertainment! Battle the dangerous gangs of post-apocalypse New York City in <em>Double Dragon</em> prequel <em>Double Dragon Gaiden: Rise of the Dragons</em>. Solve a series of puzzles and try to keep your head in the psychological horror game <em>In Sound Mind</em>. Traverse a dangerous world inspired by Nordic folktales in <em>Bramble: The Mountain King</em>. There’s way more to enjoy in this immersive bundle, so claim it now at the price of your choice, and support the global reforestation efforts of One Tree Planted!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before June 26th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 for $15 Black Friday Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/15-for-15-black-friday-bundle</link>
      <description>Big savings on Black Friday</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t fear what creeps in the night—welcome it—with the gorgeous hand-drawn art style of <em>CreaksM</em>. Fight to ensure the survival of your cubs and the entire fox species in <em>Endling – Extinction is Forever</em>, or execute PvP tactical missions with military precision in the inventive FPS <em>Due Process</em>. Save big on this diverse library of awesome indie games and help support Kiss the Ground with your Black Friday purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 3rd, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worms 30th Anniversary Celebration</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/worms-30th-anniversary-celebration</link>
      <description>Happy Wormiversary!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get your hands on some high-octane invertebrate action with this bundle of Worms games! In celebration of the irreverent artillery tactics series’ 30th anniversary, we’ve got 12 Worms classics and fan favorites together in a single collection meant for mega-fans and newcomers alike. Go back to the series’ roots with the 1990s charms of the original Worms and Worms Armageddon, and chart the series’ evolution with newer games like the 3D action of Worms Ultimate Mayhem and the arena-based cross-platform combat of Worms Rumble! Shoot and slither your way to the top of the worm pile with this bundle, available for the price of your choosing, and support One Tree Planted with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 17th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stories from Assemble Entertainment</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/narratives-and-stories-from-assemble-entertainment</link>
      <description>Primetime games from Assemble Entertainment </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepare for immersive stories and experiences told by Assemble Entertainment with this curated collection of indie games! Explore the decayed remains of a lost civilization on your custom sandglider in <em>FAR: Lone Sails</em>, design and sell custom stickers within your own cutesy store in <em>Sticky Business</em>, or navigate a fairy tale-like world in <em>A Juggler's Tale</em>—the sophisticated and complex puzzle platformer. Pay what you want for a dynamic array of standout indie titles and help support CALM with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devious Deckbuilders 2</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/devious-deckbuilders-2</link>
      <description>The dark side of deckbuilding</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Deckbuilding enthusiasts, rejoice! Not only do we have a great bundle of deckbuilders of all sorts, all of these great games use that shared mechanic to explore darker, spookier, and sometimes downright demonic narratives. Develop unique strategies and match your mahjong skills against actual demons in <em>Demonic Mahjong</em>. Customize your heroes and your deck to survive a cyber-fantasy adventure in <em>Breach Wanderers</em>. Rally your party and traverse the dingiest dungeons of <em>Deepest Chamber: Resurrection</em>. There’s a lot more to enjoy in this spine-chilling bundle, so grab it for the price of your choosing and support Alzheimer’s organization Hilarity for Charity with your purchase!<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys for Ring of Pain expire. Please redeem keys before June 12th, 2026.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Headup Games: Brilliant Bargains</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/headup-games-brilliant-bargains</link>
      <description>Blinded by big-time savings</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[These games shine bright like a diamond—grab a collection of hot titles from Headup Games with the all-new Brilliant Bargains Bundle! Experience a fresh twist on 3D platforming in Pumpkin Jack. Dive, launch, and laugh your way through the inventive hybrid of the PortalTM and Bridge ConstructorTM franchises in Bridge Constructor Portal. Or party up with your friends and brain-sucking besties in Ben and Ed – Blood Party, a wild zombie-centric game show extravaganza! With such a diverse lineup to choose from, the fun never fades.<p><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your keys before December 10th, 2026.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Headup Games: Brilliant Bargains</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/headup-games-brilliant-bargains</link>
      <description>Blinded by big-time savings</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[These games shine bright like a diamond—grab a collection of hot titles from Headup Games with the all-new Brilliant Bargains Bundle! Experience a fresh twist on 3D platforming in Pumpkin Jack. Dive, launch, and laugh your way through the inventive hybrid of the PortalTM and Bridge ConstructorTM franchises in Bridge Constructor Portal. Or party up with your friends and brain-sucking besties in Ben and Ed – Blood Party, a wild zombie-centric game show extravaganza! With such a diverse lineup to choose from, the fun never fades.<p><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your keys before December 10th, 2026.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Virtual Realities Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/beyond-virtual-realities-bundle</link>
      <description>Leave reality in the dust</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Embark on your maiden voyage into virtual reality gaming—or expand your existing VR library—with a curated collection of inventive and engaging titles. Bow down to Dragon Fist: VR Kung Fu, an action-packed and heartfelt homage to Hollywood’s golden era of martial-arts cinema. Let your intrusive thoughts win in The Break-In, a hilarious and immersive robbery title where you steal everything—including the kitchen sink. Or drop-kick a random dude’s chest in Drunkn Bar Fight, a crazy co-op experience that needs little explanation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>