<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 22:04:39 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>House Flipper and Friends Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/house-flipper-and-friends-bundle</link>
      <description>Home renovations from your couch</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about home renovations? Jump into the creative and crafty world of <em>House Flipper</em> with this value-packed game bundle! Get started with the core game then enhance your experience with a massive collection of add-ons and DLC, featuring <em>The Tenants - Pets</em>, <em>Garden DLC</em>, <em>Train Yard Builder</em>, and more. Pay what you want for the ultimate home improvement and renovation experience, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deckbuilder Bonanza</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/deckbuilder-bonanza</link>
      <description>It’s a deckbuilder bonanza!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Make your friends look silly in a friendly game of cards—but these aren’t just any card games. The Deckbuilder Bonanza Bundle offers players some of the best roguelike deck-building games around. Play hot titles like <em>HELLCARD</em>, <em>Backpack Hero</em>, and much more. These titles magically mix the familiarity of card games with roguelike progression elements to create unique and addicting video games. Mix up your game genres—and help support The ESA Foundation. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pathfinder Kingmaker Bundle from Paizo Inc.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/books/pathfinder-kingmaker-bundle-from-paizo-inc-books</link>
      <description>Elevate your Pathfinder campaigns </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather your party of trusty friends for countless adventures with our latest <em>Pathfinder</em> bundle from Paizo Inc. Enhance your existing <em>Pathfinder</em> collection with new rulebooks, sourcebooks, and campaign resources. Highlights from the Pathfinder Kingmaker Bundle include <em>Pathfinder: Kingmaker Enhanced Plus Edition</em> and <em>Pathfinder Kingmaker Companion Guide</em>. Get everything you need to embark on an epic high fantasy journey together, and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Capcom Arcade Classics &amp; Fighters Pack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/capcom-arcade-classics-fighter-pack</link>
      <description>A certified Capcom extravaganza </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hit your friends with a punishing Shoryuken in our Capcom Arcade Classics &amp; Fighters Pack. Dive into a robust collection of <em>Street Fighter</em> titles including <em>Street Fighter V - Championship Edition</em> and <em>Street Fighter 30th Anniversary Collection</em>, and fantastic arcade titles like <em>Mega Man</em> and <em>Final Fight</em>. Get hyped for tournament season, test your skills, and help support the Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase. <br/><br/><a style="color:#EF9741"><strong>Games from the CAPCOM Arcade Stadium Complete Pack are collected into two total keys: one for CAPCOM Arcade Stadium and the second for CAPCOM Arcade 2nd Stadium.</strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better With a Friend: Co-op Adventures</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/better-with-friend-coop-adventures</link>
      <description>Gaming is better with friends</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get the snacks ready because we’re playing all night! The Better With a Friend Bundle features amazing co-op titles like <em>Across the Obelisk</em>, <em>Risk of Rain Returns</em>, <em>Trine 4</em>, and more! Snag great games, get the party started, and support the Michael J Fox Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Destiny 2: The Story So Far 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/destiny-2-story-so-far-2025</link>
      <description>Do you have the heart of a Guardian? </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Destiny 2 Story So Far 2025 Bundle gives you access to the Light & Darkness Saga. Purchase the right tier for you to complete the chapters you may have missed, or live the adventure to its thrilling end! <br><br><a style="color: #ef9741;" data-darkreader-inline-color=""><strong>*Customers must download the free edition of Destiny 2 on Steam in order to redeem the keys for expansion content.</strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>