<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 16:27:13 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Curve Games Care Package</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/curve-games-care-package</link>
      <description>A care package from Curve Games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Our latest bundle offers players the very best from award-winning independent publisher Curve Games. Adorable visuals don’t diminish the action in <em>Bomber Crew</em>. Pick your specialized flight crew and keep your plane in tip-top shape to successfully accomplish each mission—plus—this bundle includes awesome weapons, planes, and skin DLCs! Embark on an exhilarating post-apocalyptic in <em>Badlands Crew</em>; a caravan driver where players customize their rigs and cause mayhem! Try adorably addicting games and help support Campaign Against Living Miserably (CALM) with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Worlds Collide 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/lego-worlds-collide-2025</link>
      <description>A LEGO world for every interest </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re stacking up great games brick-by-brick with the all-new LEGO Worlds Collide Bundle! This gigantic bundle from Warner Bros. mixes your favorite franchises with the unmistakable LEGO charm to create unique gaming experiences that puts you in the shoes of your favorite characters. Play <em>LEGO® Star Wars™: The Skywalker Saga</em>, <em>LEGO® Marvel Super Heroes 2 Deluxe Edition</em>, <em>LEGO® Batman™ 3: Beyond Gotham Premium Edition</em>, and become the LEGO hero of legend! Pay what you want for the ultimate LEGO bundle, and help support Raiden Science Foundation with your purchase! <br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your key before March 24th. 2026.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Likes and Lites</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/indie-likes-and-lites</link>
      <description>The biggest little indie games </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve curated our hottest bundle of the summer with the coolest indie games around. Explore the action-packed puzzler from the hero that helped establish a genre with <em>Shovel Knight Pocket Dungeon</em>, try the addictive roguelite puzzle mashup <em>Let's! Revolution!</em>, or enjoy a satirical dungeon-crawler based on the monotony of modern life in <em>Going Under</em>, and much more. Fall in love with an unexpected indie game and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draknek &amp; Friends: 12 Years of Great Puzzle Games!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/draknek-and-friends-12th-anniversary-celebration</link>
      <description>Prized puzzle games for you </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Diversify your games library and mix in some hot brainteasers with our latest Bundle. Celebrate 12 years of awesome titles from the genre-leading publisher, Draknek &amp; Friends with the very best from their epic catalog. Master the magical power of words to unlock mind-bending effects in <em>LOK Digital</em>. Curious monsters just want friends—use puzzles to make them in <em>A Monster’s Expedition</em>. The chemistry-based puzzles are explosively fun in <em>Sokobond Express</em>. Play these engaging puzzlers and help support The Trevor Project with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>The Trevor Project was not involved in the selection of the content in this promotion and the views, opinions, and ideas expressed in the games are not endorsed by, and do not reflect or represent the views and opinions of The Trevor Project.</em></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duo of Justice: Ace Attorney and Mega Man</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/duo-justice-ace-attorney-and-mega-man</link>
      <description>The hero team-up you never knew you needed…until now</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Put on your suit and tie and charge up your Mega Buster, because Phoenix Wright and Mega Man have joined forces for our latest games bundle! Act out the exciting courtroom drama at the heart of <em>Ace Attorney</em> compilations <em>The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles</em> and <em>Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trilogy</em>. Try out all the best <em>Mega Man</em> games with <em>Mega Man Legacy Collection, Mega Man X Legacy Collection,</em> and <em>Mega Man Battle Network Legacy Collection Vol. 1.</em> A wealth of great games are at your fingertips for the price of your choice, and all purchases support Breakthrough T1D!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGN Gamescom Bundle 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/gamescom-bundle-2025</link>
      <description>Greetings from Gamescom Germany!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gamescom 2025 is here—and we’ve assembled a curated bundle of standout games to celebrate! Located in Cologne, Germany, Gamescom is Europe's leading gaming & tech expo—where the best in the industry gather. Rule the boroughs using speed and style in <em>Bomb Rush Cyberfunk</em>, blast through <em>Antonblast's</em> fast-paced explosive action platformer worlds, and enjoy throwback vibes with turn-based RPG gameplay in <em>Lost Eidolons</em>, plus more. Get the very best of Gamescom from the comfort of your home and help support DonorsChoose with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Table Top Tag Team: Dire Wolf x Marmalade</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/table-top-tag-team-dire-wolf-x-marmalade</link>
      <description>Digital delivery of delightful boardgames </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Our latest Boardgame Bundle brings your favorite physical games to life with dynamic digital editions. Pay what you want for the very best from Direwolf and Marmalade games and let the good times roll.   Make the woods your battleground in <em>Root</em>—a boardgame rooted in fun! Establish a railroad empire while squashing the competition in <em>Ticket to Ride</em>. Solve the time old question of ‘who done it’ in <em>Clue/Cluedo: Classic Edition</em>. Play these and more iconic boardgames—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Whale & Dolphin Conservation. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>