<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 16:29:32 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Humblecraft: RTS Rush</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/humblecraft-rts-rush</link>
      <description>Get tactical with RTS standouts</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Feel the rush of real-time strategy with this outstanding bundle of top-tier indie RTS titles! Build and command voxel-powered vehicles across sea and space in <em>From the Depths</em>. Defend your stronghold in classic medieval warfare with <em>Stronghold: Definitive Edition</em>. Engage in Cold War-era combat with intense 1v1 and 8v8 battles in <em>Men of War: Assault Squad 2</em>—and more. Challenge your tactical skills with great games and help support Xperience Studios with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Games Done Quick 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/summer-games-done-quick-2025</link>
      <description>Speedrunners + charity = awesome</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Help support the annual Summer Games Done Quick live-stream event with our latest collaborative bundle with GamesDoneQuick! Add a collection of fun, fast-paced games tied to the speedrunning community to your library—and feel good doing it. Plus, a portion of your purchase goes directly to Doctors Without Borders. Try your hand at speedrunning with competitive and entertaining titles like <em>Finding Frankie</em>, <em>Code Bunny</em>, <em>Catlateral Damage: Remeowstered</em>, and more. Don’t miss the charity stream extravaganza—tune in to Games Done Quick from July 6–12, 2025!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Splash</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/summer-splash</link>
      <description>From the beach to your gaming setup</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into great water-themed games with the all-new Summer Splash Bundle. Defend the heir to the crabby kingdom using expert strategy and coral reefs as defense in <em>Crab God</em>. Leap through a kid-friendly action-platformer set on the island of Mara in <em>Koa and the 5 Pirates of Mara</em>. Explore the dark depths of the ocean with an unparalleled sense of atmosphere in <em>ABZU</em>, and more. Play great games that emphasize ocean conservation—and help support Coral Guardian with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upload VR Summer 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/upload-vr-summer-2025</link>
      <description>Dive into a new reality with VR</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want to start your VR gaming journey with our latest bundle of immersive titles! Step into the boots of a master swordsman and experience intense, physics-based combat in <em>Until You Fall</em>. Then dive into the mind-bending world of <em>Vertigo 2</em> as you uncover the mysteries of a quantum reactor teeming with aliens, rogue robots, and deadly fauna. Play these standout VR games and more—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the mental health advocates at Safe In Our World.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serenity Forge Storyteller&#39;s Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/serenity-forge-storytellers-bundle</link>
      <description>Indie games that make an impact</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Great games come in all shapes and sizes—pay what you want and explore the inventive library of indie developer and publisher Serenity Forge with our latest bundle! The pros at Serenity Forge are master storytellers, supporting exceptional titles that move your soul like <em>Arcadian Atlas</em>, <em>Long Gone Days</em>, <em>Virgo Versus the Zodiac</em>, and more. Play meaningful and impactful games that challenge the way you think, and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospital of Colorado today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June Tunes</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/june-tunes</link>
      <description>Rhythm &amp; groove in gaming</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fans of music and games—say hi to the June Tunes Bundle! This collection perfectly blends everything you love about music and gaming to deliver fun and unique gameplay experiences. Remix tracks from popular artists like Marshmello, Porter Robinson, and Yukika in <em>DJ Max Respect V</em>, keep the rhythm with a single button in <em>One Btn Bosses</em>, and follow the beat to defeat enemies in <em>Rhythm Fighter</em>. Play great rhythm games and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>