<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 01:48:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Entertainment: Full Send Bundle!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/maximum-entertainment-full-send-bundle</link>
      <description>Explore unique worlds, play great games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into whole universes of immersive storytelling and gameplay with this bundle of all the great stuff from Maximum Entertainment! Battle the dangerous gangs of post-apocalypse New York City in <em>Double Dragon</em> prequel <em>Double Dragon Gaiden: Rise of the Dragons</em>. Solve a series of puzzles and try to keep your head in the psychological horror game <em>In Sound Mind</em>. Traverse a dangerous world inspired by Nordic folktales in <em>Bramble: The Mountain King</em>. There’s way more to enjoy in this immersive bundle, so claim it now at the price of your choice, and support the global reforestation efforts of One Tree Planted!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before June 26th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>15 for $15 Black Friday Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/15-for-15-black-friday-bundle</link>
      <description>Big savings on Black Friday</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t fear what creeps in the night—welcome it—with the gorgeous hand-drawn art style of <em>CreaksM</em>. Fight to ensure the survival of your cubs and the entire fox species in <em>Endling – Extinction is Forever</em>, or execute PvP tactical missions with military precision in the inventive FPS <em>Due Process</em>. Save big on this diverse library of awesome indie games and help support Kiss the Ground with your Black Friday purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 3rd, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worms 30th Anniversary Celebration</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/worms-30th-anniversary-celebration</link>
      <description>Happy Wormiversary!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get your hands on some high-octane invertebrate action with this bundle of Worms games! In celebration of the irreverent artillery tactics series’ 30th anniversary, we’ve got 12 Worms classics and fan favorites together in a single collection meant for mega-fans and newcomers alike. Go back to the series’ roots with the 1990s charms of the original Worms and Worms Armageddon, and chart the series’ evolution with newer games like the 3D action of Worms Ultimate Mayhem and the arena-based cross-platform combat of Worms Rumble! Shoot and slither your way to the top of the worm pile with this bundle, available for the price of your choosing, and support One Tree Planted with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 17th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devious Deckbuilders 2</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/devious-deckbuilders-2</link>
      <description>The dark side of deckbuilding</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Deckbuilding enthusiasts, rejoice! Not only do we have a great bundle of deckbuilders of all sorts, all of these great games use that shared mechanic to explore darker, spookier, and sometimes downright demonic narratives. Develop unique strategies and match your mahjong skills against actual demons in <em>Demonic Mahjong</em>. Customize your heroes and your deck to survive a cyber-fantasy adventure in <em>Breach Wanderers</em>. Rally your party and traverse the dingiest dungeons of <em>Deepest Chamber: Resurrection</em>. There’s a lot more to enjoy in this spine-chilling bundle, so grab it for the price of your choosing and support Alzheimer’s organization Hilarity for Charity with your purchase!<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys for Ring of Pain expire. Please redeem keys before June 12th, 2026.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stories from Assemble Entertainment</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/narratives-and-stories-from-assemble-entertainment</link>
      <description>Primetime games from Assemble Entertainment </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepare for immersive stories and experiences told by Assemble Entertainment with this curated collection of indie games! Explore the decayed remains of a lost civilization on your custom sandglider in <em>FAR: Lone Sails</em>, design and sell custom stickers within your own cutesy store in <em>Sticky Business</em>, or navigate a fairy tale-like world in <em>A Juggler's Tale</em>—the sophisticated and complex puzzle platformer. Pay what you want for a dynamic array of standout indie titles and help support CALM with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Headup Games: Brilliant Bargains</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/headup-games-brilliant-bargains</link>
      <description>Blinded by big-time savings</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[These games shine bright like a diamond—grab a collection of hot titles from Headup Games with the all-new Brilliant Bargains Bundle! Experience a fresh twist on 3D platforming in Pumpkin Jack. Dive, launch, and laugh your way through the inventive hybrid of the PortalTM and Bridge ConstructorTM franchises in Bridge Constructor Portal. Or party up with your friends and brain-sucking besties in Ben and Ed – Blood Party, a wild zombie-centric game show extravaganza! With such a diverse lineup to choose from, the fun never fades.<p><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your keys before December 10th, 2026.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beyond Virtual Realities Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/beyond-virtual-realities-bundle</link>
      <description>Leave reality in the dust</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Embark on your maiden voyage into virtual reality gaming—or expand your existing VR library—with a curated collection of inventive and engaging titles. Bow down to Dragon Fist: VR Kung Fu, an action-packed and heartfelt homage to Hollywood’s golden era of martial-arts cinema. Let your intrusive thoughts win in The Break-In, a hilarious and immersive robbery title where you steal everything—including the kitchen sink. Or drop-kick a random dude’s chest in Drunkn Bar Fight, a crazy co-op experience that needs little explanation.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Game Favorites</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/indieio-single-publisher-bundle</link>
      <description>Unmissable indie games await </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add a splash of color to your game library with vibrant indie titles from&nbsp;indie game publishing and management platform&nbsp;indie.io! Cultivate the life you want in the cozy farming sim Echoes of the Plum Grove, travel to the purrfectly adorable town of Caterwaul Way to manage and rejuvenate your grandmother’s café in Cat Cafe Manager, and explore even more colorful worlds with this rich and diverse collection of indie favorites. Pay what you want for great games and help support Humble Bundle’s Xperience Studios with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frogwares: Lovecraft and Sherlock Classics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/frogwares-lovecraft-and-sherlock-classics</link>
      <description>Monsters and mysteries await</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Step into horror and mystery’s greatest minds: cosmic terror master H.P. Lovecraft and Sir Arthur Conan Doyle’s legendary detective Sherlock Holmes. Our latest bundle contains the very best from the gamemakers at Frogwares to satisfy your most eldritch cravings. Survive the supernaturally haunted New England town at the heart of <em>The Sinking City Remastered</em>. Hone your investigative skills by discovering the secrets behind the death of Sherlock Holmes’ mother in <em>Sherlock Holmes: Chapter One</em>. Solve the mystery of the Cthulhu mythos once and for all in the Lovecraft and Sherlock crossover <em>Sherlock Holmes The Awakened</em>. All this and much more for the price of your choosing, and all purchases help benefit the Malala Fund, supporting education for girls everywhere.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Telltale Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/telltale-collection</link>
      <description>Captivating storytelling meets amazing gameplay</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore captivating renditions of your favorite franchises with our Telltale Collection. Create your own adventures set within the worlds of <em>Batman</em>, <em>The Walking Dead</em>, <em>The Expanse</em>, and more. The Telltale Collection features iconic titles like <em>The Expanse: A Telltale Series</em>, <em>The Walking Dead: Season 1 &amp; 400 Days</em>, and <em>Batman: The Enemy Within</em>. Lose yourself in Telltale Games’ signature choose-your-own-adventure style today and help support Save The Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror Icons Showcase</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/horror-icons-showcase</link>
      <description>Horror games fit for fall</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t fear what crawls in the night—attack it head-on with weapons blazing! Feel the adrenaline rush of great horror games with a Halloween-approved bundle. Experience animated thrills in <em>Bendy: Lone Wolf</em>—a cartoon-inspired and haunting Roguelike adventure through the halls of the world’s most evil animation studio and expolore a new career in the eerily accurate <em>The Mortuary Assistant - Definitive Edition</em>. Plus, we're adding a mysterious hit title in November! Feel the chills all season long and support Girls Who Code with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armor Games: The Retro &amp; Reborn Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/armor-games-the-retro-and-reborn-collection</link>
      <description>From Armor with love</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Start new adventures with the very best games from Armor Games Studios. Play <em>The Last Stand: Aftermath</em>—the zombie survival rogue-lite where you race against the clock to help as many survivors as possible before you turn. Your journey begins once you’ve been bitten—isn’t that a twist? Or dive into the <em>Swords & Souls: Legacy Collection</em>, a five-piece nugget of hilarious games packed with hack-and-slash hijinks and more. Get the coolest collection of indie games from Armor Games Studios, and help support Children’s Miracle Network!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Fears Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/indie-fears-bundle</link>
      <description>Indie thrills and chills</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get into the spooky season with this new bundle of the creepiest indie games around! Discover what all the fuss is about with the much-memed space-set nightmare fuel game <em>Mouthwashing</em>. Keep a mystery train running and try not to run out of oxygen on the steep mountain slopes of <em>Threshold</em>. Flip burgers and keep your customers satisfied in the spooky cooking simulator send-up <em>Kiosk</em>. Those aren’t even the tip of the horror game iceberg featured in this bundle, so name your price and help support SpecialEffect charity with your purchase. And maybe keep a light on while you play. You never know.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>