<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 20:26:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Uncharted Realms Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/uncharted-realms-bundle</link>
      <description>Excitement from Mars and beyond </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore strange new corners of the cosmos with the Uncharted Realms Bundle! Investigate the unknown mystery behind a distress call from a Martian mining site in <em>Fort Solis</em>. Discover unusual and exciting alien planets—as weird and adorable aliens in <em>The Eternal Cylinder</em>. Is this world human ready? Play as a quirky planet evaluator in <em>Journey to the Savage Planet</em>, and more. Pay what you want for out-of-this-world space games—and help support charity: water with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WB Play the Legends</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wb-play-legends</link>
      <description>The very best from Warner Bros. Games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Love Sub-Zero, Middle-earth, and the Bat Family? The top-selling Warner Bros. Games bundle is back! Experience genre-defining combat as the Dark Knight himself in <em>Batman: Arkham Knight Premium Edition</em>, go toe-to-toe as the strongest and watch the blood drip off Raiden’s fists in <em>Mortal Kombat 11: Ultimate Edition</em>, stop the Court of Owls from overrunning Gotham City in <em>Gotham Knights</em>, and more. Satisfy your superhero roleplaying fantasies and help support the Raiden Science Foundation with your purchase!<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your key before February 27th. 2026.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better with 4 Friends! Co-Op Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/better-with-4-friends-coop-bundle</link>
      <description>Grab the gang—let&#39;s game!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Grab your besties for a co-op game night with the all-new Better With 4 Friends Bundle! Play a variety of hilarious and wacky indie games designed to get the whole squad laughing. Lay track before the train crashes in <em>Unrailed!</em>, turn moving day into pure chaos in <em>Moving Out</em>, and battle blazes together in <em>Embr</em>—plus so much more. Pay what you want for this laugh-packed collection and help support the Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sniper Elite: Classics Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/sniper-elite-classics-collection</link>
      <description>Line up the perfect shot</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Feel the exhilaration of lining up the perfect shot with the Sniper Elite: Classics Collection. Choose from dozens of rifles, maps, and targets across 5 complete <em>Sniper Elite</em> titles—including the <em>Sniper Elite 5 and Sniper Elite 4 Deluxe</em>. Relive sweet shots with the awesome Kill Cam and immerse yourself in the strategic gameplay. Pay what you want for hours of in-depth gunplay from the ultimate shooting simulation experience, and help support The Trevor Project with your purchase.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>The Trevor Project was not involved in the selection of the content in this promotion and the views, opinions, and ideas expressed in the games are not endorsed by, and do not reflect or represent the views and opinions of The Trevor Project.</em></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>