<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 20:23:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Horror Icons Showcase</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/horror-icons-showcase</link>
      <description>Horror games fit for fall</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t fear what crawls in the night—attack it head-on with weapons blazing! Feel the adrenaline rush of great horror games with a Halloween-approved bundle. Experience animated thrills in <em>Bendy: Lone Wolf</em>—a cartoon-inspired and haunting Roguelike adventure through the halls of the world’s most evil animation studio and expolore a new career in the eerily accurate <em>The Mortuary Assistant - Definitive Edition</em>. Plus, we're adding a mysterious hit title in November! Feel the chills all season long and support Girls Who Code with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armor Games: The Retro &amp; Reborn Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/armor-games-the-retro-and-reborn-collection</link>
      <description>From Armor with love</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Start new adventures with the very best games from Armor Games Studios. Play <em>The Last Stand: Aftermath</em>—the zombie survival rogue-lite where you race against the clock to help as many survivors as possible before you turn. Your journey begins once you’ve been bitten—isn’t that a twist? Or dive into the <em>Swords & Souls: Legacy Collection</em>, a five-piece nugget of hilarious games packed with hack-and-slash hijinks and more. Get the coolest collection of indie games from Armor Games Studios, and help support Children’s Miracle Network!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Fears Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/indie-fears-bundle</link>
      <description>Indie thrills and chills</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get into the spooky season with this new bundle of the creepiest indie games around! Discover what all the fuss is about with the much-memed space-set nightmare fuel game <em>Mouthwashing</em>. Keep a mystery train running and try not to run out of oxygen on the steep mountain slopes of <em>Threshold</em>. Flip burgers and keep your customers satisfied in the spooky cooking simulator send-up <em>Kiosk</em>. Those aren’t even the tip of the horror game iceberg featured in this bundle, so name your price and help support SpecialEffect charity with your purchase. And maybe keep a light on while you play. You never know.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microids Mega Mix 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/microids-mega-mix-2025</link>
      <description>Meet the Microids Mega Mix</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Make room for an all-new Mega Bundle from Microids! This collection of 20+ games offers the very best in RPGs, adventure, and family-friendly fun that everyone can enjoy. Lose yourself across 32 wacky and hilarious levels in Garfield Lasagna Party, uncover your true identity through exploration in Syberia 1–3, and gather the gang for a rockin’ good time in The Smurfs – Village Party! Pay what you want for an amazing assortment of games and help support charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Myst and Riven Complete Collection 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/myst-and-riven-complete-collection-2025</link>
      <description>Revisit the icons</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’re of a certain age, your first experience with video games was likely playing <em>Myst</em> or <em>Riven</em> on your parents’ PC. Whether you’ve replayed the games in the years since, explored anything else in Cyan Worlds’ catalog, or have just been thinking about revisiting a classic, our newest bundle of the complete <em>Myst</em> and <em>Riven</em> collection is sure to satisfy. Go back to the very beginning with the original <em>Myst</em> and <em>Riven</em> or check out the remastered versions. Expand your horizons and go deeper into the adventure with the later <em>Myst</em> sequels and <em>URU: Complete Chronicles</em>. You choose your price, and a portion of every purchase supports diabetes charity Breakthrough T1D!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom: 10th Anniversary Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/kingdom-10th-anniversary-bundle</link>
      <description>Create your Kingdom</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into the pixelated worlds of Kingdom on the series’ 10th Anniversary with this bundle chock-full of Kingdom games! Ride your noble steed to defend your lands from the Greed in <em>Kingdom Two Crowns</em>, and try out multiple expansions inspired by different settings, like <em>Call of Olympus</em> and <em>Norse Lands</em>. Experience where it all started in <em>Kingdom: New Lands</em>, and get even more retro with it in <em>Kingdom Eighties</em>. Pay what you want to become the monarch of your dreams, and your purchase supports the humanitarian aid work at Team Rubicon USA.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandai Namco - Dark Pictures &amp; Little Nightmares Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/bandai-namco-dark-pictures-little-nightmares-bundle</link>
      <description>Big scares—bigger savings</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Even a bat could see these savings—transform your home library into something supernatural with horror games by BANDAI NAMCO! Test your nerve and skills with fantastically haunting titles like Little Nightmares I &amp; II, the eerie adventures of a young boy and girl trapped in a nightmarish world, and The Dark Pictures Anthology: The Devil in Me, a chilling tale of documentarians exploring a haunted castle. Kick off Halloween with frighteningly good deals and help support Whale and Dolphin Conservation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Square Enix - Life is Strange True Colors Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/square-enix-life-is-strange-true-colors-bundle</link>
      <description>Turn back the clock</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Shades of <em>Twin Peaks, Gone Home</em>, Stephen King, and your favorite retro indie movies set the stage for <em>Life is Strange</em>, your favorite gamer’s favorite game. A decade after the first game’s release, our latest bundle dives into the <em>Life is Strange</em> world, including <em>Life is Strange: True Colors</em> and the <em>True Colors</em> Deluxe Upgrade. If you’re itching to rewind back to the beginning of it all, the bundle also includes the entire <em>Life is Strange Remastered Collection</em>—refined editions of the original <em>Life is Strange</em> and its sequel <em>Life is Strange: Before the Storm</em>. Plus, get 10% off the newest entry <em>Life is Strange: Double Exposure</em>! Get the comprehensive <em>Life is Strange</em> experience at your fingertips for the price of your choice, and every purchase supports the LGBTQ lifeline at the Trevor Project. <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>The Trevor Project was not involved in the selection of the content in this promotion and the views, opinions, and ideas expressed in the games are not endorsed by, and do not reflect or represent the views and opinions of The Trevor Project.</em></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Momcore: Games For a Busy Life</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/momcore-games-for-busy-life</link>
      <description>Pause reality, embrace the cozy</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take a break from your busy schedule with our latest games bundle, featuring everything you need to feel cozy, calm, and fulfilled on your time off. Escape the big city for a low-stakes mail delivery adventure in <em>Lake</em>. Rebuild a small town’s cat cafe and fill it with comfy furniture, delicious snacks, and friendly felines in <em>Calico</em>. Test your beekeeping skills with fun minigames and lush environments in the laid-back sim game <em>APICO</em>, heal your customers’ ailments in the hot springs of <em>Onsen Master</em>, and more! You choose what you pay, and every purchase supports the Trevor Project’s lifesaving services to LGBTQ youth.<br><br> <em>The Trevor Project was not involved in the selection of the content in this promotion and the views, opinions, and ideas expressed in the games are not endorsed by, and do not reflect or represent the views and opinions of The Trevor Project.</em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Empires and Engines: Return to Tropico &amp; More from Kalypso!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/empires-and-engines-return-to-tropico-more-from-kalypso</link>
      <description>The tracks are laid for great games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Introducing the Empires and Engines: Return to Tropico &amp; More Bundle from Kalypso Media! Step into Tropico 6, the city builder that blends political intrigue and humor into a bold new take on the island sim. Will you rule with compassion or an iron fist? The choices—and their consequences—are yours to make! Or climb aboard Railway Empire, the ultimate train sim featuring more than 40 meticulously detailed locomotives. Build and manage stations, maintain factories, expand your network, and much more! Pay what you want for a massive library of games, add-ons, and DLC—and help support Oceana with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGN Fan Fest 2025: Fall Edition</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/ign-fan-fest-2025-fall-edition</link>
      <description>Gear up for IGN Fan Fest!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get ready for the Fall Edition of IGN Fan Fest 2025 with our latest bundle of games celebrating all the new and upcoming releases at the event! Swash your buckles all over the Koronus Expanse of <em>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</em>. Help SpongeBob and Patrick repair the fabric of space-time in <em>SpongeBob SquarePants: The Cosmic Shake</em>—just in time for the upcoming sequel <em>Titans of the Tide</em>. Explore the mysterious world of <em>Koira</em> with a newfound puppy friend. Let your imagination run wild in the vehicular open world of <em>TerraTech</em>, become the greatest Predator of all in <em>Predator: Hunting Grounds</em>, and if you’ve ever wanted to get into train simulators, we’ve got the Free Starter Pack of <em>Train Sim World 6</em>, miles of route add-ons, and more! <br><br>Catch IGN Fan Fest 2025 October 15 live on IGN.com, YouTube, Steam, Facebook, twitch, and X starting at 9am PDT / 12pm EDT / 5pm BST. Celebrate the festivities in fashion and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>