<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 16:42:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Sid Meier Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/best-of-humble-bundle-sid-meier-collection</link>
      <description>Play Sid Meier’s greatest games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the outstanding games and worlds of legendary game designer Sid Meier with our latest epic games bundle! Sink your teeth into a massive collection of award-winning strategy games, highlighted by a massive discount code for 2025’s <em>Sid Meier’s Civilization VII</em>. Choose from a variety of civilizations and lead your people to prosperity across multiple installments, special editions, and add-ons from the <em>Sid Meier</em> universe like the <em>Settler’s Edition</em>, <em>Deluxe Edition</em>, and more! Start your adventure today and help support The Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RollerCoaster Tycoon Collection 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/roller-coaster-tycoon-collection-2026</link>
      <description>Your rides, your rules</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Build the theme park of your dreams with the complete collection of RollerCoaster Tycoon games! Whether you’re an experienced park proprietor or completely new to the series, this bundle of all five games invites you to dive right in! Or buckle up, as it were. Relive the glory days of <em>RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic</em>, see what’s new in each of the sequel games, and test the boundaries of park design in <em>RollerCoaster Tycoon Deluxe</em> and <em>RollerCoaster Tycoon World</em>. There’s so much to design, build, and explore in this series, so get the full package while you can and support Gold Star Gamers with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before August 13th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Cause Complete Collection 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/just-cause-complete-collection-2026</link>
      <description>Guns, grappling hooks, and great gameplay </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Let the bullets fly and the good times roll across four epic installments of Square Enix’s exhilarating and bombastic <em>Just Cause</em> franchise. Cause mayhem and destruction across the fictional lands of San Esperito, Panau, Medici, and Solis. Enhance your experience with a gigantic library of add-ons and DLC, featuring the <em>Just Cause 3 DLC: Air, Land & Sea Expansion Pass</em>, <em>Just Cause 2: Monster Truck DLC</em>, and more. Jump into the action-packed world of <em>Just Cause</em> and help support One Tree Planted when you purchase the complete collection from Humble Bundle.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before February 11th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garphill Game Expansions</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/garphill-game-expansions</link>
      <description>Your favorite Tabletop Board Games just got better</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re teaming up with Garphill Games to add new features, fresh adventures, and countless hours of fun to your favorite Tabletop Board Games. Gather your squad and fall in love with epic expansions like <em>Explorers of the North Sea: Rocks of Ruin</em>, <em>Architects of the West Kingdom: Works of Wonder</em>, <em>Paladins of the West Kingdom: City of Crowns</em>, and more. Pay what you want to have the very best expansions from Garphill Games shipped to your mailbox—and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase. Don’t miss out on our curated bundle of awesome Garphill Games—get the base games for your expansions before it’s gone, here.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garphill Games Core Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/garphill-games-core-games</link>
      <description>Garphill Games—arriving at your doorstep</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fill your shelves with the hottest Tabletop Board Games on the market. From the lands beyond the Black Sea and beyond—fight for glory, strength, and territory to claim victory in <em>Raiders of Scythia</em>. Be the quickest player to invent, test, and develop original contraptions within an 850 AD setting in <em>Inventors of the South Tigris</em>. Raise the kingdom of your wildest dreams and lead your people to poverty or prosperity in <em>Viscounts of the West Kingdom</em>. Pay what you want for the very best from Garphill Games and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Iceberg Hidden Gems Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/iceberg-hidden-gems-bundle</link>
      <description>Chill out with Iceberg</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Settle in for a cool beginning of 2026 with Iceberg Interactive’s Hidden Gems. Survey your capitalism kingdom, and strive to drive a profit as the <em>King of Retail</em>. Wield Gloom Girl’s <em>Doomblade</em> destroy the Dread Lords in an energetic 2D metroidvania. Or, live a pirate’s life on the PVP seas with <em>Blazing Sails</em>. Limitless adventures await across multiple genres, and every purchase benefits Doctors Without Borders/Médecins Sans Frontières! <br><br><span style="color: #EF9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem before February 6, 2027, at 11:00 PM Pacific Time.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Playful Platformers 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/playful-platformers-2026</link>
      <description>A platformer for every player</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A great platformer gets maximum entertainment out of a simple format: making your character run back and forth on a 2D track, collecting items, jumping over obstacles, and fighting enemies to achieve a goal. In this bundle, just in time for the holidays, you’ll get 9 of our favorite platformer games made to entertain every type of platformer player! Make the choice between holding down a literally cursed job or saving the world in the fun, existential <em>Peppered</em>. Help a cute little tanuki sprint through her dreams in the 3D SEGA Saturn-inspired <em>Lunistice</em>. There’s even more to enjoy in this great bundle, so get it now for the price of your choosing and help out TD Foundation with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Grapple Dogs: Cosmic Canines before August 4th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before February 4th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibrant Visual Novels</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/vibrant-visual-novels</link>
      <description>Vibrant stories with striking visuals </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a style="color:#EF9741"><strong>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences.</strong></a><br><br>Place yourself in the heat of the story with the all-new Vibrant Visual Novels Bundle of story-driven games. Play <em>The Expression Amrilato</em>, a stunning visual novel–style title centered around two young girls learning to understand each other on multiple levels. Or <em>Needy Streamer Overload</em>, the multi-ending story of a girl obsessed with becoming the biggest personality on social media and her willingness to do anything to succeed. Get these and more engrossing visual novel–style games for a price you choose and help support Charity: Water with your purchase. <br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before February 4th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D3 Waifus 4U</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/d3-waifus-4u</link>
      <description>Welcome 2026 with wonderful waifus</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a style="color:#EF9741"><strong>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences.</strong></a><br><br>Hotties and even hotter games—stay warm all winter with the D3 Waifus 4U Bundle! This collection has it all: play as a 21st-century, time-traveling teenage swordswoman tasked with saving the Sengoku period in <em>Samurai Maiden</em>. Bully enemies with bullets and leave the battlefield a bloody mess as certified waifu baddies in action-packed shooters like <em>Full Metal School Girl</em>, <em>Bullet Girls Phantasia</em>, and more. Find your waifu and help support Hello World when you shop with Humble Bundle.<br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 30th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Decked Out Collection: Great on Handheld</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/decked-out-collection-great-on-handheld</link>
      <description>On-the-go games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’re in the midst of travel planning for the new year (or just have a really long commute to and from work every day) you’re likely looking for some portable entertainment on the go. If games are what you’re looking for and you have a Steam Deck, we have good news for you: a bundle of great games you can take with you anywhere, that will transport you even further. Enjoy the best of ‘90s shooters with the delightfully retro skill-based action in <em>ULTRAKILL</em>. Slay or be slayed by hordes of the undead and survive the night in <em>Vampire Survivors</em>. Outrun the end of the world through multiple universes in <em>Haste</em>, and more! Take these games with you wherever you go, and support the American Cancer Society with every purchase at the price of your choice.<p style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 28th, 2027.</em></strong></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt: Showdown 1896 / Choice Essential DLC Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/hunt-showdown-1896-choice-essential-dlc-bundle</link>
      <description>The Hunt is on</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all crack-shots, butchering brutes, and handgun heathens—upgrade your <em>Hunt: Showdown 1896</em> experience with cosmetic content including playable Hunter and equipment skins. This addictively unforgiving extraction shooter drops players into a twisted offshoot of America’s Gilded Age, where unworldly monsters and rival hunters stand between you and a massive payday. Already own the base game from your January Humble Choice purchase? Even better! Save even more dough on the hottest DLC like <em>Fear the Reaper</em>, <em>Lonely Howl</em>, <em>Legends of the Bayou</em>, and much more. Pay what you want for endless hours of exhilarating gameplay and help support Special Effect.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before February 3rd, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Games Done Quick 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/awesome-games-done-quick-2026</link>
      <description>Gotta go fast</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re kicking off the new year right by partnering with Games Done Quick for their Awesome Games Done Quick fundraiser starting on January 4! If you want to test your skills against the expert speedrunners competing in the event, we’ve got all 10 games in one bundle! Inside you’ll find great games you can either zoom through or play at your own pace, like <em>Mika and the Witch’s Mountain</em>, a cozy game about a little witch who delivers packages to the residents of her small town. Or snag the <em>Shovel Knight</em> DLC <em>Shovel Knight: King of Cards</em> and help King Knight fight off enemies and win the ultimate card game. If horror games are more your speed (no pun intended), check out <em>F.E.A.R. 2: Project Origin</em> and escape the clutches of an experimental organization and a paranormal menace. Like Games Done Quick, we’re donating a portion of every bundle purchase to the Prevent Cancer Foundation. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Carnage Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/carnage-collection</link>
      <description>Total carnage, and totally fun</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The carnage is real, and so are the savings on the amazing games within The 2026 Carnage Collection. Los Angeles is a bloody mess—add a little more red to the mosaic in <em>Dead Island 2</em>, unleash absolute fury on your enemies in the action FPS <em>Trepang2</em>, traverse the post-apocalyptic wasteland looking for action on your coyote-carrying motorcycle in <em>Laika: Aged Through Blood</em>, and more. Play these and more carnage-filled adventures today when you shop with Humble Bundle.<p style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 21st, 2027.</em></strong></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>