<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 16:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Untold Tales&#39; Indie Roulette Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/untold-tales-indie-roulette-bundle</link>
      <description>Let the games begin!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want to spin the wheel and play Indie Roulette with our latest bundle! Get 10 unique titles—each completely different and fresh. Want to play a cozy game? We got <em>Everdream Valley</em>. Prefer a brutal top-down shooter? You're in for a treat with <em>The Hong Kong Massacre</em>. In the mood to relax with a round of golf? Look no further than <em>Golf Club Nostalgia</em>. We have every corner of the gaming spectrum covered! Let the games begin and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devil May Cry: Devil Trigger Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/devil-may-cry-devil-trigger-collection</link>
      <description>Blood will rain—demons will reign</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unleash your inner demon slayer with the Devil May Cry: Devil Trigger Collection! Dive into the fast-paced, over-the-top action of Capcom’s iconic <em>Devil May Cry</em> franchise—known for its slick combos, stylish weapons, and devilishly hunky leading men. Take on hordes of demons and towering bosses as Dante or Nero in <em>DMC 1–5</em>, including additional content and DLC. Whether you're a longtime fan or a newcomer, this enhanced collection is the ultimate way to experience the chaos. Pay what you want and help support Breakthrough T1D with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gear Up For Borderlands 4: Borderlands X Wonderlands Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/gear-up-for-borderlands-4-borderlands-x-wonderlands-bundle</link>
      <description>Insanity, guns, fun—it’s Borderlands</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into the chaotic world of Pandora with the Borderlands & Tiny Tina Bundle from Gearbox Software—one of the most stylish franchises in gaming history. A pioneer of the looter-shooter genre, the <em>Borderlands</em> series perfected the weapon-grind loop with addicting gunplay and over-the-top rewards—aka bigger, badder, crazier guns. Pay what you want and unlock <em>Tiny Tina's Wonderlands: Chaotic Great Edition</em>, <em>Borderlands 1–3</em>, <em>New Tales from the Borderlands</em>, and more. Get the ultimate <em>Borderlands</em> experience—and help support Covenant House with your purchase! Plus, get ready <em>Borderlands 4</em> coming out on September 12th.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 19:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humblecraft: RTS Rush</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/humblecraft-rts-rush</link>
      <description>Get tactical with RTS standouts</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Feel the rush of real-time strategy with this outstanding bundle of top-tier indie RTS titles! Build and command voxel-powered vehicles across sea and space in <em>From the Depths</em>. Defend your stronghold in classic medieval warfare with <em>Stronghold: Definitive Edition</em>. Engage in Cold War-era combat with intense 1v1 and 8v8 battles in <em>Men of War: Assault Squad 2</em>—and more. Challenge your tactical skills with great games and help support Xperience Studios with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>