<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:28:11 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Outright Games: Endless Fun Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/outright-games-endless-fun-bundle</link>
      <description>Endless fun awaits </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Spread some holiday cheer and smiles with the Outright Games: Endless Fun Bundle! Hilarious hijinks ensue as the mean one, Mr. Grinch, in <em>The Grinch: Christmas Adventures</em>. Explore the waters beneath the Land of Ooo with Finn, Jake, and the gang in <em>Adventure Time: Pirates of the Enchiridion</em>. Embark on an Earth-saving Eurotrip as Ben 10, everyone’s favorite teenage superhero, in <em>Ben 10 Power Trip</em>. Gather the family for an all-age gaming session and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 9th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games Under 5 Hours Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/games-under-5-hours-bundle</link>
      <description>Short and sweet</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[You’re finishing up your last-minute holiday prep and getting all your work done before you take some time off at the end of the year, and somehow you still find yourself with some free time here and there and don’t know quite how to spend it. If this sounds accurate, you’re probably going to love this bundle of short but sweet games you can finish in under five hours! Flex your puzzling skills and look at things from new angles with the full collection of <em>Monument Valley</em> games. Plan your co-op heist of the chic-est city in Western Europe in <em>Monaco 2</em>. Grow and mutate your alien body into new organs and weapons to fight off threats both human and extraterrestrial in <em>Moduwar</em>. There’s a lot more to explore in this bundle, so if you’re looking for some games that won’t be a total time suck, grab these while you can! A portion of every purchase goes to Save the Children, supporting children and families in need. <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 7, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Award Nominations Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/award-nominations-bundle-2025</link>
      <description>Award winners and nominees await</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gaming award season is around the corner—kick off the festivities with our curated bundle of award-nominated video games! Play the deeply story-driven and gorgeous indie RPG, <em>A Space for the Unbound</em>, the action-adventure/FPS fusion frenzy <em>Bright Memory: Infinite</em>, and the ghastly good time <em>Ghostrunner 2</em>. Create your own award-winning memories with friends, family, and great games—and help support charity when you shop with Humble Bundle!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 31st, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesome Snack 2025: Showcase Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wholesome-snack-2025-showcase-bundle</link>
      <description>Celebrate cozy season with Wholesome Snack</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="350" height="300" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kYwGSLM8lsQ?si=Y71Iftxi65ZM-KwS" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Now is the perfect time of year to snuggle up at home with a fun, cozy game or two. If that’s your vibe, we and our friends at Wholesome Snack have just the bundle for you! Dive into the perfectly pleasant games celebrating Wholesome Snack’s 2025 Showcase, like <em>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</em>, in which you assist Snufkin in protecting Moominvalley from an ambitious interloper. Or, send nice letters and swap compliments with your neighbors in <em>Kind Words 2 (lofi city pop)</em>. Build your ideal beach cottage or coastal mansion in <em>Summerhouse</em>, and your perfect garden in <em>Botany Manor</em>. Relax and unwind with this extra-wholesome bundle, and support the good work of the ACLU with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Shashingo: Learn Japanese with Photography and Snufkin keys before June 30th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before December 30th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upload VR Winter 2025 Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/upload-vr-winter-2025-bundle</link>
      <description>Escape reality with VR games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whether you just got your first VR headset and are ready for whatever the VR universe has to throw at you, or you’re an old hand looking to expand their collection of games, we’ve got a great bundle of post-apocalyptic adventures and hellish horrors inspired by UploadVR’s Winter Showcase! Descend deep into literal hell and fight off its most twisted demons in <em>Hellsweeper VR</em>. Survive the battlegrounds of <em>Ghosts of Tabor</em>. Puzzle your way out of the action-packed escape rooms of <em>I Expect You to Die 3: Cog in the Machine</em>. There’s so much more to enjoy in this VR bundle, so grab it while you can and support the digital privacy defenders at Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 26th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>