<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 23:30:09 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Nacon Motorsports: Drive &amp; Thrive</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/nacon-motorsports-drive-thrive</link>
      <description>Feel the exhilaration at your fingertips </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Experience the full-throttle games of Nacon Motorsports with our latest racing game bundle! This bursting bundle features some of the best racing games on the market with a wide variety of vehicle types and races. Tackle the dunes in your tricked-out buggy in <em>Overpass 2</em>. Lead the charge in our own Rally Car with <em>WRC Generations - The FIA WRC Official Game</em>. Ride on the edge of your motorcycle in <em>TT Isle of Man: Ride on the Edge 3</em>, and more—and help support The AbleGamers Charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter New Year Hunting Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/monster-hunter-new-year-hunting-collection</link>
      <description>The hunt is on in 2025</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’ve been waiting to get into the smash-hit <em>Monster Hunter</em>, this bundle is your golden opportunity. Get your hands on the two most recent <em>Monster Hunter</em> games, plus <em>both</em> of their critically acclaimed expansions. <em>Monster Hunter World</em> redefined the series when it launched in 2018, and its beloved expansion <em>Iceborne</em> introduced a host of awesome new beasts to hunt alongside plenty of game-changing systems. <em>Monster Hunter Rise</em> and the <em>Sunbreak</em> expansion doubled-down on <em>World</em>’s refinements, with an emphasis on exhilarating dog-riding and wirebug-zipping mobility. Pay what you want for the deluxe versions of both of these must-play games and their expansions, and help support Breakthrough T1D with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>