<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 08:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Return to Metroidvania</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/return-to-metroidvania</link>
      <description>Explore every inch of these deep games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore some great games keeping the Metroidvania genre thriving! Jump, shoot, and sneak your way through some amazing game worlds in our latest bundle! Our all-new Return to Metroidvania Bundle offers 8 modern search action titles that keep the genre’s spirit alive with compelling gameplay and endless replayability. Slay your foes with living weapons in <em>GRIME</em>, platform for your life in <em>Berserk Boy</em>, defeat microscopic viral threats in <em>BioGun</em>, and more—and help support Cool Effect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train Sim World® 5: Route Remix Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/train-sim-world-5-route-remix-bundle</link>
      <description>Feel the power of a locomotive</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into the conductor seat of the most realistic train simulator around with the new Train Sim World® 5: Route Remix Bundle. Gain access to new routes, new cosmetics, and new trains to keep the fun truckin’ along. This value-packed bundle starts with the <em>Train Sim World® 5: Starter Pack</em>, and includes the captivating DLCs <em>Antelope Valley Line</em> and <em>Cajon Pass</em>, and so much more. Pay what you want for the ultimate train sim experience, and help support Calm with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Lights</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/neon-lights</link>
      <description>The blinding light of great games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all cyberpunks, adrenaline junkies, and action seekers—our latest bundle has the buzzing lights, bursting action, and bad-ass gameplay you’re looking for. Become Ann: a highly-skilled combat-trained lone wolf on a personal mission in <em>ANNO: Mutationem</em>’s giant Metropolis, run 'n' gun your way through the frantic, roguelike action-platformer <em>Neon Abyss</em>, or solve mysteries in gripping futuristic noir shooter <em>Neon Blood</em>. Explore these and other great games and help support XPerience Studios with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armor Games Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/armor-games-bundle</link>
      <description>The very best from Armor Games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Indie developers aren’t bulletproof, but they sure are tough with the right armor. It’s time to feel the strength of the great games within our Armor Games Bundle. Dive into family-friendly choose-your-own-adventure fun with <em>Baladins</em>. Manipulate time with awesome RPG mechanics in <em>In Stars and Time</em>. Train to defeat an evil witch in <em>Swords & Souls:Neverseen</em>, and much more—plus, your purchase helps support the Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fellow Traveller Publisher Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/fellow-traveller-publisher-bundle</link>
      <description>Great indie games since 2011</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Indie games tell great stories—explore the narratively rich titles of Fellow Traveller publishing with our newest bundle! Since 2011, Fellow Travellers has championed smaller developers and their story-focused projects. Embark on an interplanetary adventure as the first robo reporter for the <em>Times & Galaxy</em>, the solar system's most trusted holopaper. Or play as a hardened captain of a polar expedition gone awry in <em>The Pale Beyond</em>. Get outstanding indie titles and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>