<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:31:55 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Stories from Latin America</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/stories-from-latin-america</link>
      <description>Juegos con sabor Latino</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Experience the best games with Latin American themes and stories in 10 fresh and exciting indie titles! Play despelote—the gorgeous Ecuadorian slice-of-life title that celebrates the magic of soccer, Enigma of Fear—the paranormal detective adventure where you help Mia search for her father, or Kulebra and the Souls of Limbo—an emotional tale of curses and the magic within. Try these and many more gripping Latino-inspired indie games, and help support Trees, Water & People with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lone Survivor Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/lone-survivor-bundle</link>
      <description>Fun times fighting for survival</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fight for your life—and have fun doing it—with the Lone Survivor Bundle. These action-packed titles deliver intensity, adrenaline, and suspense! Dominate all surrounding foes in <em>Conan Exiles</em>, an action-adventure set in the open-world lands of Conan the Barbarian. Don’t forget your gas mask in <em>Chernobylite Premium Edition</em>—the hyper-realistic, 3D-scanned survival sim of Chernobyl’s Exclusion Zone. Or prepare for ducking awesome PvP/PvE mayhem—as a mallard—in <em>DUCKSIDE</em>. Play these and more with the Lone Survivor Bundle, and help support Team Rubicon with your purchase.<p><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem Forager and State of Decay 2: Juggernaut Edition before April 15th, 2026. All other titles need be redeemed before Oct 15th, 2026.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remedy Games - 30th Anniversary Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/remedy-games-30th-anniversary-bundle</link>
      <description>We’ve got the Remedy for you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate 30 years of iconic titles from Remedy Entertainment with the latest Humble Games Bundle! Explore multiple award-winning titles that helped shape the history of gaming itself. Dare to explore the psychological survival  horror thriller, <em>Alan Wake 2 Deluxe Edition</em>, bend reality using superpowers to save your brother in the surreal modern classic, <em>Control Ultimate Edition</em>. Or slow time and let the bullets fly in the acclaimed <em>Max Payne</em> series. Remedy your boredom with truly outstanding games and help support Save the Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Critter Chaos Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/critter-chaos-bundle</link>
      <description>Cuteness—Critters—Chaos</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love cute critters and supporting budding indie games? The all-new Critter Chaos Bundle is perfect for gamers looking for fresh experiences! Embark on a unique critter-collecting journey with your friends online in <em>Temtem</em>. Help a lost little girl find her way home as a lovable monster in the heartwarming adventure <em>Meg's Monster</em>. Collect and fuse monsters using classic turn-based RPG mechanics in <em>Cassette Beasts</em>. Play these great titles and more—and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!</p> <p><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem TemTem and Farewell North before March 8th, 2026. All other titles need be redeemed before Oct 8th, 2026.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humbling Soulslike Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/humbling-soulslike-bundle</link>
      <description>Get good or be humbled</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Challenge your skills—and your sanity—with the Humbling Soulslike Bundle! Play <em>Enotria: The Last Song</em>, a soulslike set in a sunlit world inspired by Italian folklore where the brightest light casts the darkest shadow; <em>Flintlock: The Siege of Dawn</em>, an explosive souls-lite where gods and guns collide; and <em>Asterigos: Curse of the Stars</em>, a Roman mythology-inspired adventure full of danger and excitement. Pay what you want for addictively challenging games and help support the Starlight Children’s Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Phunky Physics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/phunky-physics</link>
      <description>Phunky Fresh Physics </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gravity is more of a suggestion than a law of nature in the all-new Phunky Physics Bundle. This collection of crazy physics-based titles from a few of our favorite publishers pushes the creative limits of gameplay. Risk your life in the cold void of space as a frigate salvage technician in <em>Hardspace: Shipbreaker</em>. Carve and slice spaceships to recover precious resources and pay off your enormous billion-dollar debt. Enjoy countless laughs at the expense of your army with the most inaccurate game physics ever in <em>Totally Accurate Battle Simulator</em>. Play these gravity-defying games and help support Cool Effect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Worlds Collide 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/lego-worlds-collide-2025</link>
      <description>A LEGO world for every interest </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re stacking up great games brick-by-brick with the all-new LEGO Worlds Collide Bundle! This gigantic bundle from Warner Bros. mixes your favorite franchises with the unmistakable LEGO charm to create unique gaming experiences that puts you in the shoes of your favorite characters. Play <em>LEGO® Star Wars™: The Skywalker Saga</em>, <em>LEGO® Marvel Super Heroes 2 Deluxe Edition</em>, <em>LEGO® Batman™ 3: Beyond Gotham Premium Edition</em>, and become the LEGO hero of legend! Pay what you want for the ultimate LEGO bundle, and help support Raiden Science Foundation with your purchase! <br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your key before March 24th. 2026.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Likes and Lites</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/indie-likes-and-lites</link>
      <description>The biggest little indie games </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve curated our hottest bundle of the summer with the coolest indie games around. Explore the action-packed puzzler from the hero that helped establish a genre with <em>Shovel Knight Pocket Dungeon</em>, try the addictive roguelite puzzle mashup <em>Let's! Revolution!</em>, or enjoy a satirical dungeon-crawler based on the monotony of modern life in <em>Going Under</em>, and much more. Fall in love with an unexpected indie game and help support World Central Kitchen with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>