<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 20:25:09 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>IGN Fan Fest 2025: Fall Edition</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/ign-fan-fest-2025-fall-edition</link>
      <description>Gear up for IGN Fan Fest!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get ready for the Fall Edition of IGN Fan Fest 2025 with our latest bundle of games celebrating all the new and upcoming releases at the event! Swash your buckles all over the Koronus Expanse of <em>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</em>. Help SpongeBob and Patrick repair the fabric of space-time in <em>SpongeBob SquarePants: The Cosmic Shake</em>—just in time for the upcoming sequel <em>Titans of the Tide</em>. Explore the mysterious world of <em>Koira</em> with a newfound puppy friend. Let your imagination run wild in the vehicular open world of <em>TerraTech</em>, become the greatest Predator of all in <em>Predator: Hunting Grounds</em>, and if you’ve ever wanted to get into train simulators, we’ve got the Free Starter Pack of <em>Train Sim World 6</em>, miles of route add-ons, and more! <br><br>Catch IGN Fan Fest 2025 October 15 live on IGN.com, YouTube, Steam, Facebook, twitch, and X starting at 9am PDT / 12pm EDT / 5pm BST. Celebrate the festivities in fashion and help support Code for America with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Avatar Legends 20th Anniversary Physical RPG Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/avatar-legends-20th-anniversary-physical-rpg-bundle</link>
      <description>Water. Earth. Fire. Air…TTRPGs</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Experience a cultural phenomenon in an all-new way from the comfort of your home with the Avatar Legends: 20th Anniversary Physical RPG Bundle by Magpie Games. Choose an elemental bending specialty, create an original character, gather your friends, and embark on adventures alongside beloved heroes like Katara, Toph, and Zuko. Get Avatar Legends: The Roleplaying Game shipped to you with an official dice set, GM screen, journal pack, cloth map, and Pai Sho tiles. Act fast—this Humble exclusive won’t last long! Pay what you want and help support the ACLU with your purchase.<br><br><strong><em><span style="color: #ef9741;">Limited Quantities Available!</span></em></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cosmic Mysteries &amp; Noir Realities</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/cosmic-mysteries-noir-realities</link>
      <description>Flex your detective skills</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Attention gumshoes, sleuths, and private eyes everywhere: we need your expert assistance on a few cases that caught our eye. Live out your noir detective and cozy mystery dreams with our latest bundle of mystery games, featuring everything from the surreal carnival at the heart of <em>Strangeland</em>, the folk horror delights of <em>The Excavation of Hob’s Barrow</em>, the unique zoological vision of <em>Chicken Police</em>, and more! Every purchase at the price of your choice helps to support the children of Make-A-Wish, some of whom may even have detective dreams of their own.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wired&#39;s Safe In Our World Anniversary Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wireds-safe-in-our-world-anniversary-bundle</link>
      <description>Wired Production’s hottest titles</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want for awesome indie standouts with the Wired Productions Publisher Bundle! Play inventive hits like Bulwark Evolution: Falconeer Chronicles—a genre-bending adventure where you can embrace chill construction mechanics or push for all-out map domination. Or jump into Gori: Cuddly Carnage—a fearless feline on a sentient hoverboard, teaming up with his A.I. buddy to take down the evil Adorable Army. Grab 10+ expressive indie games and help support Safe In Our World with your purchase today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Close Combat Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/close-combat-collection</link>
      <description>Fists and blades will fly</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ready to get your blood pumping? Sharpen your blades, steady your hands, and dive into the Close Combat Collection! Unleash stylish, aggressive combat in Dwarven Realms, the ultimate action RPG. Battle for survival in The Last Soldier of the Ming Dynasty, a grand adventure inspired by breathtaking traditional Chinese ink-painting landscapes. Try these great games and more including Ghostlore!  Get up close and personal with this exhilarating bundle—and help support the Breast Cancer Research Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WAAAGHtober! A Warhammer Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/waaaghtober-warhammer-bundle</link>
      <description>200+ hours of Warhammer games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[WAAAGH! War on an apocalyptic scale has arrived—how will you defend the Imperium? Gather your arms for the exciting Warhammer adventures within this action-packed bundle running throughout October! Sink your teeth into the very best from the Warhammer universe with brutal gunplay, blood-soaked narratives, and so much more. Bring glory to mankind as Captain Titus, a hardened hero tasked with retaking the Imperial Forge World from Orks in Warhammer 40,000: Space Marine - Anniversary Edition. Or test your tactical mettle in Warhammer 40,000: Battlesector, the turn-based strategy experience steeped in grimdark warfare.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stories from Latin America</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/stories-from-latin-america</link>
      <description>Juegos con sabor Latino</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Experience the best games with Latin American themes and stories in 10 fresh and exciting indie titles! Play despelote—the gorgeous Ecuadorian slice-of-life title that celebrates the magic of soccer, Enigma of Fear—the paranormal detective adventure where you help Mia search for her father, or Kulebra and the Souls of Limbo—an emotional tale of curses and the magic within. Try these and many more gripping Latino-inspired indie games, and help support Trees, Water &amp; People with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lone Survivor Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/lone-survivor-bundle</link>
      <description>Fun times fighting for survival</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fight for your life—and have fun doing it—with the Lone Survivor Bundle. These action-packed titles deliver intensity, adrenaline, and suspense! Dominate all surrounding foes in <em>Conan Exiles</em>, an action-adventure set in the open-world lands of Conan the Barbarian. Don’t forget your gas mask in <em>Chernobylite Premium Edition</em>—the hyper-realistic, 3D-scanned survival sim of Chernobyl’s Exclusion Zone. Or prepare for ducking awesome PvP/PvE mayhem—as a mallard—in <em>DUCKSIDE</em>. Play these and more with the Lone Survivor Bundle, and help support Team Rubicon with your purchase.<p><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem Forager and State of Decay 2: Juggernaut Edition before April 15th, 2026. All other titles need be redeemed before Oct 15th, 2026.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remedy Games - 30th Anniversary Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/remedy-games-30th-anniversary-bundle</link>
      <description>We’ve got the Remedy for you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate 30 years of iconic titles from Remedy Entertainment with the latest Humble Games Bundle! Explore multiple award-winning titles that helped shape the history of gaming itself. Dare to explore the psychological survival  horror thriller, <em>Alan Wake 2 Deluxe Edition</em>, bend reality using superpowers to save your brother in the surreal modern classic, <em>Control Ultimate Edition</em>. Or slow time and let the bullets fly in the acclaimed <em>Max Payne</em> series. Remedy your boredom with truly outstanding games and help support Save the Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>