<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Apr 2025 16:24:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Play for Miracles with Twin Sails Interactive</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/play-for-miracles-with-twin-sails-interactive</link>
      <description>Games ahoy from Twin Sails Interactive</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover all the amazing titles of Twin Sails Interactive with the Play for Miracles Bundle! Dive into a curated collection of acclaimed indie gems survival adventures, deep strategy, board games, and more. From the deep strategic management of Terraforming Mars, to the gripping survival challenge of Survival: Fountain of Youth, this bundle showcases 12 standout titles and their DLC from our superb lineup. Support great games and a great cause—your purchase helps benefit Children's Miracle Network Hospitals!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>id and Friends</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/id-and-friends</link>
      <description>Bullets, blood, and fun—from id Software</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bullets, blood, and fun—from id Software.</strong> Bullets, blood, and fun! Our latest bundle by id Software is an epic collection from iconic franchises with deep roots in the history of gaming—slay fascists in an alternate timeline in <em>Wolfenstein</em> and obliterate demons on Mars and in the <em>DOOM</em> series! Plus, get your shield ready with an exclusive coupon for the latest installment, <em>DOOM: The Dark Ages</em>, dropping in May. Play multiple installments from these mega franchises that range from old school to modern, like <em>DOOM (1993)</em> and <em>DOOM Eternal</em>.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Return to Metroidvania</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/return-to-metroidvania</link>
      <description>Explore every inch of these deep games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore some great games keeping the Metroidvania genre thriving! Jump, shoot, and sneak your way through some amazing game worlds in our latest bundle! Our all-new Return to Metroidvania Bundle offers 8 modern search action titles that keep the genre’s spirit alive with compelling gameplay and endless replayability. Slay your foes with living weapons in <em>GRIME</em>, platform for your life in <em>Berserk Boy</em>, defeat microscopic viral threats in <em>BioGun</em>, and more—and help support Cool Effect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Train Sim World® 5: Route Remix Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/train-sim-world-5-route-remix-bundle</link>
      <description>Feel the power of a locomotive</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into the conductor seat of the most realistic train simulator around with the new Train Sim World® 5: Route Remix Bundle. Gain access to new routes, new cosmetics, and new trains to keep the fun truckin’ along. This value-packed bundle starts with the <em>Train Sim World® 5: Starter Pack</em>, and includes the captivating DLCs <em>Antelope Valley Line</em> and <em>Cajon Pass</em>, and so much more. Pay what you want for the ultimate train sim experience, and help support Calm with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Lights</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/neon-lights</link>
      <description>The blinding light of great games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all cyberpunks, adrenaline junkies, and action seekers—our latest bundle has the buzzing lights, bursting action, and bad-ass gameplay you’re looking for. Become Ann: a highly-skilled combat-trained lone wolf on a personal mission in <em>ANNO: Mutationem</em>’s giant Metropolis, run 'n' gun your way through the frantic, roguelike action-platformer <em>Neon Abyss</em>, or solve mysteries in gripping futuristic noir shooter <em>Neon Blood</em>. Explore these and other great games and help support XPerience Studios with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>