<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2026 08:54:18 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Call of the Wild 9th Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/call-wild-9th-anniversary</link>
      <description>The most realistic hunting sim roaming these lands</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into the dynamic and realistic world of <em>theHunter: Call of the Wild</em> and experience a new level of hunting realism. This value-packed game bundle features a massive collection of add-ons and DLC. Hunt the rich Emerald Coast of Australia, the snowy peaks of the New England Mountains, and more. Take on alligators, lions, and other voracious predators and sell their pelts for supplies and coins. Pay what you want for the ultimate <em>theHunter: Call of the Wild</em> experience, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase! <br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before March 6th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwhelming Positive Games Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/overwhelming-positive-games-bundle</link>
      <description>Good vibes games for you </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Featuring games with over 500 reviews, and 95% approval rates, the Overwhelmingly Positive bundle is jam packed with crowd pleasers. Unleash your inner party monster alone or with friends in <em>Monster Prom 4: Monster Con</em>. Experience 2025’s unique, cult favorite, plinko-style roguelike <em>Nubby's Number Factory</em>. Craft your deck to hold back the hordes of baddies boarding the <em>Monster Train</em>, and so much more. Add certified bangers to your library and help support the It Gets Better Project all at the same time! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem before February 25, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love You to Death Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/love-you-to-death-bundle</link>
      <description>Our bloody Valentine&#39;s day gift to you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[February is the month of connection and romance, and there’s no better way to celebrate than with the horror games from our all-new Love You to Death Bundle! Try <em>Ghost Watchers</em>—the goosebump-inducing co-op ghost-hunting journey, <em>Have a Nice Death</em>—the adorably addicting action roguelike starring everyone’s favorite scythe-wielding bearer of death, <em>Iron Lung</em>—the claustrophobic journey through the bottom of a blood-filled alien ocean, and so much more. Find out what makes you scream and help support Coral Guardian with your purchase.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. All titles should be redeemed before March 4th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-Fi Shooters 2.0</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/scifi-shooters-bundle-2026</link>
      <description>Every flavor of sci-fi shooter</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Heat up the dark days of winter with a scorching-hot bundle of iconic shooters! Explore the frigid unknown of deep space in the genre-defining <em>System Shock 2: 25th Anniversary Remaster</em>, infiltrate the Galactic Empire as a covert Rebel Alliance operative in <em>Star Wars: Dark Forces Remaster</em>, and send hoards of demonic forces back to their fiery homeland in <em>DOOM Eternal</em>. Grab these rockin’ remasters of legendary sci-fi shooters—and support One Tree Planted and Cool Effect with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Battle Shapers, System Shock 2: 25th Anniversary Remaster, and STAR WARS: Dark Forces Remaster before August 20th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before February 20th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nacon Racing Collection 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/nacon-racing-collection</link>
      <description>Life in the fast lane</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Speed demons and Evel Knievels everywhere, we’ve got just the bundle for you! We’re partnering with Nacon for a collection of the publisher’s most high-octane racing simulator games that will launch you behind the wheel of the world’s fastest cars and most challenging courses, vetted by real-life professional drivers. Take a trip through the racing courses of past and present with <em>WRC 10</em>! Hop aboard your fastest bike and speed through over 200km of open-road in <em>TT Isle of Man: Ride on the Edge 3</em>! Test your mettle in the hyper-realistic rally simulation tracks of <em>WRC Generations</em>! If you’re always searching for the highest gear and living life in the fast lane, grab this bundle while you can and support SpecialEffect charity with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before February 18th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Cause Complete Collection 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/just-cause-complete-collection-2026</link>
      <description>Guns, grappling hooks, and great gameplay </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Let the bullets fly and the good times roll across four epic installments of Square Enix’s exhilarating and bombastic <em>Just Cause</em> franchise. Cause mayhem and destruction across the fictional lands of San Esperito, Panau, Medici, and Solis. Enhance your experience with a gigantic library of add-ons and DLC, featuring the <em>Just Cause 3 DLC: Air, Land & Sea Expansion Pass</em>, <em>Just Cause 2: Monster Truck DLC</em>, and more. Jump into the action-packed world of <em>Just Cause</em> and help support One Tree Planted when you purchase the complete collection from Humble Bundle.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before February 11th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>