<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 20:30:58 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Decked Out Collection: Great on Handheld</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/decked-out-collection-great-on-handheld</link>
      <description>On-the-go games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’re in the midst of travel planning for the new year (or just have a really long commute to and from work every day) you’re likely looking for some portable entertainment on the go. If games are what you’re looking for and you have a Steam Deck, we have good news for you: a bundle of great games you can take with you anywhere, that will transport you even further. Enjoy the best of ‘90s shooters with the delightfully retro skill-based action in <em>ULTRAKILL</em>. Slay or be slayed by hordes of the undead and survive the night in <em>Vampire Survivors</em>. Outrun the end of the world through multiple universes in <em>Haste</em>, and more! Take these games with you wherever you go, and support the American Cancer Society with every purchase at the price of your choice.<p style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 28th, 2027.</em></strong></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hunt: Showdown 1896 / Choice Essential DLC Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/hunt-showdown-1896-choice-essential-dlc-bundle</link>
      <description>The Hunt is on</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all crack-shots, butchering brutes, and handgun heathens—upgrade your <em>Hunt: Showdown 1896</em> experience with cosmetic content including playable Hunter and equipment skins. This addictively unforgiving extraction shooter drops players into a twisted offshoot of America’s Gilded Age, where unworldly monsters and rival hunters stand between you and a massive payday. Already own the base game from your January Humble Choice purchase? Even better! Save even more dough on the hottest DLC like <em>Fear the Reaper</em>, <em>Lonely Howl</em>, <em>Legends of the Bayou</em>, and much more. Pay what you want for endless hours of exhilarating gameplay and help support Special Effect.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before February 3rd, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awesome Games Done Quick 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/awesome-games-done-quick-2026</link>
      <description>Gotta go fast</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re kicking off the new year right by partnering with Games Done Quick for their Awesome Games Done Quick fundraiser starting on January 4! If you want to test your skills against the expert speedrunners competing in the event, we’ve got all 10 games in one bundle! Inside you’ll find great games you can either zoom through or play at your own pace, like <em>Mika and the Witch’s Mountain</em>, a cozy game about a little witch who delivers packages to the residents of her small town. Or snag the <em>Shovel Knight</em> DLC <em>Shovel Knight: King of Cards</em> and help King Knight fight off enemies and win the ultimate card game. If horror games are more your speed (no pun intended), check out <em>F.E.A.R. 2: Project Origin</em> and escape the clutches of an experimental organization and a paranormal menace. Like Games Done Quick, we’re donating a portion of every bundle purchase to the Prevent Cancer Foundation. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Carnage Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/carnage-collection</link>
      <description>Total carnage, and totally fun</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The carnage is real, and so are the savings on the amazing games within The 2026 Carnage Collection. Los Angeles is a bloody mess—add a little more red to the mosaic in <em>Dead Island 2</em>, unleash absolute fury on your enemies in the action FPS <em>Trepang2</em>, traverse the post-apocalyptic wasteland looking for action on your coyote-carrying motorcycle in <em>Laika: Aged Through Blood</em>, and more. Play these and more carnage-filled adventures today when you shop with Humble Bundle.<p style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 21st, 2027.</em></strong></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kalypso Strategy and Tactics Pack 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/kalypso-strategy-and-tactics-pack-2025</link>
      <description>Let’s get tactical </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Test your tactics and strategy with this awesome bundle of brain-teasing games from Kalypso Media! Prepare for the ultimate <em>Disciples: Liberation</em> experience, including the <em>Paths to Madness</em> expansion. The <em>Disciples</em> series is a fan-favorite dark fantasy strategy RPG featuring turn-based combat, rich lore, and mature themes—and the additional content only deepens the mystery of the lands of Nevendaar. Or put your decision-making skills to the test with the electrifying, addictive wartime RTS <em>Commandos 3 - HD Remaster</em>. Play these great games from Kalypso Media and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase! <br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your key before January 16th. 2027.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outright Games: Endless Fun Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/outright-games-endless-fun-bundle</link>
      <description>Endless fun awaits </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Spread some holiday cheer and smiles with the Outright Games: Endless Fun Bundle! Hilarious hijinks ensue as the mean one, Mr. Grinch, in <em>The Grinch: Christmas Adventures</em>. Explore the waters beneath the Land of Ooo with Finn, Jake, and the gang in <em>Adventure Time: Pirates of the Enchiridion</em>. Embark on an Earth-saving Eurotrip as Ben 10, everyone’s favorite teenage superhero, in <em>Ben 10 Power Trip</em>. Gather the family for an all-age gaming session and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 9th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Games Under 5 Hours Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/games-under-5-hours-bundle</link>
      <description>Short and sweet</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[You’re finishing up your last-minute holiday prep and getting all your work done before you take some time off at the end of the year, and somehow you still find yourself with some free time here and there and don’t know quite how to spend it. If this sounds accurate, you’re probably going to love this bundle of short but sweet games you can finish in under five hours! Flex your puzzling skills and look at things from new angles with the full collection of <em>Monument Valley</em> games. Plan your co-op heist of the chic-est city in Western Europe in <em>Monaco 2</em>. Grow and mutate your alien body into new organs and weapons to fight off threats both human and extraterrestrial in <em>Moduwar</em>. There’s a lot more to explore in this bundle, so if you’re looking for some games that won’t be a total time suck, grab these while you can! A portion of every purchase goes to Save the Children, supporting children and families in need. <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 7, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>