<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 22:08:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Upload VR Summer 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/upload-vr-summer-2025</link>
      <description>Dive into a new reality with VR</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want to start your VR gaming journey with our latest bundle of immersive titles! Step into the boots of a master swordsman and experience intense, physics-based combat in <em>Until You Fall</em>. Then dive into the mind-bending world of <em>Vertigo 2</em> as you uncover the mysteries of a quantum reactor teeming with aliens, rogue robots, and deadly fauna. Play these standout VR games and more—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the mental health advocates at Safe In Our World.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2K Classic Trilogies: Mafia X Bioshock</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/2k-classic-trilogies-mafia-x-bioshock</link>
      <description>Feel the rapture of crime and control </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Nostalgic for cinematic masterpiece games? Then you need the 2K Classic Trilogies: Mafia X Bioshock Bundle! Go from cabdriver to mob boss in the complete <em>Mafia I–III</em>, and uncover the truth behind genetic weaponry with the definitive <em>Bioshock</em> trilogy. Pay what you want for the ultimate <em>Mafia</em> and <em>Bioshock</em> collection and experience true 2000s gaming bliss. Run the city or save the city—plus, your purchase helps support the charity Covenant House! <br/><br/> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>Note: One&nbsp;key for Bioshock: The Collection and one key for Mafia Trilogy.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Serenity Forge Storyteller&#39;s Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/serenity-forge-storytellers-bundle</link>
      <description>Indie games that make an impact</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Great games come in all shapes and sizes—pay what you want and explore the inventive library of indie developer and publisher Serenity Forge with our latest bundle! The pros at Serenity Forge are master storytellers, supporting exceptional titles that move your soul like <em>Arcadian Atlas</em>, <em>Long Gone Days</em>, <em>Virgo Versus the Zodiac</em>, and more. Play meaningful and impactful games that challenge the way you think, and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospital of Colorado today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>June Tunes</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/june-tunes</link>
      <description>Rhythm &amp; groove in gaming</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fans of music and games—say hi to the June Tunes Bundle! This collection perfectly blends everything you love about music and gaming to deliver fun and unique gameplay experiences. Remix tracks from popular artists like Marshmello, Porter Robinson, and Yukika in <em>DJ Max Respect V</em>, keep the rhythm with a single button in <em>One Btn Bosses</em>, and follow the beat to defeat enemies in <em>Rhythm Fighter</em>. Play great rhythm games and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Puzzle Pizzazz Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/puzzle-pizzazz-bundle</link>
      <description>Brain melting &amp; bending puzzles</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Who doesn’t love a little mental gymnastics? Play the latest and greatest puzzle games with our latest bundle! Dive into a throwback, retro-inspired, point-and-click adventure with stylized pixel art in <em>The Abandoned Planet</em>, lose yourself in a story-rich puzzle adventure built around photography with <em>The Star Named EOS</em>, and so much more! Get the all-new Puzzle Pizzazz Bundle today and help support The Trevor Project with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case &amp; Consequence Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/case-and-consequence-collection</link>
      <description>Play marquee mystery &amp; thriller titles</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Put on your thinking caps, gather clues, and solve mysteries from the humid lowlands of the swamp to the depths of space with the Case &amp; Consequence Collection. Experience a wide range of settings and situations—embark on an Ace Attorney-like detective adventure in <em>Murders on the Yangtze River</em>, play as a literal clue-collecting alligator in <em>BROK the InvestiGator</em>, or go the sci-fi detective route in <em>Between Horizons</em>. Pay what you want and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Narrative Arc Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/narrative-arc-bundle</link>
      <description>Lose yourself in great game storytelling</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The core beauty of video games lies in their ability to emotionally connect with players through gripping narratives, and our latest bundle celebrates games with beautiful storytelling. Explore themes of hope, love, and friendship in <em>Dustborn</em>, experience a standalone survival storybook that blends interactive fiction with turn-based strategy in <em>Six Ages 2: Lights Going Out</em>, and ride, record, meet people, and unravel the strange world around you in <em>SEASON: A letter to the future</em>—and more. Pay what you want and help support the It Gets Better Project with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Up Pride</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/power-up-pride</link>
      <description>Equality in gaming—equality for all</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate PRIDE all month long with the all-new Power Up PRIDE Bundle! This curated collection features amazing games that positively portray LGBTQIA+ themes and characters. On top of that, these titles are a lot of fun to play. Dive into great games like <em>Heart of the Woods</em>, <em>Kindred Spirits</em>, <em>Echoes of the Plum Grove</em>, and more. Pay what you want and help support Xperience Studios with your purchase! <br/><br/>Kindred Spirits On The Roof is intended for mature audiences. Themes include partial nudity, suggestive situations and themes, as well as references to sexual acts in casual conversation for comedic effect. This game contains no explicit sexual or pornographic content, and all characters depicted are above the age of 18. User discretion is advised.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>