<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:34:08 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>LEGO Worlds Collide 2025 Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/lego-worlds-collide-2025-encore</link>
      <description>A LEGO world for every interest </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re stacking up great games brick-by-brick with the all-new LEGO Worlds Collide Bundle! This gigantic bundle from Warner Bros. mixes your favorite franchises with the unmistakable LEGO charm to create unique gaming experiences that puts you in the shoes of your favorite characters. Play <em>LEGO® Star Wars™: The Skywalker Saga</em>, <em>LEGO® Marvel Super Heroes 2 Deluxe Edition</em>, <em>LEGO® Batman™ 3: Beyond Gotham Premium Edition</em>, and become the LEGO hero of legend! Pay what you want for the ultimate LEGO bundle, and help support Raiden Science Foundation with your purchase! <br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your key before June 18th. 2026.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humbling Soulslike Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/humbling-soulslike-bundle-encore</link>
      <description>Get good or be humbled</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Challenge your skills—and your sanity—with the Humbling Soulslike Bundle! Play <em>Enotria: The Last Song</em>, a soulslike set in a sunlit world inspired by Italian folklore where the brightest light casts the darkest shadow; <em>Flintlock: The Siege of Dawn</em>, an explosive souls-lite where gods and guns collide; and <em>Asterigos: Curse of the Stars</em>, a Roman mythology-inspired adventure full of danger and excitement. Pay what you want for addictively challenging games and help support the Starlight Children’s Foundation with your purchase.<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your key before December 17th. 2026. Flintlock: the Siege of Dawn - Deluxe Edition will expire on June 17th, 2026.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Award Nominations Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/award-nominations-bundle-2025</link>
      <description>Award winners and nominees await</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gaming award season is around the corner—kick off the festivities with our curated bundle of award-nominated video games! Play the deeply story-driven and gorgeous indie RPG, <em>A Space for the Unbound</em>, the action-adventure/FPS fusion frenzy <em>Bright Memory: Infinite</em>, and the ghastly good time <em>Ghostrunner 2</em>. Create your own award-winning memories with friends, family, and great games—and help support charity when you shop with Humble Bundle!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 31st, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wholesome Snack 2025: Showcase Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wholesome-snack-2025-showcase-bundle</link>
      <description>Celebrate cozy season with Wholesome Snack</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="350" height="300" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/kYwGSLM8lsQ?si=Y71Iftxi65ZM-KwS" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Now is the perfect time of year to snuggle up at home with a fun, cozy game or two. If that’s your vibe, we and our friends at Wholesome Snack have just the bundle for you! Dive into the perfectly pleasant games celebrating Wholesome Snack’s 2025 Showcase, like <em>Snufkin: Melody of Moominvalley</em>, in which you assist Snufkin in protecting Moominvalley from an ambitious interloper. Or, send nice letters and swap compliments with your neighbors in <em>Kind Words 2 (lofi city pop)</em>. Build your ideal beach cottage or coastal mansion in <em>Summerhouse</em>, and your perfect garden in <em>Botany Manor</em>. Relax and unwind with this extra-wholesome bundle, and support the good work of the ACLU with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Shashingo: Learn Japanese with Photography and Snufkin keys before June 30th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before December 30th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Upload VR Winter 2025 Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/upload-vr-winter-2025-bundle</link>
      <description>Escape reality with VR games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whether you just got your first VR headset and are ready for whatever the VR universe has to throw at you, or you’re an old hand looking to expand their collection of games, we’ve got a great bundle of post-apocalyptic adventures and hellish horrors inspired by UploadVR’s Winter Showcase! Descend deep into literal hell and fight off its most twisted demons in <em>Hellsweeper VR</em>. Survive the battlegrounds of <em>Ghosts of Tabor</em>. Puzzle your way out of the action-packed escape rooms of <em>I Expect You to Die 3: Cog in the Machine</em>. There’s so much more to enjoy in this VR bundle, so grab it while you can and support the digital privacy defenders at Electronic Frontier Foundation with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 26th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rawfury: Rawcember to Remember 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/rawfury-rawcember-to-remember-2025</link>
      <description>RAWcember to Remember with a vengeance</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Ho ho hooray for epic savings—get into the holiday spirit with a curated collection of unique and exciting indie games! Play awesome indie titles like the addicting puzzle-platformer, <em>American Arcadia</em>; the point-and-click thriller, <em>Kathy Rain 2: Soothsayer</em>; the retro-inspired RPG adventure, <em>SKALD: Against the Black Priory</em>; and more with Raw Fury’s RAWcember to Remember Bundle. Experience new games and help support Save the Children with your purchase when you game with Humble Bundle!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before June 24th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Little Pony: Adventures in Equestria Deck-Building Game Physical Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/my-little-pony-adventures-in-equestria-deckbuilding-game-physical-bundle</link>
      <description>Friendship is magic</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gallop through the land of Equestria in the <em>My Little Pony: Adventures in Equestria</em> deck-building game, now available along with multiple expansions all in one convenient bundle! Choose your pony, gather your pals, and complete challenges to build up your deck and help out the residents of Ponyville. This bundle also includes the <em>Princess Pageantry</em> expansion, the <em>True Talents</em> expansion, the Meeple Pack, and more! Every purchase at the price of your choice helps end childhood hunger with No Kid Hungry.<br><br><strong><em><span style="color: #ef9741;">Limited Quantities Available!</span></em></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Maximum Entertainment: Full Send Bundle!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/maximum-entertainment-full-send-bundle</link>
      <description>Explore unique worlds, play great games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into whole universes of immersive storytelling and gameplay with this bundle of all the great stuff from Maximum Entertainment! Battle the dangerous gangs of post-apocalypse New York City in <em>Double Dragon</em> prequel <em>Double Dragon Gaiden: Rise of the Dragons</em>. Solve a series of puzzles and try to keep your head in the psychological horror game <em>In Sound Mind</em>. Traverse a dangerous world inspired by Nordic folktales in <em>Bramble: The Mountain King</em>. There’s way more to enjoy in this immersive bundle, so claim it now at the price of your choice, and support the global reforestation efforts of One Tree Planted!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before June 26th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Worms 30th Anniversary Celebration</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/worms-30th-anniversary-celebration</link>
      <description>Happy Wormiversary!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get your hands on some high-octane invertebrate action with this bundle of Worms games! In celebration of the irreverent artillery tactics series’ 30th anniversary, we’ve got 12 Worms classics and fan favorites together in a single collection meant for mega-fans and newcomers alike. Go back to the series’ roots with the 1990s charms of the original Worms and Worms Armageddon, and chart the series’ evolution with newer games like the 3D action of Worms Ultimate Mayhem and the arena-based cross-platform combat of Worms Rumble! Shoot and slither your way to the top of the worm pile with this bundle, available for the price of your choosing, and support One Tree Planted with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before December 17th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>