<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 22:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE COLLECTION</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/earth-defense-force-collection</link>
      <description>The least serious defense force ever</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Halt an evil invasion and save the world in <em>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE</em>. Our newest bundle features an amazing collection of <em>EDF</em> titles like <em>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE: WORLD BROTHERS 2</em>, <em>EDF 4</em>, and <em>EDF 5</em>, alongside a massive collection of bonus content like additional missions, cosmetics, and characters. These awesome arcade shooters are quick with the action and heavy on the charm—defeat the Ravagers and laugh along the way!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humble Heroines 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/humble-heroines-2025</link>
      <description>Celebrate kick-ass female protagonists </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate Women's History Month with Humble Heroines: Rebels, Curses, and Mystery. Take charge as powerful protagonists including Seelah from <em>Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous - Enhanced Edition</em>, Jesse Faden from <em>Control: Ultimate Edition</em>, and Fury from <em>Darksiders 3</em>!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeroCraft PC Complete</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/herocraft-pc-complete</link>
      <description>HeroCraft—championing the indie scene</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Great games come in a variety of sizes and from every corner of the globe—jump into the creative and imaginative worlds of beloved international studio, HeroCraft with our latest value-packed game bundle. Get hot titles like <em>Temptest</em>, <em>Gravewood High</em>, <em>Revival: Recolonization</em>, and much more. Pay what you want for the ultimate HeroCraft experience, help uplift indie developers, and support Care.org with your purchase. Explore the unknown and pick up an indie game today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fulqrum Publishing Spring Break</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/fulqrum-publishing-spring-break</link>
      <description>Freaky fun times with Fulqrum Publishing</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the games of epic international devs, Fulqrum Publishing with our newest bundle of great titles. This collection brings the heat—survive a moody Lovecraftian FPS world in <em>Forgive Me Father</em>. Get tactical with a fantasy setting and engaging RPG mechanics in <em>Fell Seal: Arbiter's Mark</em>. Embrace the darkness with the retro inspired RPG <em>Stygian: Reign of the Old Ones</em>. Play great games and help support nPower and The Global Foodbanking Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>