<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 08:27:30 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Dice and Destiny</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/dice-and-destiny</link>
      <description>A love letter to CRPGs</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[It’s time to fire up your computer, open a chat with your friends, and set off on some amazing CRPG adventures. Our latest bundle offers amazing titles that will spark your love for RPGs with their throwback-inspired gameplay elements and experiences. Explore the lands of acclaimed titles like <em>Disco Elysium</em>, and <em>Citizen Sleeper</em>. This curated collection of games is perfect for CRPG veterans and gamers looking to expand their field of interest. Play great games and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactical Triumph</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/tactical-triumph</link>
      <description>Let’s get tactical </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Challenge and strategy—what more could you want in a game? Dive into the Tactical Triumph Bundle and see if you have what it takes to conquer these great titles. Embark on an epic journey across the land of Caelum one tile at a time in <em>The Iron Oath</em>. Master magic with the perfect mix of tactical team-based combat and deck building in <em>Abalon</em>. Tame monsters and explore dungeons with precision in <em>Siralim Ultimate</em>. Try new and tactical titles plus help support buildOn with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leisure Suit Larry Complete Collection Bundle 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/leisure-suit-larry-complete-collection-bundle-2025</link>
      <description>Three decades of Larry adventures</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take a trip down leisure lane with luckless “lovable loser” Larry Laffer in this decades-spanning collection of games from the legendary adult-themed Leisure Suit Larry series, and relive an era when graphic adventures ruled PC gaming. This bundle includes original games in the series dating back to the ’80s, along with the latest entries that bring Larry’s escapades into the 21st century. Support the charity of your choice when you pick up this bundle!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE COLLECTION</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/earth-defense-force-collection</link>
      <description>The least serious defense force ever</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Halt an evil invasion and save the world in <em>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE</em>. Our newest bundle features an amazing collection of <em>EDF</em> titles like <em>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE: WORLD BROTHERS 2</em>, <em>EDF 4</em>, and <em>EDF 5</em>, alongside a massive collection of bonus content like additional missions, cosmetics, and characters. These awesome arcade shooters are quick with the action and heavy on the charm—defeat the Ravagers and laugh along the way!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humble Heroines 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/humble-heroines-2025</link>
      <description>Celebrate kick-ass female protagonists </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate Women's History Month with Humble Heroines: Rebels, Curses, and Mystery. Take charge as powerful protagonists including Seelah from <em>Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous - Enhanced Edition</em>, Jesse Faden from <em>Control: Ultimate Edition</em>, and Fury from <em>Darksiders 3</em>!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HeroCraft PC Complete</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/herocraft-pc-complete</link>
      <description>HeroCraft—championing the indie scene</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Great games come in a variety of sizes and from every corner of the globe—jump into the creative and imaginative worlds of beloved international studio, HeroCraft with our latest value-packed game bundle. Get hot titles like <em>Temptest</em>, <em>Gravewood High</em>, <em>Revival: Recolonization</em>, and much more. Pay what you want for the ultimate HeroCraft experience, help uplift indie developers, and support Care.org with your purchase. Explore the unknown and pick up an indie game today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fulqrum Publishing Spring Break</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/fulqrum-publishing-spring-break</link>
      <description>Freaky fun times with Fulqrum Publishing</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the games of epic international devs, Fulqrum Publishing with our newest bundle of great titles. This collection brings the heat—survive a moody Lovecraftian FPS world in <em>Forgive Me Father</em>. Get tactical with a fantasy setting and engaging RPG mechanics in <em>Fell Seal: Arbiter's Mark</em>. Embrace the darkness with the retro inspired RPG <em>Stygian: Reign of the Old Ones</em>. Play great games and help support nPower and The Global Foodbanking Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>