<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 17:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Game Favorites</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/indieio-single-publisher-bundle</link>
      <description>Unmissable indie games await </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add a splash of color to your game library with vibrant indie titles from&nbsp;indie game publishing and management platform&nbsp;indie.io! Cultivate the life you want in the cozy farming sim Echoes of the Plum Grove, travel to the purrfectly adorable town of Caterwaul Way to manage and rejuvenate your grandmother’s café in Cat Cafe Manager, and explore even more colorful worlds with this rich and diverse collection of indie favorites. Pay what you want for great games and help support Humble Bundle’s Xperience Studios with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Board Game All Stars by Renegade Game Studios</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/board-game-all-stars-renegade-game-studios</link>
      <description>The ultimate board game bonanza</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather the gang—it’s game night at your place! Pay what you want to get an awesome assortment of board games by Renegade Game Studios shipped directly to you! Roll the dice of fate and choose from <em>World's Fair 1893</em>, <em>The Search for UAPs</em>, <em>Dead Men Tell No Tales</em>, and more! Put on a grand exhibit for all to see or uncover the mysteries of the cosmos—play the hottest games Renegade has to offer and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!<br><br><strong><em><span style="color: #ef9741;">Limited Quantities Available!</span></em></strong>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frogwares: Lovecraft and Sherlock Classics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/frogwares-lovecraft-and-sherlock-classics</link>
      <description>Monsters and mysteries await</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Step into horror and mystery’s greatest minds: cosmic terror master H.P. Lovecraft and Sir Arthur Conan Doyle’s legendary detective Sherlock Holmes. Our latest bundle contains the very best from the gamemakers at Frogwares to satisfy your most eldritch cravings. Survive the supernaturally haunted New England town at the heart of <em>The Sinking City Remastered</em>. Hone your investigative skills by discovering the secrets behind the death of Sherlock Holmes’ mother in <em>Sherlock Holmes: Chapter One</em>. Solve the mystery of the Cthulhu mythos once and for all in the Lovecraft and Sherlock crossover <em>Sherlock Holmes The Awakened</em>. All this and much more for the price of your choosing, and all purchases help benefit the Malala Fund, supporting education for girls everywhere.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Telltale Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/telltale-collection</link>
      <description>Captivating storytelling meets amazing gameplay</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore captivating renditions of your favorite franchises with our Telltale Collection. Create your own adventures set within the worlds of <em>Batman</em>, <em>The Walking Dead</em>, <em>The Expanse</em>, and more. The Telltale Collection features iconic titles like <em>The Expanse: A Telltale Series</em>, <em>The Walking Dead: Season 1 &amp; 400 Days</em>, and <em>Batman: The Enemy Within</em>. Lose yourself in Telltale Games’ signature choose-your-own-adventure style today and help support Save The Children with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monster Hunter Series Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/monster-hunter-fall-hunting-collection</link>
      <description>CAPCOM’s Monster Hunter is back</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[If you’ve been waiting to get into the smash-hit <em>Monster Hunter</em>, this bundle is your golden opportunity! Vanquish voracious monsters with unique ecologies in <em>Monster Hunter Rise</em> and marvel at their breathtaking visuals. <em>Monster Hunter: World</em> redefined the series when it launched in 2018, and its beloved expansion, <em>Iceborne</em>, introduced a host of awesome new beasts to hunt alongside plenty of game-changing systems. Get these great titles and more from CAPCOM’s flagship action franchise, and help support Breakthrough T1D with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Devil May Cry: Devil Trigger Enhanced Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/devil-may-cry-devil-trigger-enhanced-collection</link>
      <description>To Hell and back</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hell is empty, and all the devils are…in this bundle! All the <em>Devil May Cry</em> games, that is. That’s right, we’ve got the whole <em>Devil May Cry</em> series for the low, low price of your choosing in one bundle! Go back to where it all started with the original stylish action of <em>Devil May Cry</em>. Play the sequel and the prequel included in the <em>Devil May Cry HD Collection</em> of the first three games. Follow Dante and his new buddy Nero as they battle the demons and monsters of the Special Edition of  <em>Devil May Cry 4</em> and the Deluxe Version of <em>Devil May Cry 5</em>. The ultimate <em>Devil May Cry</em> experience for the price of your choice, and every descent into the inferno supports the good folks at Children's Miracle Network charity!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Horror Icons Showcase</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/horror-icons-showcase</link>
      <description>Horror games fit for fall</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t fear what crawls in the night—attack it head-on with weapons blazing! Feel the adrenaline rush of great horror games with a Halloween-approved bundle. Experience animated thrills in <em>Bendy: Lone Wolf</em>—a cartoon-inspired and haunting Roguelike adventure through the halls of the world’s most evil animation studio and expolore a new career in the eerily accurate <em>The Mortuary Assistant - Definitive Edition</em>. Plus, we're adding a mysterious hit title in November! Feel the chills all season long and support Girls Who Code with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armor Games: The Retro &amp; Reborn Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/armor-games-the-retro-and-reborn-collection</link>
      <description>From Armor with love</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Start new adventures with the very best games from Armor Games Studios. Play <em>The Last Stand: Aftermath</em>—the zombie survival rogue-lite where you race against the clock to help as many survivors as possible before you turn. Your journey begins once you’ve been bitten—isn’t that a twist? Or dive into the <em>Swords & Souls: Legacy Collection</em>, a five-piece nugget of hilarious games packed with hack-and-slash hijinks and more. Get the coolest collection of indie games from Armor Games Studios, and help support Children’s Miracle Network!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indie Fears Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/indie-fears-bundle</link>
      <description>Indie thrills and chills</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get into the spooky season with this new bundle of the creepiest indie games around! Discover what all the fuss is about with the much-memed space-set nightmare fuel game <em>Mouthwashing</em>. Keep a mystery train running and try not to run out of oxygen on the steep mountain slopes of <em>Threshold</em>. Flip burgers and keep your customers satisfied in the spooky cooking simulator send-up <em>Kiosk</em>. Those aren’t even the tip of the horror game iceberg featured in this bundle, so name your price and help support SpecialEffect charity with your purchase. And maybe keep a light on while you play. You never know.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microids Mega Mix 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/microids-mega-mix-2025</link>
      <description>Meet the Microids Mega Mix</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Make room for an all-new Mega Bundle from Microids! This collection of 20+ games offers the very best in RPGs, adventure, and family-friendly fun that everyone can enjoy. Lose yourself across 32 wacky and hilarious levels in Garfield Lasagna Party, uncover your true identity through exploration in Syberia 1–3, and gather the gang for a rockin’ good time in The Smurfs – Village Party! Pay what you want for an amazing assortment of games and help support charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom: 10th Anniversary Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/kingdom-10th-anniversary-bundle</link>
      <description>Create your Kingdom</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into the pixelated worlds of Kingdom on the series’ 10th Anniversary with this bundle chock-full of Kingdom games! Ride your noble steed to defend your lands from the Greed in <em>Kingdom Two Crowns</em>, and try out multiple expansions inspired by different settings, like <em>Call of Olympus</em> and <em>Norse Lands</em>. Experience where it all started in <em>Kingdom: New Lands</em>, and get even more retro with it in <em>Kingdom Eighties</em>. Pay what you want to become the monarch of your dreams, and your purchase supports the humanitarian aid work at Team Rubicon USA.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bandai Namco - Dark Pictures &amp; Little Nightmares Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/bandai-namco-dark-pictures-little-nightmares-bundle</link>
      <description>Big scares—bigger savings</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Even a bat could see these savings—transform your home library into something supernatural with horror games by BANDAI NAMCO! Test your nerve and skills with fantastically haunting titles like Little Nightmares I &amp; II, the eerie adventures of a young boy and girl trapped in a nightmarish world, and The Dark Pictures Anthology: The Devil in Me, a chilling tale of documentarians exploring a haunted castle. Kick off Halloween with frighteningly good deals and help support Whale and Dolphin Conservation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>