<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jun 2025 08:27:28 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Power Up Pride</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/power-up-pride</link>
      <description>Equality in gaming—equality for all</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Celebrate PRIDE all month long with the all-new Power Up PRIDE Bundle! This curated collection features amazing games that positively portray LGBTQIA+ themes and characters. On top of that, these titles are a lot of fun to play. Dive into great games like <em>Heart of the Woods</em>, <em>Kindred Spirits</em>, <em>Echoes of the Plum Grove</em>, and more. Pay what you want and help support Xperience Studios with your purchase!<br/><br/>Kindred Spirits On The Roof is intended for mature audiences. Themes include partial nudity, suggestive situations and themes, as well as references to sexual acts in casual conversation for comedic effect. This game contains no explicit sexual or pornographic content, and all characters depicted are above the age of 18. User discretion is advised.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Badass Brawlers</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/badass-brawlers</link>
      <description>A bundle of Badass Brawlers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Challenge yourself and show your friends who's boss with the all-new Badass Brawlers Bundle! Experience a retro classic with a fresh coat of paint in <em>Double Dragon Neon</em>, dive into an all-new beat-’em-up adventure in <em>River City Girls 2</em>, suplex skyscraper-sized Kaiju in <em>Dawn of the Monsters</em>, and more. Play badass brawlers with our latest game bundle and help support SpecialEffect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stomp &amp; Chomp Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/stomp-chomp-bundle</link>
      <description>Dinosaur games galore!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Everyone loves dinosaurs—stomp and chomp your way through our latest games bundle and see what made these alpha predators so popular. This hot collection offers a diverse range of titles—complete the thrilling Turok Trilogy with improved visuals in <em>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion Remastered</em>, manage a cute community of cozy dinosaurs in <em>Amber Isle</em>, survive a dino-packed horror experience in <em>Fossilfuel 2</em>, and more. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support buildOn!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team 17: Chains of Command</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/team-17-chains-command</link>
      <description>Hot games from across the pond</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We love indie devs and you should too—explore a corner of Team 17’s awesome games library with our latest bundle! Experience the chaos and devastation of World War II as a hyper-realist FPS in <em>Hell Let Loose</em>, master <em>Thymesia’s</em> gruelling fast-paced combat, and become the monarch in the raucous party game <em>King of the Castle</em>. Plus, your purchase helps support indie developers and The Global FoodBanking Network (GFN)!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>