<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 08:28:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Neon Lights</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/neon-lights</link>
      <description>The blinding light of great games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all cyberpunks, adrenaline junkies, and action seekers—our latest bundle has the buzzing lights, bursting action, and bad-ass gameplay you’re looking for. Become Ann: a highly-skilled combat-trained lone wolf on a personal mission in <em>ANNO: Mutationem</em>’s giant Metropolis, run 'n' gun your way through the frantic, roguelike action-platformer <em>Neon Abyss</em>, or solve mysteries in gripping futuristic noir shooter <em>Neon Blood</em>. Explore these and other great games and help support XPerience Studios with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Armor Games Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/armor-games-bundle</link>
      <description>The very best from Armor Games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Indie developers aren’t bulletproof, but they sure are tough with the right armor. It’s time to feel the strength of the great games within our Armor Games Bundle. Dive into family-friendly choose-your-own-adventure fun with <em>Baladins</em>. Manipulate time with awesome RPG mechanics in <em>In Stars and Time</em>. Train to defeat an evil witch in <em>Swords & Souls:Neverseen</em>, and much more—plus, your purchase helps support the Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fellow Traveller Publisher Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/fellow-traveller-publisher-bundle</link>
      <description>Great indie games since 2011</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Indie games tell great stories—explore the narratively rich titles of Fellow Traveller publishing with our newest bundle! Since 2011, Fellow Travellers has championed smaller developers and their story-focused projects. Embark on an interplanetary adventure as the first robo reporter for the <em>Times & Galaxy</em>, the solar system's most trusted holopaper. Or play as a hardened captain of a polar expedition gone awry in <em>The Pale Beyond</em>. Get outstanding indie titles and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best of Boomer Shooters 4: Badda Bing Badda Boom</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/best-boomer-shooters-4-badda-bing-badda-boom</link>
      <description>Here comes the BOOM!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bullets, limbs, and blood fly freely in Best of Boomer Shooters 4: Badda Bing Badda Boom. Fire off bullets like it's a 1990s action movie with this bundle of high-octane shooters! Overcome your darkest nightmares with grit and guns in <em>Forgive Me Father 2</em>, revel in heart-pumping retro action in <em>Turbo Overkill</em>, and mix some dark magic into your next gaming session with <em>GRAVEN</em>. Play these great games and help support Cool Effect and Global Foodbanking Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Outright Games Game On! Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/outright-games-game-on-bundle</link>
      <description>Family friendly game night</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gather around the computer (or couch) and get ready for a good time! Outright Games, a leading kids publisher from the UK, have collected some of their best games fit for gamers of all ages in one convenient package. Play through new interactive stories of all your favorite series including <em>Bluey</em>, <em>Paw Patrol</em>, and <em>My Little Pony</em>.. Plus, each purchase supports Naomi House & Jacksplace, a charity centered on providing hospice care and support to children, young adults, and families. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dice and Destiny</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/dice-and-destiny</link>
      <description>A love letter to CRPGs</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[It’s time to fire up your computer, open a chat with your friends, and set off on some amazing CRPG adventures. Our latest bundle offers amazing titles that will spark your love for RPGs with their throwback-inspired gameplay elements and experiences. Explore the lands of acclaimed titles like <em>Disco Elysium</em>, and <em>Citizen Sleeper</em>. This curated collection of games is perfect for CRPG veterans and gamers looking to expand their field of interest. Play great games and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tactical Triumph</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/tactical-triumph</link>
      <description>Let’s get tactical </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Challenge and strategy—what more could you want in a game? Dive into the Tactical Triumph Bundle and see if you have what it takes to conquer these great titles. Embark on an epic journey across the land of Caelum one tile at a time in <em>The Iron Oath</em>. Master magic with the perfect mix of tactical team-based combat and deck building in <em>Abalon</em>. Tame monsters and explore dungeons with precision in <em>Siralim Ultimate</em>. Try new and tactical titles plus help support buildOn with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE COLLECTION</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/earth-defense-force-collection</link>
      <description>The least serious defense force ever</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Halt an evil invasion and save the world in <em>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE</em>. Our newest bundle features an amazing collection of <em>EDF</em> titles like <em>EARTH DEFENSE FORCE: WORLD BROTHERS 2</em>, <em>EDF 4</em>, and <em>EDF 5</em>, alongside a massive collection of bonus content like additional missions, cosmetics, and characters. These awesome arcade shooters are quick with the action and heavy on the charm—defeat the Ravagers and laugh along the way!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>