<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2026 02:28:47 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-Fi Shooters 2.0</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/scifi-shooters-bundle-2026</link>
      <description>Every flavor of sci-fi shooter</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Heat up the dark days of winter with a scorching-hot bundle of iconic shooters! Explore the frigid unknown of deep space in the genre-defining <em>System Shock 2: 25th Anniversary Remaster</em>, infiltrate the Galactic Empire as a covert Rebel Alliance operative in <em>Star Wars: Dark Forces Remaster</em>, and send hoards of demonic forces back to their fiery homeland in <em>DOOM Eternal</em>. Grab these rockin’ remasters of legendary sci-fi shooters—and support One Tree Planted and Cool Effect with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Battle Shapers, System Shock 2: 25th Anniversary Remaster, and STAR WARS: Dark Forces Remaster before August 20th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before February 20th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nacon Racing Collection 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/nacon-racing-collection</link>
      <description>Life in the fast lane</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Speed demons and Evel Knievels everywhere, we’ve got just the bundle for you! We’re partnering with Nacon for a collection of the publisher’s most high-octane racing simulator games that will launch you behind the wheel of the world’s fastest cars and most challenging courses, vetted by real-life professional drivers. Take a trip through the racing courses of past and present with <em>WRC 10</em>! Hop aboard your fastest bike and speed through over 200km of open-road in <em>TT Isle of Man: Ride on the Edge 3</em>! Test your mettle in the hyper-realistic rally simulation tracks of <em>WRC Generations</em>! If you’re always searching for the highest gear and living life in the fast lane, grab this bundle while you can and support SpecialEffect charity with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before February 18th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Sid Meier Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/best-of-humble-bundle-sid-meier-collection</link>
      <description>Play Sid Meier’s greatest games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the outstanding games and worlds of legendary game designer Sid Meier with our latest epic games bundle! Sink your teeth into a massive collection of award-winning strategy games, highlighted by a massive discount code for 2025’s <em>Sid Meier’s Civilization VII</em>. Choose from a variety of civilizations and lead your people to prosperity across multiple installments, special editions, and add-ons from the <em>Sid Meier</em> universe like the <em>Settler’s Edition</em>, <em>Deluxe Edition</em>, and more! Start your adventure today and help support The Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RollerCoaster Tycoon Collection 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/roller-coaster-tycoon-collection-2026</link>
      <description>Your rides, your rules</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Build the theme park of your dreams with the complete collection of RollerCoaster Tycoon games! Whether you’re an experienced park proprietor or completely new to the series, this bundle of all five games invites you to dive right in! Or buckle up, as it were. Relive the glory days of <em>RollerCoaster Tycoon Classic</em>, see what’s new in each of the sequel games, and test the boundaries of park design in <em>RollerCoaster Tycoon Deluxe</em> and <em>RollerCoaster Tycoon World</em>. There’s so much to design, build, and explore in this series, so get the full package while you can and support Gold Star Gamers with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before August 13th, 2026.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just Cause Complete Collection 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/just-cause-complete-collection-2026</link>
      <description>Guns, grappling hooks, and great gameplay </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Let the bullets fly and the good times roll across four epic installments of Square Enix’s exhilarating and bombastic <em>Just Cause</em> franchise. Cause mayhem and destruction across the fictional lands of San Esperito, Panau, Medici, and Solis. Enhance your experience with a gigantic library of add-ons and DLC, featuring the <em>Just Cause 3 DLC: Air, Land & Sea Expansion Pass</em>, <em>Just Cause 2: Monster Truck DLC</em>, and more. Jump into the action-packed world of <em>Just Cause</em> and help support One Tree Planted when you purchase the complete collection from Humble Bundle.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before February 11th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garphill Games Core Games</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/garphill-games-core-games</link>
      <description>Garphill Games—arriving at your doorstep</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fill your shelves with the hottest Tabletop Board Games on the market. From the lands beyond the Black Sea and beyond—fight for glory, strength, and territory to claim victory in <em>Raiders of Scythia</em>. Be the quickest player to invent, test, and develop original contraptions within an 850 AD setting in <em>Inventors of the South Tigris</em>. Raise the kingdom of your wildest dreams and lead your people to poverty or prosperity in <em>Viscounts of the West Kingdom</em>. Pay what you want for the very best from Garphill Games and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Garphill Game Expansions</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/garphill-game-expansions</link>
      <description>Your favorite Tabletop Board Games just got better</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re teaming up with Garphill Games to add new features, fresh adventures, and countless hours of fun to your favorite Tabletop Board Games. Gather your squad and fall in love with epic expansions like <em>Explorers of the North Sea: Rocks of Ruin</em>, <em>Architects of the West Kingdom: Works of Wonder</em>, <em>Paladins of the West Kingdom: City of Crowns</em>, and more. Pay what you want to have the very best expansions from Garphill Games shipped to your mailbox—and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase. Don’t miss out on our curated bundle of awesome Garphill Games—get the base games for your expansions before it’s gone, here.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Iceberg Hidden Gems Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/iceberg-hidden-gems-bundle</link>
      <description>Chill out with Iceberg</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Settle in for a cool beginning of 2026 with Iceberg Interactive’s Hidden Gems. Survey your capitalism kingdom, and strive to drive a profit as the <em>King of Retail</em>. Wield Gloom Girl’s <em>Doomblade</em> destroy the Dread Lords in an energetic 2D metroidvania. Or, live a pirate’s life on the PVP seas with <em>Blazing Sails</em>. Limitless adventures await across multiple genres, and every purchase benefits Doctors Without Borders/Médecins Sans Frontières! <br><br><span style="color: #EF9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem before February 6, 2027, at 11:00 PM Pacific Time.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibrant Visual Novels</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/vibrant-visual-novels</link>
      <description>Vibrant stories with striking visuals </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a style="color:#EF9741"><strong>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences.</strong></a><br><br>Place yourself in the heat of the story with the all-new Vibrant Visual Novels Bundle of story-driven games. Play <em>The Expression Amrilato</em>, a stunning visual novel–style title centered around two young girls learning to understand each other on multiple levels. Or <em>Needy Streamer Overload</em>, the multi-ending story of a girl obsessed with becoming the biggest personality on social media and her willingness to do anything to succeed. Get these and more engrossing visual novel–style games for a price you choose and help support Charity: Water with your purchase. <br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before February 4th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D3 Waifus 4U</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/d3-waifus-4u</link>
      <description>Welcome 2026 with wonderful waifus</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<a style="color:#EF9741"><strong>The content in this bundle is intended for mature audiences.</strong></a><br><br>Hotties and even hotter games—stay warm all winter with the D3 Waifus 4U Bundle! This collection has it all: play as a 21st-century, time-traveling teenage swordswoman tasked with saving the Sengoku period in <em>Samurai Maiden</em>. Bully enemies with bullets and leave the battlefield a bloody mess as certified waifu baddies in action-packed shooters like <em>Full Metal School Girl</em>, <em>Bullet Girls Phantasia</em>, and more. Find your waifu and help support Hello World when you shop with Humble Bundle.<br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem keys before January 30th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>