<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 20:26:04 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Xbox Games Studio Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/xbox-games-studio-bundle</link>
      <description>Must-play games by Xbox Game Studios</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Love great games? Us too. Explore the extraordinary worlds and environments of Xbox Game Studios with our latest game bundle! Explore the extraordinary worlds and environments of Xbox Game Studios! Take command of a squad of Desert Rangers in <em>Wasteland 3</em>’s post-nuclear world, help restore a magical forest in Ori and the Will of the Wisps, and battle… as toads in Battletoads. Most importantly—no Xbox console or subscription is needed. Get these great titles and more—and help support Gameheads with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9 Circles of Bullet Hell: A Survivors Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/9-circles-bullet-hell-survivors-bundle</link>
      <description>Bullets fly and bodies fall</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Let the bullets fly in our all-new 9 Circles of Bullet Hell Bundle. Play fan-favorite action-shooters and experience the thrill of intense, gun-based gameplay. Dive into <em>Picayune Dreams</em>, a roguelike blend of bullet horde survival and bullet hell chaos; <em>Vampire Survivors</em>, a retro-inspired shoot-’em-up with gothic horror elements; and <em>Genome Guardian</em>, a colorful asymmetrical shooter with psychedelic visuals. Discover fresh new games and help support Active Minds with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tycoon Titans Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/tycoon-titans-bundle</link>
      <description>Play tight ‘Tycoon’ titles today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Crazy about resource management and sim-style games? Manage farms, amusement parks, and more in our all-new Tycoon Titans Bundle! Build and design your own game studio in <em>Mad Games Tycoon 2</em>, run your own coffee shop in <em>Espresso Tycoon</em>, and construct roller coasters, carnival rides, and more in <em>RollerCoaster Tycoon 3: Complete Edition</em>. Plus, get two coupons for newly launched games: 35% off of Frostpunk 2, as well as 10% off Farm Manager World when you purchase this bundle. Lose countless hours to your addicting digital businesses—and help support No Kid Hungry with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>XCOM Complete</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/xcom-complete</link>
      <description>Defend Earth from evil aliens</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into the sci-fi world of <em>XCOM</em> with our comprehensive bundle of mainline games and DLCs. An all-out alien invasion has engulfed Earth, and it’s up to your elite team of planetary defenders to fight back and reclaim our homeland. Join the battle in iconic titles like <em>XCOM: Chimera Squad</em>, <em>X-COM: Enforcer</em>, <em>XCOM 2: War of the Chosen</em>, and more. Pay what you want for the ultimate <em>XCOM</em> experience, and help support the Michael J Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Play for Miracles with Twin Sails Interactive</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/play-for-miracles-with-twin-sails-interactive</link>
      <description>Games ahoy from Twin Sails Interactive</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Discover all the amazing titles of Twin Sails Interactive with the Play for Miracles Bundle! Dive into a curated collection of acclaimed indie gems survival adventures, deep strategy, board games, and more. From the deep strategic management of Terraforming Mars, to the gripping survival challenge of Survival: Fountain of Youth, this bundle showcases 12 standout titles and their DLC from our superb lineup. Support great games and a great cause—your purchase helps benefit Children's Miracle Network Hospitals!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>