<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2026 02:10:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Mega Man: Charged Up Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/mega-man-charged-up-collection</link>
      <description>Mega fun with Mega Man!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Mega Man mega fans and newbies alike won’t want to miss this bundle of Mega Man’s greatest hits! And, most excitingly, there are some new faces here along with a few familiar favorites: <span style="color: #ef9741;">this bundle’s higher tiers feature games that have appeared in our bundles, but the $20 tier includes games that have never been bundled before!</span> Power up your characters and weapons in entirely new combinations and test them against the side-scrolling action of Mega Man X DiVE Offline! Replay some old favorites or try them out for the first time with both volumes of the Mega Man Battle Network Legacy Collection! Get up to date with the main series and stop Dr. Wily’s nefarious plans in Mega Man 11! There’s much more Mega Man to be found in this bundle, so grab it while your Mega Busters are hot and support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem before March 19th, 2027 </span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cartridge Chaos</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/cartridge-chaos</link>
      <description>These homages will blow you away</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’re throwing it back to the good old days of bits, pixels, and platformers with this bundle of indie games with a retro feel! Save Sequin Land from total takeover by an evil foe in <em>Shantae and the Pirate’s Curse</em>! Take vengeance on your creators and discover hidden secrets in <em>Vengeful Guardian: Moonrider</em>! Go back in time for real to remix the past and help the Power Rangers fend off their archnemesis in <em>Mighty Morphin’ Power Rangers: Rita’s Rewind</em>! All of the great games in this bundle bring an old-fashioned aesthetic into the modern era. Grab it now while you can, and support NPower with your purchase!!  <br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles by March 18, 2027. The only exception is Moonrider, whose keys will expire on September 18, 2026.</span> ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Focus Entertainment Bundle 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/focus-entertainment-bundle-2026</link>
      <description>A spotlight on Focus Entertainment</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Explore the epic variety of Focus Entertainment with our latest high-octane game bundle! Every step forward comes equipped with two steps backwards in the dark, brutal, and breathtaking world of the award-winning <em>A Plague Tale: Requiem</em> and <em>A Plague Tale: Innocence</em>. Play as lightning-powered cowboys fighting monsters in <em>Evil West</em>. Defeat legendary monsters in spectacular fashion in <em>Atlas Fallen: Reign of Sand</em>. Pay what you want and help support the charity of your choice with Humble Bundle!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humble 15 Time Capsule</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/humble-15-time-capsule</link>
      <description>Celebrating 15 years of bundles!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[It’s our birthday, and everyone’s invited! We’re kicking off our 15th Anniversary of Humble Bundle with this collection of our favorite roguelikes and adventure games. Discover 5 fresh, never-before-bundled indie titles, paired with favorites from our very first bundles. Uncover the mysteries of a fantastical fantasy world alongside your own charming creations in the intricate strategy game <em>Oddsparks: An Automation Adventure</em>! Master the magic of the written word and save the Atheneum from evil in <em>Inkbound</em>! Take charge of an eldritch arena and wield powerful weapons against demonic foes in <em>Kill Knight</em>! Explore a haunted island, lift a curse, and find your missing pirate crew in <em>Mark of the Deep</em>! Celebrate 15 years of Humble along with one of our first charity partners: Child’s Play Charity!</p> <span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Bionic Bay before September 11th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before March 11th, 2027<br><br></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beamdog &amp; Owlcat: RPG Masters</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/beamdog-owlcat-rpg-masters-2026</link>
      <description>Killer RPGs from the modern masters</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[CRPG fans, this is the one you’ve been waiting for! Owlcat and Beamdog are responsible for some of the finest RPGs of the last decade—now’s your chance to snag both their entire catalogs in a single epic bundle! Explore the grimdark future like never before in <em>Warhammer 40,000: Rogue Trader</em>. Shake the very foundations of Golarion in <em>Pathfinder: Wrath of the Righteous</em>. Get all these games and more—including classics like <em>Baldur’s Gate: Enhanced Edition</em>, <em>Neverwinter Nights: Complete Adventures</em>, and many more. Plus, your purchase helps support DonorsChoose! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Pathfinder: Kingmaker - Season Pass and Pathfinder: Kingmaker - Enhanced Plus Edition before September 11th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before March 11th, 2027 </span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of the Wild 9th Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/call-wild-9th-anniversary</link>
      <description>The most realistic hunting sim roaming these lands</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Jump into the dynamic and realistic world of <em>theHunter: Call of the Wild</em> and experience a new level of hunting realism. This value-packed game bundle features a massive collection of add-ons and DLC. Hunt the rich Emerald Coast of Australia, the snowy peaks of the New England Mountains, and more. Take on alligators, lions, and other voracious predators and sell their pelts for supplies and coins. Pay what you want for the ultimate <em>theHunter: Call of the Wild</em> experience, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase! <br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem all titles before March 6th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overwhelming Positive Games Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/overwhelming-positive-games-bundle</link>
      <description>Good vibes games for you </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Featuring games with over 500 reviews, and 95% approval rates, the Overwhelmingly Positive bundle is jam packed with crowd pleasers. Unleash your inner party monster alone or with friends in <em>Monster Prom 4: Monster Con</em>. Experience 2025’s unique, cult favorite, plinko-style roguelike <em>Nubby's Number Factory</em>. Craft your deck to hold back the hordes of baddies boarding the <em>Monster Train</em>, and so much more. Add certified bangers to your library and help support the It Gets Better Project all at the same time! <br/><br/><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem before February 25, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Love You to Death Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/love-you-to-death-bundle</link>
      <description>Our bloody Valentine&#39;s day gift to you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[February is the month of connection and romance, and there’s no better way to celebrate than with the horror games from our all-new Love You to Death Bundle! Try <em>Ghost Watchers</em>—the goosebump-inducing co-op ghost-hunting journey, <em>Have a Nice Death</em>—the adorably addicting action roguelike starring everyone’s favorite scythe-wielding bearer of death, <em>Iron Lung</em>—the claustrophobic journey through the bottom of a blood-filled alien ocean, and so much more. Find out what makes you scream and help support Coral Guardian with your purchase.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. All titles should be redeemed before March 4th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sci-Fi Shooters 2.0</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/scifi-shooters-bundle-2026</link>
      <description>Every flavor of sci-fi shooter</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Heat up the dark days of winter with a scorching-hot bundle of iconic shooters! Explore the frigid unknown of deep space in the genre-defining <em>System Shock 2: 25th Anniversary Remaster</em>, infiltrate the Galactic Empire as a covert Rebel Alliance operative in <em>Star Wars: Dark Forces Remaster</em>, and send hoards of demonic forces back to their fiery homeland in <em>DOOM Eternal</em>. Grab these rockin’ remasters of legendary sci-fi shooters—and support One Tree Planted and Cool Effect with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Keys expire. Please redeem Battle Shapers, System Shock 2: 25th Anniversary Remaster, and STAR WARS: Dark Forces Remaster before August 20th, 2026. All other titles should be redeemed before February 20th, 2027.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>