<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 02:12:29 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Better with 4 Friends! Co-Op Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/better-with-4-friends-coop-bundle</link>
      <description>Grab the gang—let&#39;s game!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Grab your besties for a co-op game night with the all-new Better With 4 Friends Bundle! Play a variety of hilarious and wacky indie games designed to get the whole squad laughing. Lay track before the train crashes in <em>Unrailed!</em>, turn moving day into pure chaos in <em>Moving Out</em>, and battle blazes together in <em>Embr</em>—plus so much more. Pay what you want for this laugh-packed collection and help support the Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixel and Cartoon Enthusiasts Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/pixel-and-cartoon-enthusiasts-bundle</link>
      <description>Indie pixel and cartoony goodness</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive headfirst into the Pixel and Cartoon Enthusiasts GOG Bundle and explore a vibrant library of standout indie titles! Lead an underground resistance in Nazi Germany in <em>Through the Darkest of Times</em>, sneak your way through a spaghetti-western adventure in <em>El Hijo</em>, and explore a forgotten galaxy of strange planets in <em>Residual</em>—plus much more. Pay what you want for the very best in pixel-perfect and cartoony games—and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Classics Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/dungeons-dragons-classics-collection</link>
      <description>Play timeless D&amp;D campaigns</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Love retro TTRPGs? Rediscover legendary adventures with the all-new D&amp;D Classics Bundle from SNEG GAMES! This collection is packed with faithfully recreated campaigns for modern fans, featuring titles like <em>Forgotten Realms: The Archives – Collection I &amp; II</em>, <em>Dungeons &amp; Dragons: Dark Sun Series</em>, <em>Spelljammer: Pirates of Realmspace</em>, and more. Pay what you want to journey through timeless D&amp;D adventures and help support Covenant House with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sniper Elite: Classics Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/sniper-elite-classics-collection</link>
      <description>Line up the perfect shot</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Feel the exhilaration of lining up the perfect shot with the Sniper Elite: Classics Collection. Choose from dozens of rifles, maps, and targets across 5 complete <em>Sniper Elite</em> titles—including the <em>Sniper Elite 5 and Sniper Elite 4 Deluxe</em>. Relive sweet shots with the awesome Kill Cam and immerse yourself in the strategic gameplay. Pay what you want for hours of in-depth gunplay from the ultimate shooting simulation experience, and help support The Trevor Project with your purchase.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>The Trevor Project was not involved in the selection of the content in this promotion and the views, opinions, and ideas expressed in the games are not endorsed by, and do not reflect or represent the views and opinions of The Trevor Project.</em></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Untold Tales&#39; Indie Roulette Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/untold-tales-indie-roulette-bundle</link>
      <description>Let the games begin!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want to spin the wheel and play Indie Roulette with our latest bundle! Get 10 unique titles—each completely different and fresh. Want to play a cozy game? We got <em>Everdream Valley</em>. Prefer a brutal top-down shooter? You're in for a treat with <em>The Hong Kong Massacre</em>. In the mood to relax with a round of golf? Look no further than <em>Golf Club Nostalgia</em>. We have every corner of the gaming spectrum covered! Let the games begin and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>