<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS GAMES</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle games bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 16:26:06 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Draknek &amp; Friends: 12 Years of Great Puzzle Games!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/draknek-and-friends-12th-anniversary-celebration</link>
      <description>Prized puzzle games for you </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Diversify your games library and mix in some hot brainteasers with our latest Bundle. Celebrate 12 years of awesome titles from the genre-leading publisher, Draknek & Friends with the very best from their epic catalog.   Master the magical power of words to unlock mind-bending effects in <em>LOK Digital</em>. Curious monsters just want friends—use puzzles to make them in <em>A Monster’s Expedition</em>. The chemistry-based puzzles are explosively fun in <em>Sokobond Express</em>. Play these engaging puzzlers and help support The Trevor Project with your purchase!<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>The Trevor Project was not involved in the selection of the content in this promotion and the views, opinions, and ideas expressed in the games are not endorsed by, and do not reflect or represent the views and opinions of The Trevor Project.</em></span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Duo of Justice: Ace Attorney and Mega Man</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/duo-justice-ace-attorney-and-mega-man</link>
      <description>The hero team-up you never knew you needed…until now</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Put on your suit and tie and charge up your Mega Buster, because Phoenix Wright and Mega Man have joined forces for our latest games bundle! Act out the exciting courtroom drama at the heart of <em>Ace Attorney</em> compilations <em>The Great Ace Attorney Chronicles</em> and <em>Phoenix Wright: Ace Attorney Trilogy</em>. Try out all the best <em>Mega Man</em> games with <em>Mega Man Legacy Collection, Mega Man X Legacy Collection,</em> and <em>Mega Man Battle Network Legacy Collection Vol. 1.</em> A wealth of great games are at your fingertips for the price of your choice, and all purchases support Breakthrough T1D!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IGN Gamescom Bundle 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/gamescom-bundle-2025</link>
      <description>Greetings from Gamescom Germany!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gamescom 2025 is here—and we’ve assembled a curated bundle of standout games to celebrate! Located in Cologne, Germany, Gamescom is Europe's leading gaming & tech expo—where the best in the industry gather. Rule the boroughs using speed and style in <em>Bomb Rush Cyberfunk</em>, blast through <em>Antonblast's</em> fast-paced explosive action platformer worlds, and enjoy throwback vibes with turn-based RPG gameplay in <em>Lost Eidolons</em>, plus more. Get the very best of Gamescom from the comfort of your home and help support DonorsChoose with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Table Top Tag Team: Dire Wolf x Marmalade</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/table-top-tag-team-dire-wolf-x-marmalade</link>
      <description>Digital delivery of delightful boardgames </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Our latest Boardgame Bundle brings your favorite physical games to life with dynamic digital editions. Pay what you want for the very best from Direwolf and Marmalade games and let the good times roll.   Make the woods your battleground in <em>Root</em>—a boardgame rooted in fun! Establish a railroad empire while squashing the competition in <em>Ticket to Ride</em>. Solve the time old question of ‘who done it’ in <em>Clue/Cluedo: Classic Edition</em>. Play these and more iconic boardgames—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Whale & Dolphin Conservation. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Point Blank Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/point-blank-bundle</link>
      <description>Shooters in every size and flavor</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Grab your guns, bullets, and wits— it’s time to feel the adrenaline rush of fantastic shooters with the Point Blank Bundle! This action-packed collection of FPS and TPS hits from top indie publishers features the tactically-sound and realistic <em>EXFIL</em>, the surreal alien invasion sim <em>High on Life</em>, and the wacky roguelike FPS <em>Wild Bastards</em>. Pay what you want for an amazing library of shooters and help support the American Civil Liberties Union.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WB Play the Legends</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/games/wb-play-legends</link>
      <description>The very best from Warner Bros. Games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Love Sub-Zero, Middle-earth, and the Bat Family? The top-selling Warner Bros. Games bundle is back! Experience genre-defining combat as the Dark Knight himself in <em>Batman: Arkham Knight Premium Edition</em>, go toe-to-toe as the strongest and watch the blood drip off Raiden’s fists in <em>Mortal Kombat 11: Ultimate Edition</em>, stop the Court of Owls from overrunning Gotham City in <em>Gotham Knights</em>, and more. Satisfy your superhero roleplaying fantasies and help support the Raiden Science Foundation with your purchase!<br/><br/><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Keys expire. Please redeem your key before February 27th. 2026.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>