<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 01:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Best of Synty Game Dev Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/best-synty-game-dev-assets-software</link>
      <description>Turbo charge your game dev skills</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, build amazing worlds with this bundle of Synty polygon assets and more! Bring your projects to life quicker and make your dream game a reality while supporting a great cause. Synty assets are fully customisable and easy to use, making them accessible for game developers of all levels. Compatible with Unity and Unreal game engines—this high-quality collection features environments, characters, meshes, models, animations, and more for use. These Synty game dev assets are sure to inspire beginners and seasoned developers alike!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Game Dev Music Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-game-dev-music-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The sweet sounds of our latest bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The right soundtrack will elevate your prized project to new heights. Create the perfect audioscape for your game with The Ultimate Game Dev Music Bundle. This 50+ asset bundle features slick samurai music, scary slasher sounds, and others like <em>Paranormal Evening</em>, <em>Beyond the Horizon</em>, and <em>The Invincibles</em>. Don’t short your game’s soundtrack—get the ultimate collection of assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a C# and Unity Game Developer by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/becoming-c-and-unity-game-developer-packt-software</link>
      <description>A+ courses to master C# and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become a C# and Unity game developer with our latest super bundle by Packt! Our comprehensive collection will help you level up your skills in game creation, with hot course like <em>Build an Endless Runner Game in 3D - Unity 6 Compatible</em> and <em>Create Minecraft-Inspired Voxel Worlds - Unity 6 Compatible</em>. This 15+ course bundle will give you the knowledge you seek to begin an exciting new career. Take your passion for gaming to a new frontier and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>85 Miniatures Designed for Easy 3D Printing</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/85-miniatures-designed-for-easy-3d-printing-software</link>
      <description>Print your own 3D minis today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[It’s time to unleash your creativity and start printing your own 3D miniatures from home. Our latest bundle by HighCraft Miniatures features 85 unique mini schematics to fit any style. 3D printing continues to advance at an amazing rate—don’t fall behind this exciting technology, embrace it and fall in love with a new hobby. Print Grogs, Dagors, Pirate Toads, and style them any way you want. Paint amazing miniatures, and help support Code.org with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GODOT4 Mega Polygon Assets Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/godot4-mega-polygon-assets-bundle-software</link>
      <description>GODOT4? Yeah, we got that!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Curious about game creation? New and established game developers—build unique and beautiful worlds with our GODOT 4 Mega Polygon Assets Bundle from Animpic Studio. Add style and flare to your next project with original polygon vehicles, tools, villages, characters, and more. Break from the traditional hyper-realistic looks of modern gaming–unleash your inner creativity, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FALLOUT: The Roleplaying Game Complete Collection for Alchemy VTT</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/fallout-roleplaying-game-complete-collection-for-alchemy-vtt-software</link>
      <description>The wastelands of FALLOUT reimagined </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/E4FHSmdBpjQ?si=cF5Jv7ba19jwXZni" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>It’s time to take your <em>FALLOUT: The Roleplaying Game™</em> adventures to new heights!  Wander the Wasteland online with the complete collection of Modiphius’ award-winning tabletop RPG made specifically for the cinematic virtual tabletop, Alchemy RPG.  In this collection of Alchemy Content Modules, you’ll get core rules, expanded rules, adventures, campaigns, NPCs, and loads of new gear to collect, scrap, and craft. Dial up the immersion on game night with the Alchemy Enhanced edition of the Core Rulebook and get exclusive motion scenes, ambient sound loops, and an original dynamic score that will transport your players into the post-atomic world of <em>FALLOUT</em>.   Every module includes: A digital adaptation of the original book Fully mechanicalized game components like NPC, items, and automations Alchemy’s core Fallout integration with dice automations and smart character sheets Hundreds of art assets to amplify your adventures  Another settlement needs your help! Get this complete collection of games at one incredible price and support Direct Relief, supporting wildfire-impacted communities in California.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>War of Ashes Stl and Ruleset bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/war-ashes-stl-and-rule-set-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Rise from the War of Ashes together</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Tabletop RPG and Wargaming fans rejoice-—our War of Ashes Bundle from Strange Plastic is an action-packed collection with awesome gameplay and value.—our War of Ashes Bundle from Strange Plastic is an action-packed collection with awesome gameplay and value.&nbsp;Get 50+ unique assets to aid in bringing the battle to life. Create your own minis and play as a determined Elvorix, a vengeful Vidaar, a militaristic Jaarl, or a ravenous Kuld. Stage Romanic-style battles and embark on a grimsical adventure with your friends today. Plus, your purchase helps support the World Wildlife Fund.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The All-in-One VR Game Dev Bundle: Unreal, Godot, Unity + 1001 Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/allinone-vr-game-dev-bundle-unreal-godot-unity-1001-assets-software</link>
      <description>Game development in a new dimension</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Opportunities like this don’t come often! Learn how to create your own VR games with this bundle of courses from Mammoth Interactive! This comprehensive curriculum will help you level up your skills in VR game development, with Humble Bundle exclusives like <em>Godot 4 VR Development with WebXR</em> and <em>VR Unreal 5.5 Game Development Bootcamp</em>. This 30+ course bundle will give you the expert advice and knowledge you seek. Create in a new dimension and help support Children's Miracle Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Godot 2025 Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-godot-2025-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Go get the ultimate Godot bundle </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learning everything there is to know about Godot is simple with this comprehensive bundle. Perfect for beginners and experienced developers alike, it covers foundational concepts, programming patterns, shaders, and mechanics like crafting shops and state machines. Create diverse games, such as roguelikes, Metroidvanias, and tower defense games, using the latest Godot 4 features. Build engaging experiences with multiplayer functionality, procedural generation, and fully-fledged game systems, including civilization-style mechanics. Explore mobile game development, narrative-driven walking simulators, and visually striking projects with custom plugins and advanced optimization techniques. Start your game development journey today while supporting educational charities!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>