<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 08:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Make Music, Change Lives</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/make-music-change-lives-software</link>
      <description>Your move, maestro</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> It’s not easy to compose the perfect piece, but an asset library full of beats, clips, and instruments certainly helps. Our latest bundle has the ideal mix of sound files and melodies that span every genre you can think up, from orchestral epics to house beats to the cyberpunk trills of the future. Inside you’ll find looping synths, organs, guitars, and even a ukulele ensemble alongside a variety of genres like cumbia, R&amp;B, funk, and alt rock—perfect for crafting the fitting atmospheres for all your creative projects. </p>  <p> Valued at roughly <strong>$970</strong>, this collection includes <strong>well over 10,000 loops, samples, and MIDI files</strong> for your productions. <strong>Soundtrack Loops</strong> contributes <strong>7,559 professionally produced sounds</strong>, and at the <strong>top-tier bundle</strong>, the included <strong>Mixcraft DAW</strong> adds thousands more instruments, effects, and loops you can use to build full arrangements. Everything is royalty-free and ready for use in popular music software. </p>  <p> You choose what you pay to make the sound you’re looking for—and help fund student music programs with <strong>Music Will</strong> through your purchase! </p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Dev Station presents The Mega Game Dev Education Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/game-dev-station-presents-mega-game-dev-education-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Polish your game dev skills</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Sharpen your game development skills with a collection of curated learning paths. This flexible bundle by Game Dev Station has everything your game needs to succeed, with courses covering game testing, narrative design, procedural world generation, and project management. Whether you want to strengthen technical skills, become a better creative writer, or improve team efficiency, this bundle lets you combine the expertise that matters most to you. Pay what you want to polish your skills as a game developer and help support Save the Children when you learn with Humble.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Applied Acoustics Sound Designer Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/applied-acoustics-sound-designer-bundle-software</link>
      <description>A+ acoustics await inside </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with the ultimate bundle for sound designers and engineers. Unlock 20+ unique and specialized audio packs like the soothing <em>Lounge Lizard Session</em> pack, the retro-inspired <em>Ultra Analog Session</em> pack, the foot-tapping <em>Tabby Dance</em> pack, and so much more. Pay what you want for this curated collection of professional-quality audio assets and help support the Malala Fund with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character and Creature Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/character-and-creature-megabundle-software</link>
      <description>Start creating compelling characters</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Compelling casts of characters make or break a project—and we’re here to help you master character creation with a Megabundle of assets, tools, and techniques. This high-quality collection from Learn Squared features hot courses like <em>Designing Better Characters</em> and <em>3D Character Art</em>, and will teach you how to get the most out of trusted industry design platforms like <em>ZBrush</em> to give your work professional-level polish. Pay what you want for the assets you need to bring life to your original characters, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Film Makers VFX Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/film-makers-vfx-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Make your films pop!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Any movie can ride or die by its visual effects, and if you’re a filmmaker you know exactly how important these details really are. Finished production on your project but need a few VFX tweaks to make it really pop? We’ve got just the bundle for you: a collection of all the VFX software you need to add a little spark to your final product—maybe even literally! In this bundle of over 50 VFX packs, you’ll find everything from fiery explosions and muzzle flashes to floating embers and rain, along with animations, backgrounds, and LUTs to give your film that finished polish. Pay what you want for this great bundle, and support children and families in crisis with Save the Children!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Alchemy: A Premium Collection of Sound FX, Music, and Game Engine Plugins from Ovani Sound Encore </title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-alchemy-premium-collection-sound-fx-music-and-game-engine-plugins-from-ovani-sound-software-encore</link>
      <description>Audio alchemy with no strings attached </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the perfect audioscape for your next game or creative project with the Audio Alchemy Bundle of subscription-free sounds from Ovani Sound. Highlights from this extensive library of commercial-ready assets include Animals Sound FX Pack, Short Phrases Voice Over Pack, Epic Music Pack Vol. 2, and more! Explore a variety of genres, from lo-fi to classical and everything in between. Get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete 2026 Coding, AI, and GameDev Everything Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-2026-coding-ai-and-gamedev-everything-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The complete 2026 coding and AI collection</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get The Complete 2026 Coding, AI, and GameDev Everything Bundle and discover what possibilities await you within these red-hot fields. This curated collection of industry-standard courses from Mammoth Club, like <em>Multiplayer Lobby with Chat – Godot 4.6 3D Game Template</em> and <em>Animation Fundamentals: Keyframing, Blendspaces & Sequencer in Unreal 5.7</em>, lays the groundwork for you to learn the fundamentals. Gain the expert-led instruction and knowledge you need to succeed, and help support Little Free Library when you upgrade your skill sets with Humble.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Own Games In Unreal 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/make-your-own-games-in-unreal-2026-software</link>
      <description>From gamer to developer with ease </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Go from gamer to developer with the Make Your Own Games in Unreal Bundle! We’ve partnered with GameDev.tv to curate a library of courses and exams to streamline your progress and help you succeed in making RPGs, action games, and beyond. Get easy-to-understand courses like <em>Unreal 5 C++ Developer Course: Project Shooter Sam</em>, <em>Unreal Engine Blueprint Game Developer Course</em>, <em>Unreal Engine 5: Build a Complete Survival Game with Blueprint Course</em>, and more to help you master the fundamentals of game development. Unlock new possibilities and help support Trees, Water & People with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Coding for the Future: Intelligent App Creation</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vibe-coding-for-future-intelligent-app-creation-software</link>
      <description>No-code design is the vibe</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add new skills to your tech toolbelt with the Vibe Coding Bundle by Packt—the technique that blends AI and the development process to streamline your work and create no-code web applications! Learn from eCourses <em>Vibe Coding Bootcamp</em>, <em>Make Apps with ChatGPT and Generative AI</em>, and 10+ other can’t-miss lessons on your way to becoming a vibe-y all-star. Catch a coding vibe and help support buildOn when you level up your skills with Humble Bundle.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manager&#39;s Toolkit by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/managers-toolkit-packt-software</link>
      <description>Lead processes and people with confidence</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want to take your career to the next level and become a leader of people and processes with the Manager’s Toolkit Bundle. Master fundamental systems like Microsoft 365, or even take on new responsibilities as a scrum master with personalized lesson plans like <em>Microsoft Excel 365 – Beginner to Advanced</em>, <em>The AI-Enhanced Scrum Master – Automate, Analyse, and Accelerate Agile Workflow</em>, and more. Strengthen your leadership skills and learn how to get the most out of your team today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picture Perfect Creations</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/picture-perfect-creations-software</link>
      <description>Make your photos look their best!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whether you’re finishing up a film, building a photography portfolio, or creating a website, you want to make sure your images look their very best. That’s why we’ve partnered with Richdale Ventures for a software bundle focused on adding the finishing touches to anything and everything you’re working on! In this bundle you’ll find professional tools for optimizing images for HDR, high-quality video scaling, advanced website design, simple photography editing, and much more! Grab over $1,000-worth of software for the price of your choosing, and support the American Cancer Society with your purchase!! <br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">FRANZIS products: most programs can be installed and activated on up to three different computers. <br><br>WebSite X5 Evo: up to 2 workstations per license. License duration is 1 year. </span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega Game Dev Assets &amp; Tools bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/mega-game-dev-assets-tools-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Elite assets for any occasion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Save time, money, and effort on your next project with the Mega Game Dev Assets & Tools Bundle! We’re offering a streamlining experience for your next development cycle with 40 ready-to-use asset packs—including hyper-realistic water effects with the <em>Modular Swimming Pool Megapack</em>, user-friendly interface creation with the <em>Hyper Menu and Gamepad System v3</em>, and a trip to the moon with the <em>Space Launch Ground Control Command Center</em>. Get the right asset for any occasion, and help support EveryLibrary Institute with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra High Quality Unreal Engine Environment Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultra-high-quality-unreal-engine-environment-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Set the scene with unreal clarity </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve teamed up with ScansMatter to curate a bundle of ultra high-quality environmental assets for you this holiday season. Create big, beautiful scenarios within Unreal Engine using unique and clear preset environment kits designed to give you hyper-realistic settings: offices, abandoned airports, massive medieval markets, restaurants, and more. Pay what you want for amazing assets that save you time, money, and effort—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the World Wildlife Fund and animals in need. <br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">These are direct downloads through your Humble download page.</span><br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Licence Terms: Fab Standard License</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa&#39;s Phat Sack of Royalty Free Music</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/santas-phat-sack-royalty-free-music-software</link>
      <description>Unwrap Santa’s royalty-free music</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ea2ezRQOlw4?si=Ep50rwytQYaLylXU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> <br><br>Giddy-up, giddy-up, giddy-up, let’s go. Let’s look at the savings on Santa's Phat Sack of Royalty-Free Music from the audio experts at Phat Phrog Studio! Unwrap the gifts of RPG battle tracks, lo-fi, ambient, action, and countless other music collections for your next project. Never worry about renewing licenses or subscriptions when you pay what you want for audio assets from Humble Bundle. Plus, feel the holiday spirit and help support Save the Children with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IK Multimedia presents Audio Master Suite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ik-multimedia-presents-audio-master-suite-software</link>
      <description>IK Multimedia’s flagship audio software</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add a real punch to your next project with the Audio Master Suite Bundle from IK Multimedia! Get the <em>Sunset Studio Reverb Collection for MixBox</em>, and pro-quality plugins like <em>Delay Lab</em> and <em>Lo-Fi Punch</em> for <em>T-RackS 6</em>, IK's mixing and mastering software with countless modules and world-class processing. Alongside the <em>Bubinga</em> and <em>Plexi</em> kits for the MODO instrument series of digital drum and drum-modeling software. Pay what you want for these elite audio tools and help support Music Will with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software-encore-2025</link>
      <description>Calling all cartographers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything either released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, Cartographer's Annual Vol. 1–17, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>