<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 01:49:42 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software-encore-2025</link>
      <description>Calling all cartographers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything either released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, Cartographer's Annual Vol. 1–17, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Unreal Engine &amp; Unity Asset Bundle by Hivemind</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/massive-unreal-engine-unity-asset-bundle-hivemind-software</link>
      <description>Unleash your creativity with Unreal &amp; Unity</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/V_aqiiLCIl8" title="Humble Bundle Presents: Massive Unreal Engine &amp; Unity Asset Bundle by Hivemind" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Create the perfect setting for your next game wherever your heart desires with a massive Unreal Engine and Unity asset bundle by hivemind. Your project’s potential is limitless with easy-to-use modular assets that save you time and effort. Transport your players into epic fantasy battles with the <em>Duskbane: Modular Medieval Castle</em> and <em>Dungeon Forge: Modular Dungeon Building Kit</em> packs for Unreal Engine—or create an Eastern vibe with <em>Mountain Temple: Japanese Shrine / Temple</em>! Get the assets you need to achieve the look you’re seeking, and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase!<br><br><em>Unreal Engine FAB keys include Professional Licensing.</em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City of Mist Mythos Awakened Collection for Alchemy VTT</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/city-mist-mythos-awakened-collection-for-alchemy-vtt-software</link>
      <description>City of Mist x Alchemy VTT</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Play the hottest RPG, <em>City of Mist</em>, with meaningful theatrical enhancements using the City of Mist Mythos Awakened Collection for Alchemy VTT! Start your journey on the right foot with the core set, Player’s Guide, and more. Feel empowered as a GM to push the envelope of your adventures with Alchemy’s unmatched enhancements like animated scenes, ambient sound, and music. Elevate your campaign’s immersion, scale, and overall experience with the City of Mist Mythos Awakened Collection for Alchemy VTT—and help support the Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SampleTraxx Everything Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/sampletraxx-everything-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Award-winning samples have arrived</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7d0n41-LNaA?si=8oR8aVFyC2RK1gBB" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> Rock out to 54 signature Sampletraxx sound libraries in one definitive collection—create music in any genre, from pop to electronic and beyond! 100% royalty-free, easy to download, and packed with the highest-quality sonics around. Download the entire 61.4 GB collection quickly and easily via the Pulse downloader, too. Iconic braams, earth-shattering impacts, and tension-building risers—all for a price you choose. Unlock a vast array of uniquely recorded and diverse instruments, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Character Mega Pack by Maksim Bugrimov</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-character-mega-pack-maksim-bugrimov-software</link>
      <description>Unreal savings on Unreal Engine assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all game developers—we’ve got you covered with a curated collection of custom characters from Maksim Bugrimov! This awesome Mega Pack is optimized for Unreal Engine—an industry-leading game engine for developers of all levels. Pay what you want for countless unique assets, including fantasy creatures and warriors, post-apocalyptic survivors, vikings, and more. Bring your dream characters to life with powerful Unreal creation tools, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build It Better: The Ultimate 3D CAD Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/build-it-better-ultimate-3d-cad-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Embrace the CAD-do attitude</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lay a strong foundation in architecture with Build It Better: The Ultimate 3D CAD Bundle! Map out your future with Ashampoo 3D CAD Professional & Architecture 12’s easy-to-use interface and Office, Interior, and Kitchen Catalog extensions. Perfect for seasoned architects and students alike, this comprehensive library has everything you need to blueprint and plan the building of your dreams. Pay what you want to design the life you want to live, and help support the American Cancer Society!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design Unlimited Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/design-unlimited-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Draw, render, design, and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4eRHhqT2400?si=shKxtXlEV0v-HJ1t" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br> Calling all creatives and graphic designers—bring your vision to life without restrictions using CorelDRAW! Get professional graphic design software with vector, technical illustration, and CAD options to create logos, posters, drafts, and more. Plus, powerful AI applications like Vision FX, Vector FX, and Render FX are included! Level up your creative skills with elite software, and help support the Optimist International Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate 3D &amp; VR Sculpting, Character &amp; Game Asset Creation Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-3d-vr-sculpting-character-game-asset-creation-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Sculpt your future in VR &amp; 3D</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unleash your creativity with the Ultimate 3D & VR Sculpting, Character & Game Asset Creation Mega Bundle from FastTrack Tutorials and Shapelab! This powerhouse collection combines cutting-edge sculpting software, in-depth tutorials, and premium 3D asset packs to help you design stunning characters, creatures, weapons, and props. Whether you’re diving into VR sculpting with Shapelab, mastering AAA character workflows, or expanding your asset library, this bundle equips you with everything you need to level up your 3D artistry.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Unreal Asset Megapack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultra-unreal-asset-megapack</link>
      <description>Unearth Ultra Unreal Assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Ultra Unreal Asset Megapack brings together 38 high-end packs, each built for professional use, and designed to deliver AAA-quality visuals straight out of the box. From detailed cityscapes and gothic interiors to vibrant carnivals and sci-fi worlds, everything is fully modular, PBR-ready, and optimized for production. Also included is a Professional License, allowing use in large-scale studio and commercial projects. Expand your project or kickstart the next one, and support No Kid Hungry with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming for Modern Developers by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/programming-for-modern-developers-packt-software</link>
      <description>Get Learn to Code with Rust, Complete Modern C++ (C++11/14/17) and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pave your way to new beginnings in computer science. Discover a complete suite of courses by Packt, tailored for modern developers beginning their journey in programming. Learn Java, C++, and Rust through detailed lessons designed to take you from square one to seasoned programming veteran. Build strong fundamentals with courses like Java from Beginner to Expert, Complete Modern C++, and Learn Java from Scratch: A Beginner's Guide Specialization—and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Unreal Engine 5.7 + Assets Deluxe Bundle+</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-unreal-engine-57-assets-deluxe-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Create and excite with Unreal Engine </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="200" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ee57nG4aSuE?si=kA36zqa-aVciMXAl" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Pay what you want for an unrivaled bundle of Unreal Engine 5.7 assets, lessons, and more from Mammoth Club. Learn from 45+ courses designed to specifically fast-track your progression as a game dev master.   Become an asset-independent creator with massive VR, AR, 2D, and 3D libraries at your fingertips. Build professional-quality games featuring cinematic sequences and intelligent physics with an epic collection of environmental packs compatible with Lumen, Nanite, and procedural generation. Unlock powerful assets and help support charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>