<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 22:09:45 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete 2026 Coding, AI, and GameDev Everything Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-2026-coding-ai-and-gamedev-everything-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The complete 2026 coding and AI collection</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get The Complete 2026 Coding, AI, and GameDev Everything Bundle and discover what possibilities await you within these red-hot fields. This curated collection of industry-standard courses from Mammoth Club, like <em>Multiplayer Lobby with Chat – Godot 4.6 3D Game Template</em> and <em>Animation Fundamentals: Keyframing, Blendspaces & Sequencer in Unreal 5.7</em>, lays the groundwork for you to learn the fundamentals. Gain the expert-led instruction and knowledge you need to succeed, and help support Little Free Library when you upgrade your skill sets with Humble.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Own Games In Unreal 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/make-your-own-games-in-unreal-2026-software</link>
      <description>From gamer to developer with ease </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Go from gamer to developer with the Make Your Own Games in Unreal Bundle! We’ve partnered with GameDev.tv to curate a library of courses and exams to streamline your progress and help you succeed in making RPGs, action games, and beyond. Get easy-to-understand courses like <em>Unreal 5 C++ Developer Course: Project Shooter Sam</em>, <em>Unreal Engine Blueprint Game Developer Course</em>, <em>Unreal Engine 5: Build a Complete Survival Game with Blueprint Course</em>, and more to help you master the fundamentals of game development. Unlock new possibilities and help support Trees, Water & People with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vibe Coding for the Future: Intelligent App Creation</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/vibe-coding-for-future-intelligent-app-creation-software</link>
      <description>No-code design is the vibe</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add new skills to your tech toolbelt with the Vibe Coding Bundle by Packt—the technique that blends AI and the development process to streamline your work and create no-code web applications! Learn from eCourses <em>Vibe Coding Bootcamp</em>, <em>Make Apps with ChatGPT and Generative AI</em>, and 10+ other can’t-miss lessons on your way to becoming a vibe-y all-star. Catch a coding vibe and help support buildOn when you level up your skills with Humble Bundle.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Manager&#39;s Toolkit by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/managers-toolkit-packt-software</link>
      <description>Lead processes and people with confidence</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want to take your career to the next level and become a leader of people and processes with the Manager’s Toolkit Bundle. Master fundamental systems like Microsoft 365, or even take on new responsibilities as a scrum master with personalized lesson plans like <em>Microsoft Excel 365 – Beginner to Advanced</em>, <em>The AI-Enhanced Scrum Master – Automate, Analyse, and Accelerate Agile Workflow</em>, and more. Strengthen your leadership skills and learn how to get the most out of your team today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Picture Perfect Creations</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/picture-perfect-creations-software</link>
      <description>Make your photos look their best!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whether you’re finishing up a film, building a photography portfolio, or creating a website, you want to make sure your images look their very best. That’s why we’ve partnered with Richdale Ventures for a software bundle focused on adding the finishing touches to anything and everything you’re working on! In this bundle you’ll find professional tools for optimizing images for HDR, high-quality video scaling, advanced website design, simple photography editing, and much more! Grab over $1,000-worth of software for the price of your choosing, and support the American Cancer Society with your purchase!! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega Game Dev Assets &amp; Tools bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/mega-game-dev-assets-tools-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Elite assets for any occasion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Save time, money, and effort on your next project with the Mega Game Dev Assets & Tools Bundle! We’re offering a streamlining experience for your next development cycle with 40 ready-to-use asset packs—including hyper-realistic water effects with the <em>Modular Swimming Pool Megapack</em>, user-friendly interface creation with the <em>Hyper Menu and Gamepad System v3</em>, and a trip to the moon with the <em>Space Launch Ground Control Command Center</em>. Get the right asset for any occasion, and help support EveryLibrary Institute with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Lovable and Vibe Coding Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-lovable-and-vibe-coding-bundle-software</link>
      <description>A love for coding is in the air</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fall in love with the challenging and rewarding world of coding with The Complete Lovable and Vibe Coding Bundle by Mammoth Club. This modern library focuses on Vibe Coding—the technique that blends AI and the development process to streamline time-eating line writing. Learn from <em>Vibe Coding Unreal Engine 5.5 Game Development</em> and 40+ other can’t-miss lessons on your way to becoming a vibe-y all-star. Catch feels for coding and help support Girls Who Code when you level up your skills with Humble Bundle.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra High Quality Unreal Engine Environment Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultra-high-quality-unreal-engine-environment-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Set the scene with unreal clarity </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve teamed up with ScansMatter to curate a bundle of ultra high-quality environmental assets for you this holiday season. Create big, beautiful scenarios within Unreal Engine using unique and clear preset environment kits designed to give you hyper-realistic settings: offices, abandoned airports, massive medieval markets, restaurants, and more. Pay what you want for amazing assets that save you time, money, and effort—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the World Wildlife Fund and animals in need. <br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">These are direct downloads through your Humble download page.</span><br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">Licence Terms: Fab Standard License</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minis, Minis, and More Minis!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/minis-minis-and-more-minis-software</link>
      <description>Many minis, big bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Enhance your tabletop experiences with a gigantic collection of files to print off your own miniatures! With over 80 packages featuring heroes, villains, scenery and beyond, you’ll have a heap of realistic models at your fingertips. Plus, every purchase makes an impact on the Make-A-Wish Foundation, and that’s no small feat!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa&#39;s Phat Sack of Royalty Free Music</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/santas-phat-sack-royalty-free-music-software</link>
      <description>Unwrap Santa’s royalty-free music</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ea2ezRQOlw4?si=Ep50rwytQYaLylXU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> <br><br>Giddy-up, giddy-up, giddy-up, let’s go. Let’s look at the savings on Santa's Phat Sack of Royalty-Free Music from the audio experts at Phat Phrog Studio! Unwrap the gifts of RPG battle tracks, lo-fi, ambient, action, and countless other music collections for your next project. Never worry about renewing licenses or subscriptions when you pay what you want for audio assets from Humble Bundle. Plus, feel the holiday spirit and help support Save the Children with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAD ASSet BUNDLE (Unity Exclusive)</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/bad-asset-bundle-unity-exclusive-software</link>
      <description>Unlock a BAD ASSet or two</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RbuYvJofW8U?si=PBHC2e6i5pMxtYth" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> <br></br> Add a little spice to your holiday whether you’re naughty or nice with the hottest, BAD ASSets, around! This Unity-exclusive collection has everything you need to build stylized settings that are perfect for a variety of genres—run your own theme park with the <em>Carnival</em>, explore the dark and moody <em>Gothic Interior Megapack</em>, or a horror-ready <em>Apocalyptic Hospital</em>, and much more. Unlock endless possibilities with these badass assets and help support Stack Up when you shop with Humble. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering A.I.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/mastering-ai-software</link>
      <description>Learning AI just got easier </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve teamed up with the experts at Mammoth Club to help you master AI, machine learning, app development, and more through a massive collection of video lessons and practice exams designed to help you succeed. Confidently enter the exam room knowing you’ve seen it all after you’ve taken the <em>7-HOUR NVIDIA Certified Associate & Professional Infrastructure & Operations with 30 Practice Exams</em> course—build knowledge in Azure, Python, and beyond too!  Pay what you want for professional-quality courses and help support Music Will with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IK Multimedia presents Audio Master Suite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ik-multimedia-presents-audio-master-suite-software</link>
      <description>IK Multimedia’s flagship audio software</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add a real punch to your next project with the Audio Master Suite Bundle from IK Multimedia! Get the <em>Sunset Studio Reverb Collection for MixBox</em>, and pro-quality plugins like <em>Delay Lab</em> and <em>Lo-Fi Punch</em> for <em>T-RackS 6</em>, IK's mixing and mastering software with countless modules and world-class processing. Alongside the <em>Bubinga</em> and <em>Plexi</em> kits for the MODO instrument series of digital drum and drum-modeling software. Pay what you want for these elite audio tools and help support Music Will with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software-encore-2025</link>
      <description>Calling all cartographers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything either released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, Cartographer's Annual Vol. 1–17, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>