<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 01:48:12 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Super Weapons pack from Superhive</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/super-weapons-pack-from-superhive-software</link>
      <description>These weapon assets bring the BOOM!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking for blockbuster-level weaponry for your next project? Gear up with the Super Weapons Asset Pack by Superhive and add unbeatable value to your personal asset library! Choose from exceptionally detailed models or a colorful lowpoly look. Unleash the boom with a wide range of weapon types and genres, from medieval fantasy to sci-fi, like mounted machine guns, ninja shuriken, Smith & Wesson revolvers, rocket launchers, and so much more. Don’t bring a basic knife to a gunfight—get the Super Weapons Asset Pack and add exciting firearms and beyond to your next project! All these products work with the free, open-source software, Blender, and many assets function across 3D applications for maximum bang for your buck!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Game Creator Mega Bundle Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/game-creator-mega-bundle-vol-2-software</link>
      <description>Bring your game to life</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Want to build your own RPG with unique environments and exciting characters but just have no clue where to start? Find what you need in this Mega Bundle full of detailed, high-quality assets for games of every genre–everything from tilesets to build your perfect cursed school, map packs to design the dreariest dungeon, character generators for all your sprites, battlers, and faces, and music for every big moment and setting, from your darkest nightmares to your seediest cyber bars. Get over 100 asset packs to bring your game to life in Unreal Engine and Unity, and support Type 1 diabetes charity Breakthrough T1D with your purchase at the price of your choosing!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build your fantasy world with KitBash3D&#39;s Enchanted Collection Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/build-your-fantasy-world-with-kitbash3ds-enchanted-collection-software-encore</link>
      <description>Craft your own enchanted land</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Bring your dream fantasy world to life with this bundle of stunning premium 3D assets from KitBash3D! This bundle consists of KitBash3D’s <em>Enchanted</em> asset kit, which is perfect for any fantasy setting. You’ll get all the buildings you need to craft any number of convincing and authentic medieval fantasy environments—from bustling inns and pubs, to majestic keeps and secluded wizards’ towers. You’ll get a vast toolbox full of props to help make your fantasy world feel cozy and lived-in. Take advantage of this unbelievable value and help support Girls Who Code!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Create Game Art in Blender 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-create-game-art-in-blender-2025-software</link>
      <description>Blender for beginners and beyond </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Start your next career as a game art designer with a little help from the Learn to Create Game Art in Blender 2025 Bundle! Learn the basics or polish your existing skill set with expert-led courses like The Blender Sculpting Brushes Course, The Complete Blender Creator Course, and The Blender Animation & Rigging Course. Discover how to export your work directly from Blender to Unity and Godot with ease! Save big on life-changing creative tools and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Godot Game Development Template and Online Course Bundle+</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/massive-godot-game-development-template-and-online-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Discover your creative greatness with Godot </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OpsE6iXAbIs?si=p5OxXEZknkuoxZq-" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br> Start your new career in game development with a little help from the pros at Mammoth Club! Create engaging characters and dynamic levels with beta-ready templates, learn foundational development techniques through expert-led courses, and so much more. Build your own puzzle games, platformers, and first-person shooters—even get into the real nuts and bolts of game development by creating your own multiplayer lobbies with chat! Get massive savings on the tools and techniques you need to succeed as a game developer, and help support buildOn with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Apocalypse: A World-Ending Collection of Premium Sound &amp; Music</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-apocalypse-worldending-collection-premium-sound-music-software</link>
      <description>Savings never sounded so good</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We present to you the Audio Apocalypse—a red-hot landscape where the word overpriced has been eliminated! Pay what you want for the ultimate Audio Apocalypse and melt your eardrums with 30+ award-winning audio packs from Ovani Sound. Choose from specialized music plugins for Godot and Unity, a plethora of modular FX packs ranging from horrific to magical, complete genre-specific soundtracks, character voiceover packs, and more. We dare you—go nuclear and blow the minds of your listeners with elite sounds]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software-encore-2025</link>
      <description>Calling all cartographers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything either released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, Cartographer's Annual Vol. 1–17, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Unreal Engine &amp; Unity Asset Bundle by Hivemind</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/massive-unreal-engine-unity-asset-bundle-hivemind-software</link>
      <description>Unleash your creativity with Unreal &amp; Unity</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/V_aqiiLCIl8" title="Humble Bundle Presents: Massive Unreal Engine &amp; Unity Asset Bundle by Hivemind" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Create the perfect setting for your next game wherever your heart desires with a massive Unreal Engine and Unity asset bundle by hivemind. Your project’s potential is limitless with easy-to-use modular assets that save you time and effort. Transport your players into epic fantasy battles with the <em>Duskbane: Modular Medieval Castle</em> and <em>Dungeon Forge: Modular Dungeon Building Kit</em> packs for Unreal Engine—or create an Eastern vibe with <em>Mountain Temple: Japanese Shrine / Temple</em>! Get the assets you need to achieve the look you’re seeking, and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase!<br><br><em>Unreal Engine FAB keys include Professional Licensing.</em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City of Mist Mythos Awakened Collection for Alchemy VTT</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/city-mist-mythos-awakened-collection-for-alchemy-vtt-software</link>
      <description>City of Mist x Alchemy VTT</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Play the hottest RPG, <em>City of Mist</em>, with meaningful theatrical enhancements using the City of Mist Mythos Awakened Collection for Alchemy VTT! Start your journey on the right foot with the core set, Player’s Guide, and more. Feel empowered as a GM to push the envelope of your adventures with Alchemy’s unmatched enhancements like animated scenes, ambient sound, and music. Elevate your campaign’s immersion, scale, and overall experience with the City of Mist Mythos Awakened Collection for Alchemy VTT—and help support the Michael J. Fox Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SampleTraxx Everything Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/sampletraxx-everything-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Award-winning samples have arrived</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7d0n41-LNaA?si=8oR8aVFyC2RK1gBB" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> Rock out to 54 signature Sampletraxx sound libraries in one definitive collection—create music in any genre, from pop to electronic and beyond! 100% royalty-free, easy to download, and packed with the highest-quality sonics around. Download the entire 61.4 GB collection quickly and easily via the Pulse downloader, too. Iconic braams, earth-shattering impacts, and tension-building risers—all for a price you choose. Unlock a vast array of uniquely recorded and diverse instruments, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Character Mega Pack by Maksim Bugrimov</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-character-mega-pack-maksim-bugrimov-software</link>
      <description>Unreal savings on Unreal Engine assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all game developers—we’ve got you covered with a curated collection of custom characters from Maksim Bugrimov! This awesome Mega Pack is optimized for Unreal Engine—an industry-leading game engine for developers of all levels. Pay what you want for countless unique assets, including fantasy creatures and warriors, post-apocalyptic survivors, vikings, and more. Bring your dream characters to life with powerful Unreal creation tools, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build It Better: The Ultimate 3D CAD Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/build-it-better-ultimate-3d-cad-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Embrace the CAD-do attitude</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lay a strong foundation in architecture with Build It Better: The Ultimate 3D CAD Bundle! Map out your future with Ashampoo 3D CAD Professional & Architecture 12’s easy-to-use interface and Office, Interior, and Kitchen Catalog extensions. Perfect for seasoned architects and students alike, this comprehensive library has everything you need to blueprint and plan the building of your dreams. Pay what you want to design the life you want to live, and help support the American Cancer Society!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design Unlimited Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/design-unlimited-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Draw, render, design, and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4eRHhqT2400?si=shKxtXlEV0v-HJ1t" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br> Calling all creatives and graphic designers—bring your vision to life without restrictions using CorelDRAW! Get professional graphic design software with vector, technical illustration, and CAD options to create logos, posters, drafts, and more. Plus, powerful AI applications like Vision FX, Vector FX, and Render FX are included! Level up your creative skills with elite software, and help support the Optimist International Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Unreal Asset Megapack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultra-unreal-asset-megapack</link>
      <description>Unearth Ultra Unreal Assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Ultra Unreal Asset Megapack brings together 38 high-end packs, each built for professional use, and designed to deliver AAA-quality visuals straight out of the box. From detailed cityscapes and gothic interiors to vibrant carnivals and sci-fi worlds, everything is fully modular, PBR-ready, and optimized for production. Also included is a Professional License, allowing use in large-scale studio and commercial projects. Expand your project or kickstart the next one, and support No Kid Hungry with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>