<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 16:26:46 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Animation Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/pro-animation-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Animate like a big-time pro</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all animators—it’s time to level up your digital toolbox! Prepare to be blown away by the ultimate animation bundle from Graphixly LLC! Pay what you want for the Moho Pro 12.5 Bundle featuring <em>100 Brushes Content Pack</em>, <em>Characters Content Pack</em>, and <em>School Days Content Pack</em>. Take your skills from novice to pro in no time and help support No Kid Hungry with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Defold Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-defold-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Create fully-fledged original games</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn everything you need to know about building original games with The Complete Defold Course Bundle! Create your own original console, desktop, mobile, and web games using Defold—one of the most powerful and free dev engines around! Hone your skills with approachable courses like <em>Make a Fully-Fledged 2D Action RPG in Defold</em>, <em>Build a Complete 2D Platformer in Defold</em>, <em>Make a Farming RPG from Scratch with Defold</em>, and more. Get the knowledge you seek from the experts at Zenva Academy, and help support NPower with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a 3D Environment/Prop Artist - Mega Tutorial Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/become-3d-environmentprop-artist-mega-tutorial-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Create your own immersive 3D environments</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Curious about advanced game development and creation? Then become a 3D environmental artist with our latest Mega Tutorial Bundle! Get hot courses and asset packs like the <em>Japanese Environment</em> pack, <em>Large Game Environment Creation</em> guide, <em>Creating Low-Poly Stylized 3D Weapons</em> course, and more. Learn how to build beautiful cherry blossom fields, develop open-world maps, and manipulate low-polygon assets for added style. Pay what you want for professional-quality tools and help support Special Effect with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Becoming a C++ and Unreal Game Developer by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/becoming-c-and-unreal-game-developer-packt-software</link>
      <description>Unreal tools for game devs</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn how to create video games in Unreal Engine and C++ from the pros at Packt with our latest Humble Video Learning Bundle. Master modern game development with comprehensive courses designed to help you succeed quickly—like <em>Creating Stunning Environments in Unreal Engine 5 – A Game Artist Bootcamp</em> and <em>Complete Modern C++</em>. Get the expert education you seek from the professionals at Packt, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miniac presents An Intergalactic SkullForge STL Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/miniac-presents-an-intergalactic-skullforge-stl-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Models from galaxies far, far away</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about printables? Miniac presents the Intergalactic SkullForge STL Bundle. Pay what you want and get 20+ hot figure sets that bring life to your games—spend hours perfecting your own playables then show them off to your friends! Print, paint, and customize your own model figures from galaxies far, far away. Add new companions to your collection and help support Oceana with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MEGA MIX Unity Asset Store Pack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/mega-mix-unity-asset-store-pack-software</link>
      <description>Hot new assets for Unity</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Dive into our latest Humble Software Bundle and add hot new assets to your next game or creative project! The Unity Asset Mega Mix Bundle offers 25+ outstanding asset packs bursting with style. Pay what you want and get amazing asset packs like the <em>Modular Castle & Dungeon</em> pack, <em>Blood Effects Pack</em>, <em>Mystify FX</em> pack, and more. Get the professional-quality assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete 100-HOUR Software Architecture Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-100hour-software-architecture-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Software design made easier</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking to break into the tech world or land your first software design role? This exclusive bundle is your complete toolkit for building job-ready skills using Unreal Engine, AWS, and more!   Ideal for beginners and career-switchers—every lesson is practical, approachable, and focused on real outcomes. Actively learn from hands-on projects that mirror the challenges faced by real-world software professionals. Get hot courses that’ll prepare you for the field like <em>Advanced Software Design - Level Up Your Mastery</em> and <em>3D Web Architecture - Organize, Abstract, and Scale Your Code</em> today and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 16:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Game Dev with Unity, Godot, Unreal, GameMaker, Blender &amp; C#</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-game-dev-with-unity-godot-unreal-gamemaker-blender-c-software</link>
      <description>Make games like a pro</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about video games? Then start making your own! Our latest bundle will help you learn vital game development skills. Master the most popular creation platforms like Unity, Godot, Unreal, GameMaker, Blender, and C#—now that’s a sharp-lookin’ bundle! Build a 2.5D farming RPG with Unreal Engine, create a micro turn-based RPG in Godot, explore game optimization, and so much more. Get the expert advice and knowledge you need to become an elite game creator, and help support CARE with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Python, Machine Learning, Bots and AI Mega Bundle+</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-python-machine-learning-bots-and-ai-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Data engineering made easier </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking to break into data science or land your first data engineering role? This exclusive bundle is your complete toolkit for building a job-ready portfolio using Python, Pandas, and Scikit-Learn! Ideal for beginners and career-switchers—every lesson is practical, approachable, and focused on real outcomes. Actively learn from hands-on projects that mirror the challenges faced by real-world data professionals. Get hot courses that’ll prepare you for the field like today and help support The American Cancer Society with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Bang Unreal &amp; Unity Asset Packs Bundle ( 75 Products )</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/big-bang-unreal-unity-asset-packs-bundle-75-products-software</link>
      <description>5000+ unrivaled assets in one bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/B0WOTr5_vDQ?si=8ONHLg499EaXT6MM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Calling all game devs—build your worlds with this gigantic bundle of over 5000 assets, including realistic and stylized environments, SFX packs, and powerful tools. Perfect for hobbyists, beginners, and professional developers alike, you'll gain access to essential resources, tutorials, and beta-testing–ready content to start building immediately. The experts at Leartes Studios have curated an amazing library packed with value, featuring environments, VFX packs, and tutorial courses on Unreal Engine, Blender, Substance Painter, and ZBrush.  Get the assets you need to bring your game to life—and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!  This bundle provides Unity Asset Store keys directly with your purchase, and FAB keys via redemption through Cosmos, if the product is available on those platforms.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>