<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 01:46:16 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Programming for Modern Developers by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/programming-for-modern-developers-packt-software</link>
      <description>Get Learn to Code with Rust, Complete Modern C++ (C++11/14/17) and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pave your way to new beginnings in computer science. Discover a complete suite of courses by Packt, tailored for modern developers beginning their journey in programming. Learn Java, C++, and Rust through detailed lessons designed to take you from square one to seasoned programming veteran. Build strong fundamentals with courses like Java from Beginner to Expert, Complete Modern C++, and Learn Java from Scratch: A Beginner's Guide Specialization—and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Unreal Engine 5.7 + Assets Deluxe Bundle+</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-unreal-engine-57-assets-deluxe-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Create and excite with Unreal Engine </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="200" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ee57nG4aSuE?si=kA36zqa-aVciMXAl" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Pay what you want for an unrivaled bundle of Unreal Engine 5.7 assets, lessons, and more from Mammoth Club. Learn from 45+ courses designed to specifically fast-track your progression as a game dev master.   Become an asset-independent creator with massive VR, AR, 2D, and 3D libraries at your fingertips. Build professional-quality games featuring cinematic sequences and intelligent physics with an epic collection of environmental packs compatible with Lumen, Nanite, and procedural generation. Unlock powerful assets and help support charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GODOT Ultimate Asset Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/godot-ultimate-asset-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Godot for beginners &amp; experts</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Stop wondering what game to play next—start creating your own! Harness the power of Godot, the ultimate open-source creation engine! Pay what you want to access professional-quality content for Godot’s latest engine, including ancient cathedrals, stylized pirate port cities, dynamic fighting stages, and more. Perfect for beginners and experienced devs alike—start developing your own 2D and 3D games today! Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support Save The Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudioHero&#39;s Largest Cinematic Creator Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audioheros-largest-cinematic-creator-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Royalty free music sure sounds nice</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add professional-quality polish to your streams, YouTube videos, podcasts, and more with a gigantic bundle of licensed tracks and worldwide rights. One download gives you royalty-free music ranging from Arcade Anthems to Blockbuster Beasts. In this Humble exclusive, you’ll also unlock the Action Hero, Prodigy, and Starter Plans! Get a massive library of over 300,000 royalty-free songs and sounds from AudioHero Inc.—complete with licenses included—all for a price you choose! Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Artist Tutorial &amp; Learning Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/digital-artist-tutorial-learning-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Execute your vision from concept to completion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Go from indie to big-time with the Mastering Digital Art: From Concept to Completion Bundle. With powerful tools like Hard-Surface Masters Vol. 1 and Substance Masters Vol. 4, learn how digital art comes to life with bold textures, enhanced sculpting, and so much more. Plus, JROTools included ZBrush Masters Vol. 2, a tutorial series highlighting the workflows and techniques of top ZBrush artists. Add professional-quality polish to your next project and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Music Production Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-music-production-bundle-encore-software</link>
      <description>Total studio essentials for musicians </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Rock out or chill out to your own original music with our all-new Ultimate Music Production Bundle by IK Multimedia! Unlock your inner musician and create video game soundtracks, albums, and more with help from professional-quality plugins and programs like Total Studio Essentials and MODO BASS Studio Upright. Get the instruments and tools you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for—and help support Music Will with your purchase!<br><br> <a ><strong><em>Please note that these bundles do not qualify for the IK All-In 2025 Group Buy.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Top Down Adventure Assets Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-top-down-adventure-assets-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Amazing game assets working together</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Crafted by game developers for game developers—the Ultimate Top Down Adventure Assets Bundle by ElvGames is here to make your dev cycle easier. Get 75+ well-organized and properly named asset packs optimized for easy integration into popular game engines like Unity, Godot, GameMaker, and more. The standout feature of this expansive library is that all assets—including characters, sound effects, and music—are created by the same artists, so every element is designed to fit seamlessly with each other. Pay what you want for exceptional assets and help support the Prevent Cancer Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete DevOps &amp; MLOps Mastery Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-devops-mlops-mastery-bundle-packt-software</link>
      <description>Master machine learning operations</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get a leg up on the competition with practical machine learning skills from The Complete DevOps & MLOps Mastery Bundle. We’ve teamed up with the experts at Packt to assemble a comprehensive library of courses that include some of the most commonly used platforms in the industry. Pay what you want for hot courses like Python for DevOps: The Ultimate Hands-On Guide and Azure DevOps and Continuous Delivery with Git. Learn the skills you need from industry leaders, and help support The Against Malaria Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon &amp; Noir - Elite Photos with Luminar Neo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/neon-noir-elite-photos-with-luminar-neo-software</link>
      <description>Next-gen photo editing at your fingertips </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take your photos to the next level—introducing the Neon & Noir: Elite Photos with Luminar Neo Bundle. Luminar Neo by Skylum Software is an easy-to-use tool that helps you edit and enhance your images with ease! Within this exceptional bundle, you’ll gain access to a how-to-use course, the base software, expressive presets, and dynamic overlays—alongside standout add-ons like Tranquil Dawn Skies and City Lights. Picture-perfect edits at a price you’ll love. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Code.org.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>30,000 Loops for $30</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/30000-loops-for-30-software</link>
      <description>Get All 30 packs (30k loops) for $30 and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get ready for one of the largest and most versatile loop collections ever with the 30,000 Loops for $30 Bundle! Nine Volt Audio’s award-winning libraries have been restructured and repackaged into a Humble-exclusive collection featuring more than 30,000 loops across 30 genre-spanning packs, all delivered in WAV and REX2 formats—for just $30. The easy-to-use interface clearly labels and organizes every loop by key and tempo, making music creation faster than ever. Don’t miss the hottest loop bundle ever assembled—and help support Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Audiophile Collection</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audiophile-collection-software</link>
      <description>Add exceptional audio effortlessly</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[20 standout music packs in one bundle—nothing gets better than that! Get the most comprehensive collection of professional-quality music assets with The Audiophile Collection. Add bold expression with the Theme Music Pack, sophistication and class with the Orchestral Music Packs, or soothing and relaxing background sounds with the Ambient Music Pack. Create the perfect soundscape with The Audiophile Collection today and take your projects to the next level. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps the fantastic individuals at No Kid Hungry provide warm meals.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Beat Builders 2 - For Producers, Game Devs &amp; Creators</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/beat-builders-2-for-producers-game-devs-creators-software</link>
      <description>Beat packs built for you</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all producers, game developers, and content creators—mix your own mega hit, video game soundtrack, or ambient score with the latest Humble Software Bundle: Beat Builders 2! Drop specialized hip-hop beats inspired by Memphis style, Chop-N-Screwed, Heavy Bass, Trap, and more. Get the crowd moving with epic drops from House, Dubstep, Dark Techno, Progressive Psytrance, and beyond. Pay what you want for elite audio tracks to power your next project—and help support Little Kids Rock with your purchase.<p><a style="color: #ef9741;"><strong><em>Everything in this bundle is 100% royalty-free, allowing you to use it in any project without restrictions.</em></strong></a></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Python, Data Science and Machine Learning Mastery with Exams Bundle+</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-python-data-science-and-machine-learning-mastery-with-exams-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Get Machine Learning with Python and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/nomysjL7EYE?si=u4T3yGEq6q3wO0Lu" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>We've teamed up with Mammoth Club for our newest bundle! Get software like Excel Power Query Basics: Beginner's Path to Data Transformation with 10 Exams, ChatGPT-Powered Python Machine Learning Automation with 10 Exams, and Web Scraping Mastery: Python & Beautiful Soup Bootcamp with 10 Exams. Plus, your purchase will support Save The Children!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Total Action DevKit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/total-action-devkit-software</link>
      <description>Load up on action-packed game assets </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Action-packed assets await with the Humble Software Bundle: Total Action DevKit! This massive collection of professional-quality assets is fine-tuned for big explosions, magical mayhem, zombie apocalypses, and more. Get packs like <em>Ultimate Spell System</em>, <em>Elite Soldiers</em>, <em>Customized Post Apocalyptic Characters</em>, and more. The very best assets are here to help bring your game to life—plus, a portion of your purchase goes to support No Kid Hungry. Stop dreaming about building your game—start today!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Legendary Soundtrack Suite Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/legendary-soundtrack-suite-software-encore</link>
      <description>Soundtracks to suit any occasion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whether you’re a game dev, film maker, content creator, or creative of any stripe, this bundle has the music you need to make your project soar! Included are 40 music packs across a vast galaxy of genres, ready to plug into your workflow. From medieval tunes suitable for your fantasy epic, to symphonic metal to get your audience’s spirit stirring, get all the music you need to capture the perfect vibe. Pay what you want for this massive library of music and help support No Kid Hungry with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Best of Synty Game Dev Assets #5</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/best-synty-game-dev-assets-5-software</link>
      <description>Simply the best assets from Synty Studios</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Game developers, rejoice! The pros at Synty Studios are here to help you take your project from baseline to beta with our latest Software Bundle. Build your worlds with professional-quality assets—from towns, people, and militaries to stylized polygon kaiju, casinos, dungeons, and more. Add complex interfaces or simple dungeons—anything you need to help bring your dream game to life. You’ll even get a $10 voucher to the Synty Studios store to keep creating.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeon Master&#39;s Tabletop Essentials - 3D Printable Scenery &amp; Accessories</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/dungeon-masters-tabletop-essentials-3d-printable-scenery-accessories-software</link>
      <description>Give life to your next campaign</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add new levels of detail and depth to your tabletop adventures with the Humble Software Bundle: Dungeon Master’s Tabletop Essentials – 3D Printable Scenery & Accessories. This jam-packed collection is bursting with printable landscapes, structures, and more. Perfect for a variety of TTRPGs—design and customize elven shrines, crypt bookcases, dungeon traps, and 90+ other detailed scenery pieces, all from the comfort of home. Pay what you want to bring your game nights to life—and help support No Kid Hungry with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gigantic Game Dev Assets &amp; Tools Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/gigantic-game-dev-assets-tools-megabundle-software</link>
      <description>A gigantic game dev cache</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4oEJSAN7_iY?si=dW4BJO-gSAZcq93F" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Get ready to build the game of your dreams with this tremendous collection of assets and applications. With packs spanning from Victorian themes to medieval times and all the way to sci-fi, you’ll be ready to transpose your ideas to game space with ease. Over $5,000 worth of art, sound effects, visual effects, and more await your creative guidance. Plus, you’ll support Girls Who Code with your purchase.   ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Godot in 2025: Complete Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-godot-in-2025-complete-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Harness the freedom to create with Godot </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Your creative possibilities are limitless with the right game engine. Say hello to our latest Software Bundle: Learn Godot in 2025—a complete course collection designed to help you master Godot’s powerful, open-source, and beginner-friendly tools. Build any game you can imagine with step-by-step lessons like <em>Make a Complete Bullet Hell from Scratch in Godot </em> and <em>Make a Fully-Fledged Farming RPG with Godot</em>—then, learn to upload them online with <em>Publishing to Steam for Godot Game Projects</em>! Pay what you want for these great tools and help support NPower with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>