<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Feb 2026 20:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete n8n and Automation Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-n8n-and-automation-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Speed &amp; functionality in automation</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Automation feeling too rigid? Add flexibility to your workflows with The Complete n8n and Automation Bundle. n8n easily connects applications, databases, and APIs to quickly automate your tasks without extensive code. In a first-time Humble Bundle exclusive deal, learn how to use n8n to master lead generation automation for sales teams, build AI Agents with LLMs, streamline social media content, optimize your email marketing in Mailchimp, and so much more. Speed up your automation using the power of n8n, and help support Girls Who Code with a portion of your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best of Humble Level Up: 5K World Building Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/level-up-5k-world-building-assets-software-encore</link>
      <description>3D assets for any occasion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fSkGCpV2P7o?si=10s9RjOqmMKqm_jQ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Build the game of your dreams in any setting or scenario with our Level Up: 5K World Building Assets Bundle. The possibilities are endless—this massive library has everything from medieval to cyberpunk, gothic to ‘80s-inspired styles. Bring life and style to your projects with assets that let you create specialized hospitals, atmospheric taverns, underground subways, and more. Don’t wait—grab this jam-packed collection of high-quality 3D assets today and support Child's Play your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Game Audio Collection 1,800+ music tracks &amp; 65,000+ sound effects</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/game-audio-collection-1800-music-tracks-65000-sound-effects-software</link>
      <description>65,000+ professional audio assets ready for production</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all game developers and video creators! This massive audio bundle delivers 1,800+ high-quality music tracks and 65,000+ sound effects built for real projects and real pipelines. From dark fantasy scores for RPGs to punchy UI sounds, ambient soundscapes, and high-energy tracks for action and cinematic scenes, there’s music, sound effects and voice packs here for every style and genre. <p>  All assets are created by experienced contributors from GameDev Market, giving you production-ready sound at a huge scale. Expand your audio library, speed up your workflow, and support Hello World when you pick up this bundle through Humble Bundle. </p>   <p> All of the software in this bundle is available DRM-Free via direct download. <p/> <p>   License Terms:   <a href="https://gamedevmarket.net/terms-conditions#pro-licence"      target="_blank"      style="color: white;">     https://gamedevmarket.net/terms-conditions#pro-licence   </a> </p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Noise Alchemy SFX Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/noise-alchemy-sfx-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Brew the ultimate audio concoctions</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/sBoLXWsdOuw?si=dd9vCvA8YKHgHeLx" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with the Noise Alchemy SFX Bundle. This curated collection features hundreds of royalty-free effects and genre-specific sounds like sci-fi voices, sword clashing, and more. Plus, Humble members gain exclusive access to a one-year subscription to <em>Noise Alchemy</em>, the number one online sound effect creation platform! Pay what you want for a massive concoction of can’t-miss SFX assets, and help support Music Will with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ArchiMaster and Cadsoft Complete</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/archimaster-and-cadsoft-complete-software</link>
      <description>Design your future in architecture</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Start planning, blueprinting, and designing like a pro with our latest 3D CAD bundle! Learn how to use powerful CAD software and take your grand design ideas from your imagination to the real world. This amazing library includes <em>Cadsoft Personal Architect Online</em>, <em>ArchiMaster 3D Expert</em>, and a curated collection of specialized ArchiMaster home and landscaping design add-ons. Pay what you want for everything you need to succeed in architecture and help support the American Cancer Society with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Godot in 2026 Complete Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-godot-in-2026-complete-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Learn Godot and help others</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Are you curious about game creation? Learn to harness the power of Godot, the ultimate open-source creation engine, with our 2026 Complete Course Bundle! Pay what you want to access professional-quality game creation courses like <em>Metroidvania with Godot - Unit 1 - Platformer Basics</em>, <em>Monster Collector in Godot - Unit 1 - Overworld</em>, and more, all for a low price you choose. Make the most out of Godot and build any genre game you want—plus—a portion of your purchase helps support code.org!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Battle Hardened Game Asset Bundle by Hivemind</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/battle-hardened-game-asset-bundle-hivemind-software</link>
      <description>Badass battle hardened game assets </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="250" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/wUrGBRM01oI?si=lEn5CDp2zc0ztoD4" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Customize your next big action set piece with the ultimate collection of battle-hardened game assets by Hivemind! Light up the sky with realistic gun effects and set the perfect war scene in any era of history you choose—get the <em>Townsmith: Modular Medieval Town Megapack</em>, <em>Modular Military Base Megapack</em>, <em>Ultimate Spaceship System</em>, and much more. Create the realism of war with the very best battle-hardened game assets and help support the miracle workers at Make-A-Wish with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Polygon Assets by Animpic Studio</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/polygon-assets-animpic-studio-software-encore</link>
      <description>Low-poly game development asset trove</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking for a little help to build your digital world? Get an instant library of flexible, lightweight, low-polygon assets, perfect for any game. Whether you’re trying to create a moody, atmospheric sci-fi adventure (<em>Poly Style Mega Sci-Fi Sandbox</em>) or a dangerous and dark survival horror adventure (<em>Mega Survival Kit</em>), there’s something here for every kind of game. Vehicles, city-scapes, fantasy villages, medieval camps—it’s all here waiting for your creativity. Plus, your purchase helps support Save the Children!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Notch Unity Assets by Chris West</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/top-notch-unity-assets-chris-west-software</link>
      <description>Massive savings on breathtaking Unity assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Top Notch Unity Assets Bundle is here to help you create effortlessly. Streamline the development process behind your next project with a curated bundle of ready-to-use Unity assets by Chris West. Save time and money with beautiful and practical prefabricated asset packs like the <em>Full Sail</em> collection—the ultimate tool for realistic movement on sails and other cloth-like objects—and <em>Texture Studio</em>, the perfect rendering platform for clothing, buildings, and more. Pay what you want for the very best from Chris West and help support the Make-A-Wish Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Claude Code and AI Development in 2026</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-claude-code-and-ai-development-in-2026-software</link>
      <description>Build with Claude Code</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want to add the newest coding skills to your toolbelt with the 2026 Claude Code and AI Development Bundle. Learn from specialized courses like <em>Prompt Engineering for Programmers</em> and <em>Learn Vibe Coding with Cursor</em> alongside your mainline Claude Coding lesson plan. Claude is an automated coding agent you can use to help create original code, check your work, and save you from spending countless hours overworking yourself. Harness the ultra-powerful techniques of this amazing Humble Software Bundle and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bundle Big Royalty-Free Music</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/big-royaltyfree-music-software-encore</link>
      <description>The sweet sounds of royalty-free music</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Set the right tone for your next game with the perfect mix of music. We've teamed up with Dark Fantasy Studio for our latest royalty-free music bundle! Get 29 albums and over 400 tracks, including .wav, .mp3, and seamless premium licenses for music such as <em>Shadows Guild</em>, <em>Superheroes</em>, <em>Dreamagination</em>, and <em>Slasher</em>. Enjoy big-time savings on the best music collection around and help support Prevent Cancer with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Networking Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-networking-bundle-packt</link>
      <description>Your personal networking boot camp</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Building any network comes with risk, from malware to denial-of-service attacks, and knowing how to shield your personal or team data is basically a full-time job. To help you turn your collection of programs into an impenetrable fortress, we’ve partnered with Packt to bring you the complete bundle of networking and cybersecurity courses for an unbelievably low price. Think of this bundle of guides and video courses as the ultimate boot camp, with topics ranging from exam training for CCNA, CCST, and ENCOR, information on building advanced network topologies, and crash courses on Azure and GitHub. Everything in this bundle comes straight from the experts, so act now to get it all at the price of your choosing, and support women and children in poverty with Lotus Outreach International.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design Unlimited Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/design-unlimited-bundle-encore-software</link>
      <description>Draw, render, design, and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all creatives and graphic designers—bring your vision to life without restrictions using CorelDRAW! Get professional graphic design software with vector, technical illustration, and CAD options to create logos, posters, drafts, and more. Level up your creative skills with elite software, and help support the Trees, Water & People with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Music, Change Lives</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/make-music-change-lives-software</link>
      <description>Your move, maestro</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p> It’s not easy to compose the perfect piece, but an asset library full of beats, clips, and instruments certainly helps. Our latest bundle has the ideal mix of sound files and melodies that span every genre you can think up, from orchestral epics to house beats to the cyberpunk trills of the future. Inside you’ll find looping synths, organs, guitars, and even a ukulele ensemble alongside a variety of genres like cumbia, R&amp;B, funk, and alt rock—perfect for crafting the fitting atmospheres for all your creative projects. </p>  <p> Valued at roughly <strong>$970</strong>, this collection includes <strong>well over 10,000 loops, samples, and MIDI files</strong> for your productions. <strong>Soundtrack Loops</strong> contributes <strong>7,559 professionally produced sounds</strong>, and at the <strong>top-tier bundle</strong>, the included <strong>Mixcraft DAW</strong> adds thousands more instruments, effects, and loops you can use to build full arrangements. Everything is royalty-free and ready for use in popular music software. </p>  <p> You choose what you pay to make the sound you’re looking for—and help fund student music programs with <strong>Music Will</strong> through your purchase! </p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character and Creature Megabundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/character-and-creature-megabundle-software</link>
      <description>Start creating compelling characters</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Compelling casts of characters make or break a project—and we’re here to help you master character creation with a Megabundle of assets, tools, and techniques. This high-quality collection from Learn Squared features hot courses like <em>Designing Better Characters</em> and <em>3D Character Art</em>, and will teach you how to get the most out of trusted industry design platforms like <em>ZBrush</em> to give your work professional-level polish. Pay what you want for the assets you need to bring life to your original characters, and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2026 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>