<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 22:08:43 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Ascension: Game Music &amp; Character Voices Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-ascension-game-music-character-voices-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Make your game sound epic</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Elevate your game development with the Audio Ascension: Game Music & Character Voices Mega Bundle from Phat Phrog Studio! This massive royalty-free audio collection features 86 total albums, including 50 brand new music albums and—for the first time ever—19 all-new character and creature voice packs designed specifically for game developers and D&D / TTRPG enthusiasts.  From sweeping orchestral scores and intense battle themes to ambient soundscapes and terrifying horror loops, this bundle covers every genre and mood imaginable. And with high-quality, ready-to-use voice packs for fantasy creatures, sinister villains, heroic companions, and more, it’s never been easier to bring your characters to life. Whether you’re building your dream game or upgrading your existing projects, Audio Ascension gives you the tools to sound truly epic. Plus, you’ll be supporting Save The Children with your purchase, and that sounds pretty good to us.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blender 3D Modeling Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/blender-3d-modeling-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Mix it up with Blender assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add open-source 3D creation skills to your toolkit with our latest Software Bundle: Blender 3D Modeling Courses! Whether you’re a beginner or a seasoned pro, get comprehensive, professional-quality training covering every aspect of Blender in one complete library.  Learn from standout sessions from Eldamar Studio like <em>Learn Geometry Nodes Animation in Blender</em>, the <em>Creating a Modern House In Blender Course</em>, the <em>Procedural Materials In Blender Course</em>, and more. Pay what you want for priceless 3D modeling skills—and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Materia Collective Original Soundtrack Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/materia-collective-original-soundtrack-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Sweet tunes from hot games  </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get the sweetest tracks from the hottest games with the Materia Collective Original Soundtrack Bundle! Need to set some tunes on and chill? We’ve got you covered with the <em>Celeste Original Soundtrack</em>, <em>Superliminal Original Soundtrack</em>, <em>Shadows Over Loathing Original Soundtrack</em>, and more atmospheric, sensational tracks. Bring your day-to-day soundtrack to life with premium music and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase.<br><br> <a style="color:#EF9741"><strong><em>The titles in this bundle are original soundtracks and not to be used in other works.</em></strong></a>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Databricks, CompTIA, Cybersecurity, AI Certifications with 470 Exams Back to School Bundle+</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/databricks-comptia-cyber-ai-470-exams-back-to-school-software-bundle</link>
      <description>Back-to-school lessons by Mammoth Club</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get a head start on the new semester with our latest Humble Tech Bundle. Conquer your Databricks, CompTIA, cybersecurity, and AI certifications with ease using this curated library. Learn from first-time Humble Bundle exclusive courses like <em>The Ultimate GPT-5 Coding Guide with 10 Practice Exams</em> and <em>CEH: Certified Ethical Hacker with 10 Practice Exams</em>—and help support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UNITEd Together</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/united-together-software</link>
      <description>The ever enduring RPG creation platform</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pay what you want for RPG Maker Unite—the ultimate indie game-creation platform! Dive into our latest game dev bundle, designed to bring your game concept to life with a no-code structure, pre-built databases, and a massive library of assets to choose from. This comprehensive RPG Maker collection includes <em>RPG Maker VX Ace</em>, <em>RPG Maker XP</em>, <em>Pixel Game Maker MV</em>, and more! Get the tools you need to succeed—and help support Child’s Play with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Call of Cthulhu Keeper&#39;s Collection for Alchemy VTT</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/call-cthulhu-keepers-collection-for-alchemy-vtt-software</link>
      <description>Fresh spins on Eldritch Horror </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Thwart evil with the Call of Cthulhu Keeper’s Collection from Alchemy VTT! Get the complete rules for <em>Call of Cthulhu</em> players and Keepers, plus a massive pool of customization options for your original investigator. Pay what you want for thrilling expansions like <em>Call of Cthulhu: Masks of Nyarlathotep</em>, <em>Call of Cthulhu: Keeper Rulebook</em>, and more. From epic globe-spanning campaigns to single-evening sessions, this curated library offers a wide range of ready-to-play scenarios for you to explore. Perfect for parties of up to 5 players—gather your friends for a chilling adventure and help support Direct Relief with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity Analyst Course Collection by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cybersecurity-analyst-course-collection-packt-software</link>
      <description>Fortify your data from the digital world </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Nothing gets past our latest Humble Software Bundle: The Cybersecurity Analyst Course Collection. Learn how to protect your digital world from fraud, phishing attacks, and bad actors with top-tier courses from Packt. Pay what you want for <em>Risk Management for Cyber Security Managers</em>, <em>CCST Cybersecurity Video Training Series</em>, <em>CompTIA Security+ Certification: The Total Course</em>, and more.  Level up your cybersecurity skills—and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban Life Collection from KitBash3D</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/urban-life-collection-from-kitbash3d-software</link>
      <description>Blockbuster Assets Built for You. Worldbuild like a Pro!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Urban Life Collection bundle of interiors, props and vehicles by KitBash3D puts 500+ blockbuster-quality assets at your fingertips! These studio-grade, fully customizable assets have been used in major films including Dr. Strange, and Spider-Man, popular like The Last of Us, Star Trek: Discovery, and Halo and AAA gaming titles such as The Last of Us Part II, NBA 2K, and The Elder Scrolls, and now they’re available to creators of all levels. Whether you're a hobbyist, beginner or pro, these Kits are built to fit right into your workflow. Fully compatible with Blender, Unreal, Maya, Unity, Houdini, Cinema 4D, 3ds Max, and more, this bundle delivers unmatched value for anyone building cinematic urban scenes.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Aug 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Concept Art Training Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/the-complete-concept-art-training-bundle-software-encore</link>
      <description>Art training from the pros at Learn Squared</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Reach new heights in concept art and more with our latest bundle from the experts at Learn Squared. This bundle is perfect for artists starting their journey and experienced creatives alike—learn essential skills and workflows, and advanced training. Bring 3D sequence illustrations to life using master tools like ZBrush and Photoshop. Standout courses include <em>Concept Art for Video Games</em>, <em>Concept Art in Unreal Engine 5</em>. That’s right—learn to develop original art in the uber popular game engine Unreal Engine 5! Don’t wait, get this curated collection of courses and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freedom to create with CorelDRAW Graphics Suite 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/freedom-to-create-with-coreldraw-graphics-suite-2024-software</link>
      <description>Elite graphic design suite supersale</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your creative toolkit with <em>CorelDRAW Graphics Suite 2024.</em> Save big too—more than $475 off MSRP! Get vector illustration, layout assistance, photo editing, and typography tools with this professional-level software. Pay what you want to create with freedom and help support the Children's Miracle Network via Extra Life with your purchase. Act fast—this special promotion won’t last long]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>