<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Picture Perfect Creations</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/picture-perfect-creations-software</link>
      <description>Make your photos look their best!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Whether you’re finishing up a film, building a photography portfolio, or creating a website, you want to make sure your images look their very best. That’s why we’ve partnered with Richdale Ventures for a software bundle focused on adding the finishing touches to anything and everything you’re working on! In this bundle you’ll find professional tools for optimizing images for HDR, high-quality video scaling, advanced website design, simple photography editing, and much more! Grab over $1,000-worth of software for the price of your choosing, and support the American Cancer Society with your purchase!! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mega Game Dev Assets &amp; Tools bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/mega-game-dev-assets-tools-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Elite assets for any occasion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Save time, money, and effort on your next project with the Mega Game Dev Assets & Tools Bundle! We’re offering a streamlining experience for your next development cycle with 40 ready-to-use asset packs—including hyper-realistic water effects with the <em>Modular Swimming Pool Megapack</em>, user-friendly interface creation with the <em>Hyper Menu and Gamepad System v3</em>, and a trip to the moon with the <em>Space Launch Ground Control Command Center</em>. Get the right asset for any occasion, and help support EveryLibrary Institute with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Lovable and Vibe Coding Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-lovable-and-vibe-coding-bundle-software</link>
      <description>A love for coding is in the air</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Fall in love with the challenging and rewarding world of coding with The Complete Lovable and Vibe Coding Bundle by Mammoth Club. This modern library focuses on Vibe Coding—the technique that blends AI and the development process to streamline time-eating line writing. Learn from <em>Vibe Coding Unreal Engine 5.5 Game Development</em> and 40+ other can’t-miss lessons on your way to becoming a vibe-y all-star. Catch feels for coding and help support Girls Who Code when you level up your skills with Humble Bundle.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra High Quality Unreal Engine Environment Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultra-high-quality-unreal-engine-environment-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Set the scene with unreal clarity </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve teamed up with ScansMatter to curate a bundle of ultra high-quality environmental assets for you this holiday season. Create big, beautiful scenarios within Unreal Engine using unique and clear preset environment kits designed to give you hyper-realistic settings: offices, abandoned airports, massive medieval markets, restaurants, and more. Pay what you want for amazing assets that save you time, money, and effort—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support the World Wildlife Fund and animals in need.<br><br><span style="color: #ef9741;">These are direct downloads through your Humble download page.</span>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Santa&#39;s Phat Sack of Royalty Free Music</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/santas-phat-sack-royalty-free-music-software</link>
      <description>Unwrap Santa’s royalty-free music</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Ea2ezRQOlw4?si=Ep50rwytQYaLylXU" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> <br><br>Giddy-up, giddy-up, giddy-up, let’s go. Let’s look at the savings on Santa's Phat Sack of Royalty-Free Music from the audio experts at Phat Phrog Studio! Unwrap the gifts of RPG battle tracks, lo-fi, ambient, action, and countless other music collections for your next project. Never worry about renewing licenses or subscriptions when you pay what you want for audio assets from Humble Bundle. Plus, feel the holiday spirit and help support Save the Children with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minis, Minis, and More Minis!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/minis-minis-and-more-minis-software</link>
      <description>Many minis, big bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Enhance your tabletop experiences with a gigantic collection of files to print off your own miniatures! With over 80 packages featuring heroes, villains, scenery and beyond, you’ll have a heap of realistic models at your fingertips. Plus, every purchase makes an impact on the Make-A-Wish Foundation, and that’s no small feat!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mastering A.I.</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/mastering-ai-software</link>
      <description>Learning AI just got easier </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve teamed up with the experts at Mammoth Club to help you master AI, machine learning, app development, and more through a massive collection of video lessons and practice exams designed to help you succeed. Confidently enter the exam room knowing you’ve seen it all after you’ve taken the <em>7-HOUR NVIDIA Certified Associate & Professional Infrastructure & Operations with 30 Practice Exams</em> course—build knowledge in Azure, Python, and beyond too!  Pay what you want for professional-quality courses and help support Music Will with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BAD ASSet BUNDLE (Unity Exclusive)</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/bad-asset-bundle-unity-exclusive-software</link>
      <description>Unlock a BAD ASSet or two</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RbuYvJofW8U?si=PBHC2e6i5pMxtYth" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> <br></br> Add a little spice to your holiday whether you’re naughty or nice with the hottest, BAD ASSets, around! This Unity-exclusive collection has everything you need to build stylized settings that are perfect for a variety of genres—run your own theme park with the <em>Carnival</em>, explore the dark and moody <em>Gothic Interior Megapack</em>, or a horror-ready <em>Apocalyptic Hospital</em>, and much more. Unlock endless possibilities with these badass assets and help support Stack Up when you shop with Humble. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IK Multimedia presents Audio Master Suite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ik-multimedia-presents-audio-master-suite-software</link>
      <description>IK Multimedia’s flagship audio software</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add a real punch to your next project with the Audio Master Suite Bundle from IK Multimedia! Get the <em>Sunset Studio Reverb Collection for MixBox</em>, and pro-quality plugins like <em>Delay Lab</em> and <em>Lo-Fi Punch</em> for <em>T-RackS 6</em>, IK's mixing and mastering software with countless modules and world-class processing. Alongside the <em>Bubinga</em> and <em>Plexi</em> kits for the MODO instrument series of digital drum and drum-modeling software. Pay what you want for these elite audio tools and help support Music Will with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Finance Pro by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/finance-pro-packt-software</link>
      <description>Fundamental financial lessons for less</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello, future financial professional! Level up your money mastery with the latest Humble Video Learning Bundle.    Learn desirable and widely implemented software like QuickBooks Online and become the office payroll and finance expert with courses like <em>QuickBooks Online: Real-World Skills + Certification Readiness</em>. Or deepen your understanding of Microsoft’s Power BI with courses like <em>Power BI Masterclass - Python, Finance, and Advanced DAX</em>. Save big on a wide range of financial learning tools from Packt and help support Breakthrough T1D with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Unity in 2025 Complete Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-unity-in-2025-complete-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Unleash the creative power of Unity </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Go from gamer to creator with the Learn Unity in 2025 Complete Course Bundle! As the name suggests, this curated collection for the Unity Engine is a complete roadmap for your success. Each module covers a different genre of interest—take advantage of expert-led courses like <em>Construct a Micro-Farming RPG in Unity</em>, <em>Create a 3D Turn-Based RPG in Unity</em>, <em>Build an Arcade Kart Racing Game in Unity</em>, and more. Get the expert guidance and knowledge you seek, and help support buildOn with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinematic Magic with Vegas Pro 22 and Sound Forge Pro 17</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cinematic-magic-with-vegas-pro-22-and-sound-forge-pro-17-software</link>
      <description>Pioneers of sound &amp; video editing</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gift the creative in your life the power of AV editing with our newest bundle by MAGIX. Unlock <em>Vegas Pro 22</em>, the ultimate all-in-one video production powerhouse and gain access to effortless editing, advanced expandability, and so much more. For over 30 years, <em>SOUND FORGE Pro 17</em> has been the go-to audio platform of renowned and award-winning producers worldwide, and with Humble, you can get it for a fraction of the retail price. Get two cornerstone production tools for one low price—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support World Central Kitchen!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-in-One Game Dev Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/allinone-game-dev-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The one-stop-shop for game devs.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Build your worlds faster and bring your ideas to life with this massive collection of ready-to-use assets for Unreal Engine, Unity, and most major tools by Eldamar Studio. Unlock more than 13,000 assets, including 3D models, effects, UI, audio, textures, graphics, VFX, and more. No matter what kind of game you’re making—whether horror, fantasy, sci-fi, survival, or something completely unique—this bundle has assets for every style and setting. No complicated setup, no use limits—just drop the files in and start creating! Get textures, graphics, VFX, and more, and help support Save the Children!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Content Creator Audio Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-content-creator-audio-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Level up your sound with AudioHero&#39;s Ultimate Content Creator Bundle!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[This isn't just an update—it's a total audio revolution, packing the legendary Sound Explosion library with a massive injection of brand-new music and SFX. Get 100+ genre-spanning music collections and premium SFX toolkits for everything from epic cinematics to viral social clips. Score powerful moments with orchestral themes, design immersive worlds with detailed soundscapes, and hold your audience with professionally crafted tension and texture. From uplifting anthems and cozy home life ambience to podcast enhancers and wild nature recordings—every sound is royalty-free, instantly downloadable, and yours to keep forever. This is your complete sonic power-up to transform projects from great to legendary. Stop dreaming of pro audio—claim it.   ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leartes Black Friday Mega Game Dev Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/leartes-black-friday-mega-game-dev-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Bring your game to life</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ve_qOalBNjU?si=WjZraAn0zsg9CaM5" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Video games are nothing without detailed, atmospheric environments for your characters to move around in. Those can be tough to build from scratch, so we have the perfect solution: a bundle full of game development assets for every type of story and gameplay from the good folks at Leartes! This bundle of nearly 100 assets and asset packs for Unreal, Unity, and Godot has everything you need to design your neon-drenched cyberpunk city, your imposing fantasy castle, or your feudal Japanese village, along with nature assets for pine forests, jungles, and desert ruins. Get started building the game of your dreams, and help support the education and empowerment resources at Lotus Outreach International with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic Royalty-Free Music Collection Vol. 3</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/epic-royaltyfree-music-collection-vol-3-software</link>
      <description>Royalty-free tunes and tracks</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all sound engineers, game devs, part-time podcasters, and live streamers—save big on your next game, video, and more with awesome royalty-free music! Establish a dark, moody atmosphere for your ghost-themed podcast with <em>Terrifying Tension</em> and <em>Gothic Castle</em> tracks, or build the audioscape for your planet-jumping sci-fi RPG with <em>Replicant World</em> or <em>Desert Planet</em> tracks. Create the perfect mix for any situation with the Epic Royalty-Free Music Collection Vol. 3 by Joel Steudler, and help support Breakthrough T1D with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software-encore-2025</link>
      <description>Calling all cartographers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything either released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, Cartographer's Annual Vol. 1–17, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>