<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 22:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>3D CAD Professional Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/3d-cad-professional-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Professional CAD software for all</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Give your imaginary designs life—start designing like a pro with our latest 3D CAD bundle! Learn how to use powerful CAD software and take your grand design ideas from your imagination to the real world. This curated library of tutorials is highlighted by standout lessons like <em>Ashampoo 3D CAD Professional 12</em>, <em>Ashampoo Home Design 10</em>, <em>Ashampoo 3D CAD Architecture 12</em>, and more. Gain the skills you need to succeed in architecture and help support the American Cancer Society with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Arsenal: A Comprehensive Audio and Music Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-arsenal-comprehensive-audio-and-music-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The ultimate audio arsenal</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Up your Audio Arsenal and create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with our comprehensive audio and music bundle! Get 30+ unique themed products ranging from Sound FX Packs, Music Packs, and Voice Over Packs like like <em>Anime Music Pack Vol. 2</em>, <em>Stealth Sound FX Pack Vol. 1</em>, <em>Fantasy Music Pack Vol. 7</em>, and more. This collection also contains six plugins specifically designed for game engines including GODOT, Unreal, and Unity. Grab the assets you need to achieve the perfect sound design you’re looking for, and help support Children’s Miracle Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create, Paint and Animate Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/create-paint-and-animate-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Become a digital Picasso</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become a modern Claude Monet with our Create, Paint, and Animate Bundle! We’ve curated a beautiful collection of brushes and assets to help you make your own digital artwork. Turn your hot ideas into fashionable prints, design your own greeting cards, or finally panel that comic book project you’ve been procrastinating on. Get professional-quality creation tools like <em>Ultimate Brush Pack</em>, <em>Superhero Brush Pack</em>, <em>Comic Brush Pack</em>, and—huge news—Humble Bundle purchasers get exclusive 12 month license to <em>Clip Studio Paint Pro Version 4.0</em> too!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Projects for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/machine-learning-projects-for-beginners-software</link>
      <description>Machine Learning made easy </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master Machine Learning with our latest bundle by Packt. Our Machine Learning Projects for Beginners integrates video-style courses into the lesson plan to aid visual learners and avoid endless pages of text. This comprehensive curriculum will help you build your skills in <em>Natural Language Processing - Machine Learning Models in Python</em>, <em>Machine Learning - Modern Computer Vision & Generative AI</em>, and more! Get the expert advice you need to start a new career, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Unreal &amp; Unity Game Dev Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/supreme-unreal-unity-game-dev-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Unrivaled assets for Unreal &amp; Unity</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IjGKTsdpquI" title="Humble Bundle Presents: The Supreme Unreal &amp; Unity Game Dev Bundle" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Dive into an asset collection that offers the widest range of stylized towns, buildings, and more with The Supreme Unreal & Unity Game Dev Bundle! Save time and money by accessing this library of 50+ asset sets, ranging from medieval Viking villages to deserted military outposts—specific standouts include <em>Whispering Grove Environment</em> and <em>Asian Dynasty Environment</em>. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dungeons &amp; Monsters &amp; Pirates - Fantasy 3D Printable Models</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/dungeons-monsters-pirates-fantasy-3d-printable-models-software</link>
      <description>100+ printable 3D monsters &amp; more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about tabletop role-playing games? Stop buying stock figures from stores—start printing and painting your own at home! Turn game night into crafts night with our latest figure bundle with Hayland Terrain—get 100+ 3D-printable model schematics for you to customize any way you choose! Create your own plants, people, monsters, boats, and more. Unleash your creativity and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stylized Cartoon Assets Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/stylized-cartoon-assets-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Stylized—eye-catching—assets that pop</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Make games—but make them with style using our latest asset bundle by Hayq Art. The Stylized Cartoon Assets Bundle offers 40+ beautiful and unique asset packs for new and professional game devs. Add life and color to your next project with great packs like <em>Sci-Fi Environment Pack</em>, <em>Stone Age Characters Pack</em>, <em>Medieval Castle City</em>, and more. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life—and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Music Production Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-music-production-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Total studio essentials for musicians</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Rock out or chill out to your own original music with our all-new Ultimate Music Production Bundle by IK Multimedia! Unlock your inner musician and create video game soundtracks, albums, and more with help from professional-quality plugins and programs like <em>Total Studio Essentials</em> and <em>MODO BASS Studio Upright</em>. Get the instruments and tools you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for—and help support Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cybersecurity -  Zero to Hero ENCORE</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cyber-security-zero-to-hero-encore-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Take your cybersecurity into your own hands</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Looking to skill-up into the exciting field of cybersecurity? Or do you simply want to keep your systems secure and hack-proof? This bundle of online courses from Packt and ACI Learning will arm you with the skills you need! Dive into the deep end with a course on the National Institute of Standards and Technology’s cybersecurity and risk management frameworks. Work toward CompTIA certifications including CASP+, CySA+, PenTest+, and Security+. Dive into specialized training with Cisco's CCNP Security, DevNet Associate, and more. Master ethical hacking with CEH v.12, enhance your risk management skills with CISM, CRISC, and NIST frameworks, and become a cybersecurity all-rounder ready to tackle any threat. Update your skillset with the tools you need to break into this thriving field and help support Alzheimer’s Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become The Architect: CAD Software &amp; Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/become-architect-cad-software-tutorials-software</link>
      <description>Become the architect of your future</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Your exciting future in a new career awaits within our Become The Architect: CAD Software & Tutorials Bundle! Learn how to use powerful CAD software and take your grand design ideas from your imagination to the real world. This curated library of tutorials is highlighted by standout lessons like <em>BeckerCAD 3D PRO</em>, <em>BeckerCAD 2D</em>, <em>Autocad Tips & Tricks</em>, and much more. Gain the skills you need to help you succeed in architecture and help support Oceana with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developer Code Along by DataLab</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/developer-code-along-datalab-software</link>
      <description>Code your path to new frontiers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Coding is a limitless skillset that can elevate your career to new heights. Our latest Humble Video Learning Bundle in conjunction with DataLab offers 10+ professional quality lessons on a variety of coding techniques. Learn to build a variety of apps from hot courses like <em>Building a Fitness Tracker</em>, <em>Building a Movie Recommender System</em>, <em>Classifying Emails using Llama</em>, and more. Get the expert advice and knowledge you seek, and help support Alzheimer's UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic Adventures Asset Mega Pack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/epic-adventures-asset-mega-pack-software</link>
      <description>The perfect asset for any situation</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Our latest asset bundle offers a little bit of everything—dive into the Epic Adventures Asset Mega Pack and see what you can create. Setting a dramatic high school scene—or an adventure on a Mediterranean island? Then you’ll fall in love with asset packs like the <em>Mediterranean Island Pack</em>, <em>Survival Forest Cabin Bundle</em>, and much more. Get the unique assets you need to help bring your next project to life, and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The complete cartographic collection</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything ever released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, seventeen Cartographer's Annual, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Python Development</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-python-ai-agent-development-software</link>
      <description>Perfect Python like a pro</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master Python programming and AI agent development with this comprehensive bundle from Zenva. Inside this 25-course collection, you'll get hands-on experience building AI apps with DeepSeek, creating autonomous agents with CrewAI, and developing practical projects like meme generators and speech-to-text web apps. This bundle equips you with essential skills in Python fundamentals, web development with Flask and Django, data visualization, and cutting-edge AI implementation techniques. Progress from coding basics to sophisticated AI applications whether you're a complete beginner or mid-journey developer, and support technology education initiatives with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2025 AWS, CompTIA, Azure,Google Cloud, and NVIDIA Certification Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/2025-aws-comptia-azuregoogle-cloud-and-nvidia-certification-bundle-software</link>
      <description>A certification for every platform</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A new career is only a test or two away—our 2025 AWS, CompTIA, Azure, Google Cloud, and NVIDIA Certification Bundle has everything you need to study and prep. Get over 300 hours of expert-led content 420 full length practice exams and over 21,000 exam questions plus tons of Humble Bundle first time launch exclusives you will not find anywhere else. Ace your certification exams and help support Care.org with your purchase!</p> <p><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>Mammoth Interactive has re-branded to MammothClub. Please note, all new courses will be on their new platform at MammothClub.com. For valued returning students, your existing courses are linked to your email and will be imported shortly. Their new site has achievements, AI tutors, and more.</em></span></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>