<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 20:21:35 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Wanderlust Summer: Travel &amp; Learn with Lonely Planet / uTalk</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/wanderlust-summer-travel-learn-with-lonely-planet-utalk-software</link>
      <description>Explore the world from home</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn key words and phrases in another language—and so much more—with our latest bundle. This collaboration with Lonely Planet and uTalk offers 50+ travel ebooks from local travel experts, revealing everything you need to plan the trip of a lifetime, no matter what time of year you go. Plus, get 25+ language courses with video! Familiarize yourself with the words and culture of the Japanese, Filipinos, French, and more. Get the expert advice and planning help you need, and support World Central Kitchen with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Bang Unreal &amp; Unity Asset Packs Bundle ( 75 Products )</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/big-bang-unreal-unity-asset-packs-bundle-75-products-software</link>
      <description>5000+ unrivaled assets in one bundle</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/B0WOTr5_vDQ?si=8ONHLg499EaXT6MM" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Calling all game devs—build your worlds with this gigantic bundle of over 5000 assets, including realistic and stylized environments, SFX packs, and powerful tools. Perfect for hobbyists, beginners, and professional developers alike, you'll gain access to essential resources, tutorials, and beta-testing–ready content to start building immediately. The experts at Leartes Studios have curated an amazing library packed with value, featuring environments, VFX packs, and tutorial courses on Unreal Engine, Blender, Substance Painter, and ZBrush.  Get the assets you need to bring your game to life—and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!  This bundle provides Unity Asset Store keys directly with your purchase, and FAB keys via redemption through Cosmos, if the product is available on those platforms.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No-Code No Problem Game Dev Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/nocode-no-problem-game-dev-bundle-software</link>
      <description>DRM-Free Assets &amp; A No-Code GameDev Course!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Stuck in a time crunch on your latest project? Kick your development cycle into hyperdrive with the new No-Code, No Problem Game Dev Bundle from GDevelop. Save time, money, and effort with this curated library of unique and helpful DRM-FREE asset packs designed to deliver fast, high-quality results. Get 6 months of GDevelop Silver for free, along with amazing collections like the Pixel Dark Fantasy Bundle, Sci-Fi Space Village, and more. Explore the GDevelop Master Course and learn how to make a game quickly, no coding required! Bring your next game to life, and help support the Prevent Cancer Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FlippedNormals Extreme Add-ons Bundle for Blender &amp; ZBrush</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/flippednormals-extreme-addons-bundle-for-blender-zbrush-software</link>
      <description>Extraordinary quality—Extreme add-ons</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get quality add-ons for Blender and ZBrush with our latest bundle! We’ve teamed up with the pros at FlippedNormals to deliver a gigantic library of powerful tools for your next game development project. Add new life to your creative work with standout assets like <em>Real-time Hair ZBrush Plugin</em>, <em>Physical Starlight and Atmosphere</em>, <em>Easy Mesh ZBrush Plugin</em>, and more. Get the add-ons you need to bring color and individuality to your next project—and help support Extra Life with your purchase!<p><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>Free lifetime updates are not included in the bundle purchase. All creators have included coupon codes in the bundle, so you can purchase directly from their shop at a discounted price to receive updates and full support.</em></span></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D Artist Tools &amp; Brushes Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/3d-artist-tools-brushes-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Strokes of 3D art perfection </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all game developers, graphic artists, and budding printmakers—create your art using the elite tools in this awesome library. Our latest Mega Bundle offers 50+ collections of tools, assets, plugins, and brushes fit for any style of work. Use industry-leading resources like the <em>Bags & Pouches Collection</em> and <em>Hard-Surface Kitbash Collection</em>. Get the assets you need to bring your next project to life, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sound Explosion: 100+ Packs of Royalty Free Music &amp; Sound Effects</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/sound-explosion-100-packs-royalty-free-music-sound-effects-software</link>
      <description>The sweet sounds of savings</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with this amazing bundle of royalty-free sounds from Audio Hero! This massive library features 100+ samples, tracks, instruments, and more. Get the tools you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for with unique audio assets like the <em>Global Creator Mix</em>, <em>YouTube Creator’s SFX</em>, and <em>YouTube Creator’s Music</em>. Pay what you want and help support Children's Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biggest Graphics Bundle 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/biggest-graphics-bundle-2025-software</link>
      <description>The Biggest Graphics Bundle of 2025</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/_6GvnxH8O8k?si=PuW5zthkrQs9mR-p" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Are you a game designer looking to level up your project’s visuals? Then you need The Biggest Graphics Bundle of 2025 by Eldamar Studio. Get 70,000+ overlays, backgrounds, patterns, textures, and more from 80+ asset packs—standouts include <em>7700+ High-Resolution Backgrounds Bundle</em>, <em>3000+ Space Backgrounds and Textures Collection - Vol.1</em>, and <em>2500+ Massive Photo Overlays Bundle</em>. Get professional-quality tools compatible with Photoshop, Lightroom, Affinity, Premiere, After Effects, Final Cut, DaVinci Resolve, Unreal Engine, Unity, GIMP, and others—and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lights, Camera, Movavi! The Photo &amp; Video Dream Kit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/lights-camera-movavi-photo-video-dream-kit-software</link>
      <description>Lights, Camera, Movavi</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master the arts of film and photography with our latest software bundle from the experts at Movavi Studios. The Lights, Camera, Movavi Bundle offers 10+ tools for original photo and movie creation, including high-powered development software and additional asset packs to help you bring your vision to life. Get hot software like <em>Movavi Video Editor 2023</em> & <em>Movavi Photo Editor 2024</em>—and help support Oceana with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Make Games in Godot 4 by GameDev.tv 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-make-games-in-godot-4-gamedevtv-2025-software</link>
      <description>Godot 4 just got a lot easier</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Been sitting on your game dev ambitions? Jump into this bundle of online courses from GameDev.tv, packed with expert instruction on the skills you need to develop both 2D and 3D games using Godot 4. Learn the fundamentals of game mechanics, animation, scripting, and more with hot courses like <em>Complete Godot 3D Course: Develop Your Own 3D Games Using Godot 4</em>. Get the expert advice and knowledge you’re looking for—and help support Oceana with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>