<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 22:09:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Finance Pro by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/finance-pro-packt-software</link>
      <description>Fundamental financial lessons for less</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Hello, future financial professional! Level up your money mastery with the latest Humble Video Learning Bundle.    Learn desirable and widely implemented software like QuickBooks Online and become the office payroll and finance expert with courses like <em>QuickBooks Online: Real-World Skills + Certification Readiness</em>. Or deepen your understanding of Microsoft’s Power BI with courses like <em>Power BI Masterclass - Python, Finance, and Advanced DAX</em>. Save big on a wide range of financial learning tools from Packt and help support Breakthrough T1D with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IK Multimedia presents Audio Master Suite</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ik-multimedia-presents-audio-master-suite-software</link>
      <description>IK Multimedia’s flagship audio software</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add a real punch to your next project with the Audio Master Suite Bundle from IK Multimedia! Get the <em>Sunset Studio Reverb Collection for MixBox</em>, and pro-quality plugins like <em>Delay Lab</em> and <em>Lo-Fi Punch</em> for <em>T-RackS 6</em>, IK's mixing and mastering software with countless modules and world-class processing. Alongside the <em>Bubinga</em> and <em>Plexi</em> kits for the MODO instrument series of digital drum and drum-modeling software. Pay what you want for these elite audio tools and help support Music Will with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Futuristic Forge: Sci-fi 3D Printable Models Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/futuristic-forge-scifi-3d-printable-models-software-encore</link>
      <description>3D printing fun for everyone</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Are you passionate or curious about 3D printing? Start creating your very own sci-fi 3D printed models with the Futuristic Forge Bundle! Get the schematics for a diverse library of diverse character models, buildings, and settings like the Heavy Mecha Revenant M-2, Sci-fi Police Station, Heavy Berserks Squad, and more. Fire up the 3D printer for some new age fun while supporting Make-A-Wish with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Unity in 2025 Complete Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-unity-in-2025-complete-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Unleash the creative power of Unity </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Go from gamer to creator with the Learn Unity in 2025 Complete Course Bundle! As the name suggests, this curated collection for the Unity Engine is a complete roadmap for your success. Each module covers a different genre of interest—take advantage of expert-led courses like <em>Construct a Micro-Farming RPG in Unity</em>, <em>Create a 3D Turn-Based RPG in Unity</em>, <em>Build an Arcade Kart Racing Game in Unity</em>, and more. Get the expert guidance and knowledge you seek, and help support buildOn with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deluxe Dev Dream: 3D Unreal Engine Mega Bundle 4000+ Assets Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/deluxe-dev-dream-3d-unreal-engine-and-unity-mega-bundle-4000-assets-software-holiday-encore</link>
      <description>Jaw-dropping environments for Unreal Engine</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iTx4D2PuibQ?si=nQKfIpVTTLeGefx8" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Get the tools you need to craft environments that will truly transport your players with this massive bundle of assets for Unreal Engine. Included are over 20 asset packs stuffed to the brim with modular architecture pieces, props, materials, textures, blueprints, and more. Whether you’re aiming for the majesty of feudal Japan or the grim darkness of a gothic dungeon, you’ll get all the building blocks you need to make your vision real. Plus, your purchase helps Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Make Games in Godot 4 by GameDev.tv 2025 Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-make-games-in-godot-4-gamedevtv-2025-software-encore</link>
      <description>Godot 4 just got a lot easier</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Been sitting on your game dev ambitions? Jump into this bundle of online courses from GameDev.tv, packed with expert instruction on the skills you need to develop both 2D and 3D games using Godot 4. Learn the fundamentals of game mechanics, animation, scripting, and more with hot courses like <em>Complete Godot 3D Course: Develop Your Own 3D Games Using Godot 4</em>. Get the expert advice and knowledge you’re looking for—and help support Oceana with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cinematic Magic with Vegas Pro 22 and Sound Forge Pro 17</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/cinematic-magic-with-vegas-pro-22-and-sound-forge-pro-17-software</link>
      <description>Pioneers of sound &amp; video editing</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Gift the creative in your life the power of AV editing with our newest bundle by MAGIX. Unlock <em>Vegas Pro 22</em>, the ultimate all-in-one video production powerhouse and gain access to effortless editing, advanced expandability, and so much more. For over 30 years, <em>SOUND FORGE Pro 17</em> has been the go-to audio platform of renowned and award-winning producers worldwide, and with Humble, you can get it for a fraction of the retail price. Get two cornerstone production tools for one low price—plus, a portion of your purchase helps support World Central Kitchen!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>All-in-One Game Dev Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/allinone-game-dev-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The one-stop-shop for game devs.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Build your worlds faster and bring your ideas to life with this massive collection of ready-to-use assets for Unreal Engine, Unity, and most major tools by Eldamar Studio. Unlock more than 13,000 assets, including 3D models, effects, UI, audio, textures, graphics, VFX, and more. No matter what kind of game you’re making—whether horror, fantasy, sci-fi, survival, or something completely unique—this bundle has assets for every style and setting. No complicated setup, no use limits—just drop the files in and start creating! Get textures, graphics, VFX, and more, and help support Save the Children!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate Content Creator Audio Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-content-creator-audio-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Level up your sound with AudioHero&#39;s Ultimate Content Creator Bundle!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[This isn't just an update—it's a total audio revolution, packing the legendary Sound Explosion library with a massive injection of brand-new music and SFX. Get 100+ genre-spanning music collections and premium SFX toolkits for everything from epic cinematics to viral social clips. Score powerful moments with orchestral themes, design immersive worlds with detailed soundscapes, and hold your audience with professionally crafted tension and texture. From uplifting anthems and cozy home life ambience to podcast enhancers and wild nature recordings—every sound is royalty-free, instantly downloadable, and yours to keep forever. This is your complete sonic power-up to transform projects from great to legendary. Stop dreaming of pro audio—claim it.   ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme 2 - Unreal and Unity Game Dev Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/supreme-2-unreal-and-unity-game-dev-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Your world, your rules</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/O0SDyBUDJH8?si=delrs0zyHZSW5RGz" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Game devs everywhere, do we have a great bundle for you. Feast your eyes on a treasure trove of game assets in this new bundle from the good folks at Befour Studios! This asset library includes everything your heart desires, from sci-fi space environments, volcanic landscapes, and Mediterranean villages, to stylized weapons slashes and magic abilities, all for use in Unreal Engine and Unity. Use these assets to fill in the blanks in your newly completed game, or sift through them for some much-needed inspiration on a new project. Get this bundle for the price of your choosing, and support the Extra Life charity from Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EaseUS x Ashampoo: Windows Powerhouse Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/easeus-x-ashampoo-windows-powerhouse-bundle-software</link>
      <description>System Essentials for a clean and optimized Windows</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Skip the headache of searching for Black Friday deals and get the ultimate data recovery, backup, and disk-management software collection with the EaseUS x Ashampoo: Windows Powerhouse Bundle! We’ve assembled the coolest software bundle of the holiday season with OS2Go, Snap 17, WinOptimizer 28, and so much more. Optimize your Windows setup with the perfect tech software bundle, and help support the American Cancer Society with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Best of 2025 Asset Bundle - From GameDev Market</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/best-2025-asset-bundle-from-gamedev-market-software</link>
      <description>Wrap up 2025 with A+ assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepare to be amazed with the Best of 2025 Asset Bundle from GameDev Market. GDM is the ultimate marketplace for top-notch assets, and we’ve partnered together to offer you 60+ professional-level 2D, GUI and Audio game dev asset packs, which provide fantastic diversity without sacrificing quality. Standout packs include the Pixel Character Creator, the Military Soldiers Bundle, the 16-Bit Collection and more—all for a low price you choose. Simplify your holiday shopping when you choose Humble Bundle and help support Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leartes Black Friday Mega Game Dev Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/leartes-black-friday-mega-game-dev-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Bring your game to life</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ve_qOalBNjU?si=WjZraAn0zsg9CaM5" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Video games are nothing without detailed, atmospheric environments for your characters to move around in. Those can be tough to build from scratch, so we have the perfect solution: a bundle full of game development assets for every type of story and gameplay from the good folks at Leartes! This bundle of nearly 100 assets and asset packs for Unreal, Unity, and Godot has everything you need to design your neon-drenched cyberpunk city, your imposing fantasy castle, or your feudal Japanese village, along with nature assets for pine forests, jungles, and desert ruins. Get started building the game of your dreams, and help support the education and empowerment resources at Lotus Outreach International with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epic Royalty-Free Music Collection Vol. 3</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/epic-royaltyfree-music-collection-vol-3-software</link>
      <description>Royalty-free tunes and tracks</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all sound engineers, game devs, part-time podcasters, and live streamers—save big on your next game, video, and more with awesome royalty-free music! Establish a dark, moody atmosphere for your ghost-themed podcast with <em>Terrifying Tension</em> and <em>Gothic Castle</em> tracks, or build the audioscape for your planet-jumping sci-fi RPG with <em>Replicant World</em> or <em>Desert Planet</em> tracks. Create the perfect mix for any situation with the Epic Royalty-Free Music Collection Vol. 3 by Joel Steudler, and help support Breakthrough T1D with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Urban Apocalyptic Wasteland 3D Printable Models 2!</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/urban-apocalyptic-wasteland-3d-printable-models-2-software</link>
      <description>Create your own apocalypse</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Make your ultimate vision of the end of the world into a terrifying reality with this bundle of 3D printable assets for everything you need to build your own apocalyptic wasteland! This software library has over 100 assets to create the perfect ruined city: old-fashioned consoles and tables to give your environment a retro look, accessories and templates to build detailed supermarket and shopping mall interiors, and a ton of printable bunkers and figures caught in the middle of some extra-grungy post-catastrophe trench warfare. Pay what you want to build the perfect apocalyptic TTRPG environment, and support Make-A-Wish charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Unreal in 2025 Complete Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-unreal-in-2025-complete-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Make your game a reality with Unreal</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We’ve all been there: you’ve downloaded some really exciting new software but realized you have zero clue how to use it to its full potential. If this applies to you, and said program happens to be game design software Unreal Engine, we’ve got great news in the form of a giant bundle full of intro courses that will help you use Unreal to create anything you want. This bundle has comprehensive courses on everything from creating a high-octane bullet hell to building tower defense, horror, survival and turn-based RPG games from the ground up. Get the knowledge you need to build the skills you want, and support the Girls Who Code charity with every purchase at the price of your choice!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Create Game Art in Blender 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-create-game-art-in-blender-2025-software</link>
      <description>Blender for beginners and beyond </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Start your next career as a game art designer with a little help from the Learn to Create Game Art in Blender 2025 Bundle! Learn the basics or polish your existing skill set with expert-led courses like The Blender Sculpting Brushes Course, The Complete Blender Creator Course, and The Blender Animation & Rigging Course. Discover how to export your work directly from Blender to Unity and Godot with ease! Save big on life-changing creative tools and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Godot Game Development Template and Online Course Bundle+</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/massive-godot-game-development-template-and-online-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Discover your creative greatness with Godot </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/OpsE6iXAbIs?si=p5OxXEZknkuoxZq-" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br> Start your new career in game development with a little help from the pros at Mammoth Club! Create engaging characters and dynamic levels with beta-ready templates, learn foundational development techniques through expert-led courses, and so much more. Build your own puzzle games, platformers, and first-person shooters—even get into the real nuts and bolts of game development by creating your own multiplayer lobbies with chat! Get massive savings on the tools and techniques you need to succeed as a game developer, and help support buildOn with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Apocalypse: A World-Ending Collection of Premium Sound &amp; Music</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-apocalypse-worldending-collection-premium-sound-music-software</link>
      <description>Savings never sounded so good</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[We present to you the Audio Apocalypse—a red-hot landscape where the word overpriced has been eliminated! Pay what you want for the ultimate Audio Apocalypse and melt your eardrums with 30+ award-winning audio packs from Ovani Sound. Choose from specialized music plugins for Godot and Unity, a plethora of modular FX packs ranging from horrific to magical, complete genre-specific soundtracks, character voiceover packs, and more. We dare you—go nuclear and blow the minds of your listeners with elite sounds]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software-encore-2025</link>
      <description>Calling all cartographers</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything either released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, Cartographer's Annual Vol. 1–17, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Massive Unreal Engine &amp; Unity Asset Bundle by Hivemind</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/massive-unreal-engine-unity-asset-bundle-hivemind-software</link>
      <description>Unleash your creativity with Unreal &amp; Unity</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/V_aqiiLCIl8" title="Humble Bundle Presents: Massive Unreal Engine &amp; Unity Asset Bundle by Hivemind" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Create the perfect setting for your next game wherever your heart desires with a massive Unreal Engine and Unity asset bundle by hivemind. Your project’s potential is limitless with easy-to-use modular assets that save you time and effort. Transport your players into epic fantasy battles with the <em>Duskbane: Modular Medieval Castle</em> and <em>Dungeon Forge: Modular Dungeon Building Kit</em> packs for Unreal Engine—or create an Eastern vibe with <em>Mountain Temple: Japanese Shrine / Temple</em>! Get the assets you need to achieve the look you’re seeking, and help support Make-A-Wish with your purchase!<br><br><em>Unreal Engine FAB keys include Professional Licensing.</em>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>