<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 08:24:26 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The complete cartographic collection</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything ever released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, seventeen Cartographer's Annual, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adventurers and Adversaries STL Miniatures Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/adventurers-and-adversaries-stl-miniatures-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Miniature stature–big time fun</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Prepare to pour countless hours into your favorite artistic pursuit—mini figures—glorious miniatures for TTRPGs and more! Our latest bundle with Next Level Miniatures offers 50+ downloadable files to print and paint your own minis from home. Bring newfound depth and realism to your favorite TTRPGs with stunning figures like the <em>Dwarf Paladin</em>, <em>Goblin Mage</em>, <em>Red Dragon</em>, and more! Unleash your creativity and support a charity of your choice with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Python Development</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-python-ai-agent-development-software</link>
      <description>Perfect Python like a pro</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Master Python programming and AI agent development with this comprehensive bundle from Zenva. Inside this 25-course collection, you'll get hands-on experience building AI apps with DeepSeek, creating autonomous agents with CrewAI, and developing practical projects like meme generators and speech-to-text web apps. This bundle equips you with essential skills in Python fundamentals, web development with Flask and Django, data visualization, and cutting-edge AI implementation techniques. Progress from coding basics to sophisticated AI applications whether you're a complete beginner or mid-journey developer, and support technology education initiatives with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sounds for Adventure - A TTRPG Audio Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/sounds-for-adventure-ttrpg-audio-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Adventurous mood music for D&amp;D</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Oou9PnLk3MY?si=YTaUwwkEUxp6nDxa" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>The mysterious & mighty tunes of a dark fantasy soundtrack have never been closer—create the perfect audioscape for your <em>Dungeons & Dragons</em> game night with the Sounds for Adventure Bundle. This audio-based bundle is designed to enhance your <em>D&D</em> campaigns with thematic tracks like <em>Battle Music Vol 3: 50 Battle Scores</em>, <em>Dark Fantasy Vol 1: 50 Dark Scores</em>, and more. Get everything you need to elevate your <em>D&D</em> experience and help support Care.org with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2025 AWS, CompTIA, Azure,Google Cloud, and NVIDIA Certification Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/2025-aws-comptia-azuregoogle-cloud-and-nvidia-certification-bundle-software</link>
      <description>A certification for every platform</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A new career is only a test or two away—our 2025 AWS, CompTIA, Azure, Google Cloud, and NVIDIA Certification Bundle has everything you need to study and prep. Get over 300 hours of expert-led content 420 full length practice exams and over 21,000 exam questions plus tons of Humble Bundle first time launch exclusives you will not find anywhere else. Ace your certification exams and help support Care.org with your purchase!</p> <p><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>Mammoth Interactive has re-branded to MammothClub. Please note, all new courses will be on their new platform at MammothClub.com. For valued returning students, your existing courses are linked to your email and will be imported shortly. Their new site has achievements, AI tutors, and more.</em></span></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music for Dummies</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/music-for-dummies-software</link>
      <description>Feeling the rhythm—For Dummies</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The professionals from the <em>For Dummies</em> series are back again to help you unleash your inner musician. Learn a variety of digital instruments with in-depth lessons like <em> Singing For Dummies</em>, <em> Guitar For Dummies</em>, and <em> Piano For Dummies</em>. Track how you’re doing in real time—this 10 course bundle offers beginner and advanced courses for you to progress through. Take your passion for digital music to a new frontier and help support Care.org with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legendary Game Dev Environments Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/legendary-game-dev-environments-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Legendary assets for aspiring devs </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9VQzRJOrpwU" title="Humble Bundle Presents: Legendary Game Dev Environments Bundle by Leartes Studios" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Game developers—it’s time to build new and unique worlds with this bundle of 5000+ legendary game assets from Leartes Studios! This high-quality collection features environments, models, animations, and more for use in Unreal Engine and Unity. Recreate the post-WW2 Era with the <em>1950s NYC Environment Megapack</em>. Build a mighty castle setting with the <em>Fantasy Castle Environment</em>. Or curate your own magical garden lands with the <em>Stylized Paradise Gardens</em>. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support Care.org with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPG Maker Beyond Expectations Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/rpg-maker-beyond-expectations-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The magic of RPG Maker unleashed</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Love RPGs? Start making your own with the all new RPG Maker Beyond Expectations Bundle by Gotcha Gotcha Games. Unlock your creativity through the powerful medium of video games—you’ll be surprised how user-friendly <em>RPG Maker</em> is too. Within this amazing bundle, you’ll gain access to premium engine tools like <em>RPG Maker Unite</em>, <em>Pixel Game Maker MV</em>, <em>RPG MAKER VX Ace</em>, and more! Feel the freedom of expressing your personal style through game development—show off your love for anime, high-fantasy, steam-punk, and more. Make your own games and help support Extra Life with your purchase! <br><br>Check out the RPG Maker 2025 Game Jam <a href="https://itch.io/jam/rpg-maker-2025-game-jam">here</a>!</p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a 3D Artist - Mega Tutorial Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/become-3d-artist-mega-tutorial-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Creativity unlocked with a digital paintbrush</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unlock new beauty of creating vast digital worlds—Artists, it's time to become a 3D artist with this outstanding bundle of tutorials from FastTrackTutorials! Our high-quality collection features 30+ tutorials focusing on environments, characters, models, textures, and more for use in Unreal Engine, Unity, Blender, Zbrush and many more. Get the education you need to bring your art to life, and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>