<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 08:29:57 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Character Art Tutorial Bundle - Flash Sale</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/character-art-tutorial-bundle-flash-sale-software</link>
      <description>Create stylized AAA characters today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Say hi to summer with a scorching hot FLASH SALE! Learn how to create original AAA-quality characters from the pros at FastTrackTutorials. Build warriors, ninjas, and more with a suite of lesson videos. Pay what you want and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Level Up: 5K World Building Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/level-up-5k-world-building-assets-software</link>
      <description>3D assets for any occasion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/fSkGCpV2P7o?si=10s9RjOqmMKqm_jQ" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Build the game of your dreams in any setting or scenario with our Level Up: 5K World Building Assets Bundle. The possibilities are endless—this massive library has everything from medieval to cyberpunk, gothic to ‘80s-inspired styles. Bring life and style to your projects with assets that let you create specialized hospitals, atmospheric taverns, underground subways, and more. Don’t wait—grab this jam-packed collection of high-quality 3D assets today and support a charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn To Make Games in Godot 4 by GameDev.tv 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-to-make-games-in-godot-4-gamedevtv-2025-software</link>
      <description>Godot 4 just got a lot easier</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Been sitting on your game dev ambitions? Jump into this bundle of online courses from GameDev.tv, packed with expert instruction on the skills you need to develop both 2D and 3D games using Godot 4. Learn the fundamentals of game mechanics, animation, scripting, and more with hot courses like <em>Complete Godot 3D Course: Develop Your Own 3D Games Using Godot 4</em>. Get the expert advice and knowledge you’re looking for—and help support Oceana with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate World Building Asset Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-world-building-asset-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Imagine it—build it—love it</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Elevate your next project with elite 3D assets, textures, references, and more from the Ultimate World Building Asset Bundle by ScansMatter—featuring 300 free commercial credits on ScansMatter.com, <em>Rooftop Asset Kit</em>, <em>Office Environment Kit</em>, and much more. This limited-time partnership with ScansMatter gives Humble Bundle members a unique opportunity to access countless professional-quality assets at a fraction of the price. Get the assets you need to bring your next visual project to life—and help support the World Wildlife Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Electronics Bundle: Arduino, AI, ESP32, IoT, Robotics &amp; More</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-electronics-bundle-arduino-ai-esp32-iot-robotics-more-software</link>
      <description>Feel the spark of great electronics </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MZyUvlWHA24?si=R-6ci01VpF5xW9Qj" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Learn the ins and outs of Arduino, AI, ESP32, IoT, and robotics with The Ultimate Electronics Bundle by Skillet, and turn your curiosity into tangible skills. We have the right combination of courses to prepare you for success—get <em>ESP32 AI Assistant and Advanced Controls</em>, <em>Arduino Foundations: From Basics to Prototyping</em>, and other great tech courses within this amazing collection. Gain the expert advice you need, and help support One Tree Planted with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Vibe Coding, Automation and Profit Super Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-vibe-coding-automation-and-profit-super-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Work smarter—Code faster</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Vibe Coding is the number one skill for building modern software fast. Create games, apps, and profitable SaaS projects in a fraction of the time. With Mammoth Club's ready-to-use source code and expert-crafted prompts, you'll launch faster and automate smarter. Top courses include <em>Game Development with Godot 4 Vibe Coding</em>, <em>Vibe Coding Unreal Engine 5.5 Game Development</em>, and <em>SaaS Empire—hand picked to give you the ultimate edge.</em> Plus, Mammoth Club just launched their new platform with achievements, AI tutors and more. Humble Bundle users get a special, exclusive achievement available for the top tier only. Don't fall behind. Get this bundle now and support Children's Miracle Network while you futureproof your skills.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlock Pro 3D Modeling Skills with Blender by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unlock-pro-3d-modeling-skills-with-blender-packt-software</link>
      <description>Unlock awesome 3D tools for Blender</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[3D modeling has never been more popular and widely available—get into the action and start creating for yourself with our latest bundle by Packt! Render, animate, model, and more in 3D with hot Blender tutorials like <em>Material Fundamentals - Procedural Textures in Blender 4.4</em>, <em>Geometry Nodes For Blender 4.4</em>, and more. Get the professional-quality guides you need to create and manipulate 3D objects, characters, and environments, and more. Plus, your purchase helps support Alzheimer's Research UK!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Complete 2D Game Assets Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-2d-game-assets-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Retro inspired assets for a new age</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add retro vibes to your next game project with our all-new 2D game asset bundle by ElvGames! Choose from 75+ collections of unique and exciting game assets for use in Unity, Unreal, and other popular development engines. This high-quality collection features environments, characters, meshes, models, animations, and more in a variety of styles ranging from cute to horrific. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support the Prevent Cancer Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3D CAD Professional Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/3d-cad-professional-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Professional CAD software for all</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Give your imaginary designs life—start designing like a pro with our latest 3D CAD bundle! Learn how to use powerful CAD software and take your grand design ideas from your imagination to the real world. This curated library of tutorials is highlighted by standout lessons like <em>Ashampoo 3D CAD Professional 12</em>, <em>Ashampoo Home Design 10</em>, <em>Ashampoo 3D CAD Architecture 12</em>, and more. Gain the skills you need to succeed in architecture and help support the American Cancer Society with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Arsenal: A Comprehensive Audio and Music Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-arsenal-comprehensive-audio-and-music-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The ultimate audio arsenal</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Up your Audio Arsenal and create the perfect audioscape for your game, film, or creative project with our comprehensive audio and music bundle! Get 30+ unique themed products ranging from Sound FX Packs, Music Packs, and Voice Over Packs like like <em>Anime Music Pack Vol. 2</em>, <em>Stealth Sound FX Pack Vol. 1</em>, <em>Fantasy Music Pack Vol. 7</em>, and more. This collection also contains six plugins specifically designed for game engines including GODOT, Unreal, and Unity. Grab the assets you need to achieve the perfect sound design you’re looking for, and help support Children’s Miracle Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create, Paint and Animate Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/create-paint-and-animate-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Become a digital Picasso</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Become a modern Claude Monet with our Create, Paint, and Animate Bundle! We’ve curated a beautiful collection of brushes and assets to help you make your own digital artwork. Turn your hot ideas into fashionable prints, design your own greeting cards, or finally panel that comic book project you’ve been procrastinating on. Get professional-quality creation tools like <em>Ultimate Brush Pack</em>, <em>Superhero Brush Pack</em>, <em>Comic Brush Pack</em>, and—huge news—Humble Bundle purchasers get exclusive 12 month license to <em>Clip Studio Paint Pro Version 4.0</em> too!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Supreme Unreal &amp; Unity Game Dev Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/supreme-unreal-unity-game-dev-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Unrivaled assets for Unreal &amp; Unity</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IjGKTsdpquI" title="Humble Bundle Presents: The Supreme Unreal &amp; Unity Game Dev Bundle" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Dive into an asset collection that offers the widest range of stylized towns, buildings, and more with The Supreme Unreal & Unity Game Dev Bundle! Save time and money by accessing this library of 50+ asset sets, ranging from medieval Viking villages to deserted military outposts—specific standouts include <em>Whispering Grove Environment</em> and <em>Asian Dynasty Environment</em>. Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support the charity of your choice with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Music Production Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-music-production-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Total studio essentials for musicians</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Rock out or chill out to your own original music with our all-new Ultimate Music Production Bundle by IK Multimedia! Unlock your inner musician and create video game soundtracks, albums, and more with help from professional-quality plugins and programs like <em>Total Studio Essentials</em> and <em>MODO BASS Studio Upright</em>. Get the instruments and tools you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for—and help support Music Will with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Map Making MEGA Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/map-making-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>The complete cartographic collection</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about building maps to great game worlds? Say hello to the Map Making MEGA Bundle. Whether it's starships and solar systems, entire worlds, historical maps or fantasy floorplans, this treasure trove of assets and apps has what you need for your cartography. It includes practically everything ever released by map-making experts ProFantasy Software, including the latest CC3+, seventeen Cartographer's Annual, every symbol set, dungeon, city and overland app they've ever released. Map your world and help Save the Children at the same time!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The 2025 AWS, CompTIA, Azure,Google Cloud, and NVIDIA Certification Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/2025-aws-comptia-azuregoogle-cloud-and-nvidia-certification-bundle-software</link>
      <description>A certification for every platform</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[A new career is only a test or two away—our 2025 AWS, CompTIA, Azure, Google Cloud, and NVIDIA Certification Bundle has everything you need to study and prep. Get over 300 hours of expert-led content 420 full length practice exams and over 21,000 exam questions plus tons of Humble Bundle first time launch exclusives you will not find anywhere else. Ace your certification exams and help support Care.org with your purchase!</p> <p><span style="color: #ef9741;"><em>Mammoth Interactive has re-branded to MammothClub. Please note, all new courses will be on their new platform at MammothClub.com. For valued returning students, your existing courses are linked to your email and will be imported shortly. Their new site has achievements, AI tutors, and more.</em></span></p>]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>