<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 22:08:34 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Concept Art Training Bundle Encore</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/the-complete-concept-art-training-bundle-software-encore</link>
      <description>Art training from the pros at Learn Squared</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Reach new heights in concept art and more with our latest bundle from the experts at Learn Squared. This bundle is perfect for artists starting their journey and experienced creatives alike—learn essential skills and workflows, and advanced training. Bring 3D sequence illustrations to life using master tools like ZBrush and Photoshop. Standout courses include <em>Concept Art for Video Games</em>, <em>Concept Art in Unreal Engine 5</em>. That’s right—learn to develop original art in the uber popular game engine Unreal Engine 5! Don’t wait, get this curated collection of courses and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Freedom to create with CorelDRAW Graphics Suite 2024</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/freedom-to-create-with-coreldraw-graphics-suite-2024-software</link>
      <description>Elite graphic design suite supersale</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your creative toolkit with <em>CorelDRAW Graphics Suite 2024.</em> Save big too—more than $475 off MSRP! Get vector illustration, layout assistance, photo editing, and typography tools with this professional-level software. Pay what you want to create with freedom and help support the Children's Miracle Network via Extra Life with your purchase. Act fast—this special promotion won’t last long]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn Programming in 2025 MEGA Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/learn-programming-in-2025-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Program like a pro today</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learn to program like a pro with our latest Mega Bundle! This gigantic library of programming courses is designed to teach you the fundamentals of the craft and prepare you for a bright future in the field. Standout lessons include <em>Learn Vibe Coding with Cursor</em>, <em>Intro to Algorithms with Python</em>, <em>Intro to C++ Data Structures</em>, and more. Become an expert in a variety of programming fundamentals and help support NPower with your purchase! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Norton &amp; Laplink Solid Security Flash Sale</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/norton-laplink-solid-security-flash-sale-software</link>
      <description>Be everywhere at once with Norton VPN</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Don’t wait—protect your PC with our Norton Flash Sale Bundle! Get the latest edition of Norton Antivirus to stop threats before they strike and mask your digital footprint with Norton VPN. Act fast and also receive PCmover Pro Use 1 & 2 and DiskImage 64-bit—essential tools for backup, transfer, and security. Our all-new Norton Flash Sale is tough to beat—pay what you want to safeguard your computer and help support the American Cancer Society with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open World Adventures Kit</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/open-world-adventures-kit-software</link>
      <description>Expand your horizons with real-world assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your game creation with our latest asset bundle from Dekogon! Choose from a massive selection of premium-quality environments and set pieces—subways, safe houses, grocery stores, police stations, and more—with the versatile Open World Adventures Kit. Unlock game-ready assets like the <em>Military Training Facility</em>, <em>1996 Police Headquarters</em>, and others, perfect for expanding environmental storytelling and themed level design. Add style to your next project—and help support Whale and Dolphin Conservation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audio Odyssey Vol. 2</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audio-odyssey-vol-2-software</link>
      <description>Embark on an audio odyssey</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Want to level up the sound design on your next game or creative project? Stop wasting time and call in the heavy hitters with powerful asset packs like the <em>Anime Music Pack</em>, <em>Mutated Beings Sound FX Pack</em>, <em>Orchestral Ambient Music Pack</em>, and more. Set sail for savings and stellar sound with the Sound Odyssey Bundle from Ovani Sound—your go-to source for crafting the perfect audioscape. Pay what you want for this ultimate audio asset collection and help support the Children's Miracle Network with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate Linux Developer Collection by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-linux-developer-collection-packt-software</link>
      <description>Limitless possibilities in Linux</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Ultimate Linux Developer Collection Bundle by Packt offers budding IT professionals the tools they need to compete with the best in the field. Learn how to bend Linux to your will and create the most optimized operating systems around. This curated library of courses includes <em>Linux Foundation Certified System Administrator</em>, <em>Linux Essentials: Hands-On Course with Labs</em>, <em>Mastering Linux Admin with Rocky - A Hands-On Approach</em>, and more. Pay what you want and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opus FX: Superior Plugins &amp; Orchestral Elegance</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/opus-fx-superior-plugins-orchestral-elegance-software</link>
      <description>A sweet suite of sound</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Elevate your productions to new heights with Opus FX: Superior Plugins & Orchestral Elegance. This bundle unites cutting-edge audio plugins with a sweeping collection of orchestral samples, empowering you to craft breathtaking cinematic scores, rich soundscapes, and dramatic compositions. Perfect for music producers, composers, and sound designers who want to add professional polish, depth, and emotion to their projects, whether you’re scoring a film, producing epic trailers, or creating immersive game soundtracks. Make your magnum opus and support One Tree Planted with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Ultimate SFX &amp; VFX Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-sfx-vfx-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Turn up the volume with powerful assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Crank up the volume on your next game or creative project with The Ultimate SFX & VFX Bundle. Create the perfect audio-visual vibe with this massive library of royalty-free assets—featuring 100+ sounds and effects, from realistic medieval combat clinks and clanks to spot-on gunfire and more. Pay what you want for the tools you need to dial in your project’s SFX & VFX—and help support the Breast Cancer Research Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Unreal Engine Asset Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-engine-asset-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Unreal value. Unreal assets. Unreal results. </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/dCXjvoRdStA" title="" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>Calling all game developers—we’ve got an awesome collection of Unreal goodies for you! Get The Unreal Engine Asset Mega Bundle and bring life to your next adventure with stylized asset packs like the <em>Modern Art Museum Environment</em>, <em>American Village house</em>, and <em>Modular Amsterdam City Street</em>. Get the pro-quality assets you need to help bring your next Unreal Engine project to life, and help support Direct Relief with your purchase!<br></br>This bundle is redeemed via FAB and includes a Professional License, plus over 4500 meshes for your next project!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro Animation Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/pro-animation-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Animate like a big-time pro</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all animators—it’s time to level up your digital toolbox! Prepare to be blown away by the ultimate animation bundle from Graphixly LLC! Pay what you want for the Moho Pro 12.5 Bundle featuring <em>100 Brushes Content Pack</em>, <em>Characters Content Pack</em>, and <em>School Days Content Pack</em>. Take your skills from novice to pro in no time and help support No Kid Hungry with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Miniac presents An Intergalactic SkullForge STL Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/miniac-presents-an-intergalactic-skullforge-stl-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Models from galaxies far, far away</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Passionate about printables? Miniac presents the Intergalactic SkullForge STL Bundle. Pay what you want and get 20+ hot figure sets that bring life to your games—spend hours perfecting your own playables then show them off to your friends! Print, paint, and customize your own model figures from galaxies far, far away. Add new companions to your collection and help support Oceana with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>