<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 01:22:24 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>Leadership and Project Management in the Software Development Workplace</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/leadership-and-project-management-in-software-development-workplace-software</link>
      <description>Great leaders always have a plan</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Level up your project management and leadership skills with this comprehensive bundle of courses by Packt. Track the progress of your team, learn cyber security best practices, and analyze valuable data quickly with courses like <em>The Complete Project Management Fundamentals Course</em>, <em>Data Science, Analytics, & AI for Business & the Real World</em>, <em>Risk Management for Cyber Security Managers</em>, and more! Get the expert advice and knowledge you seek, and help support Alzheimer's Research UK with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Godot 2025 Course Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-godot-2025-course-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Go get the ultimate Godot bundle </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Learning everything there is to know about Godot is simple with this comprehensive bundle. Perfect for beginners and experienced developers alike, it covers foundational concepts, programming patterns, shaders, and mechanics like crafting shops and state machines. Create diverse games, such as roguelikes, Metroidvanias, and tower defense games, using the latest Godot 4 features. Build engaging experiences with multiplayer functionality, procedural generation, and fully-fledged game systems, including civilization-style mechanics. Explore mobile game development, narrative-driven walking simulators, and visually striking projects with custom plugins and advanced optimization techniques. Start your game development journey today while supporting educational charities!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elites: Creator&#39;s Superbundle 4000+ Assets</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/elites-creators-superbundle-4000-assets-software</link>
      <description>4,000+ reasons this bundle rocks</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/3SnvUZZwpG4?si=xTRh3e5D0Z7OlSYa" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br>So many assets—it’s mind-bending! Game developers, build your worlds with this amazing bundle of 4,000+ assets! Crafted from the top Unreal Engine market sellers’ best-selling products, this high-quality collection features massive environments, prefabs, blueprints, tools, props, animations, SFX, and more for use in Unreal Engine, Unity, and beyond. Highlighted by the Gothic Interior Megapack and Pharaoh's Legacy: Egyptian Temple Megapack, this bundle has everything you need to bring your game to life. Plus, your purchase helps support Make-A-Wish America!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Concept Art Training Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/the-complete-concept-art-training-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Art training from the pros at Learn Squared</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Reach new heights in concept art and more with our latest bundle from the experts at Learn Squared. This bundle is perfect for artists starting their journey and experienced creatives alike—learn essential skills and workflows, and advanced training. Bring 3D sequence illustrations to life using master tools like ZBrush and Photoshop. Standout courses include <em>Concept Art for Video Games</em>, <em>Concept Art in Unreal Engine 5</em>. That’s right—learn to develop original art in the uber popular game engine Unreal Engine 5! Don’t wait, get this curated collection of courses and help support Girls Who Code with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS Cloud Engineer Accelerator: From Zero to Certified by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/aws-cloud-engineer-accelerator-from-zero-to-certified-packt-software</link>
      <description>AWS cloud engineering for everyone</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Harnessing the power of cloud computing and storage continues to be an industry trend with real staying power—supercharge your career prospects and get the AWS Cloud Engineer Accelerator Bundle by Packt. Learn the skills and knowledge you need to succeed with professional quality courses like <em>Mastering AWS CDK - Coding Cloud Architectures</em>, <em>Mastering AWS SAM and Lambda - A Complete Hands-on Journey</em>, and more! Get the tools to succeed in cloud engineering and help support Alzheimer's UK! ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pro-Level Photography with Anthropics</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/pro-level-photography-with-anthropics-software</link>
      <description>Your photos never looked this good</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get your cameras ready—it’s time to shoot some amazing photographs. Our latest bundle offers pro-level photography applications from the experts at Anthropics. This collection is perfect for seasoned professionals and novices looking to up their photography game. Focus on a variety of topics with stand-out classes like <em>PortraitPro</em>, <em>LandscapePro</em>, <em>LandscapePro Studio</em>, and more. Take your hobby to the next level and support the Save The Children Fund with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Your Own Games In Unreal Engine 5 from GameDev.tv</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/make-your-own-games-in-unreal-engine-5-from-gamedevtv-software</link>
      <description>From gamer to game developer</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Are you curious about turning your passion for gaming into a career in game development? Our latest bundle with GameDev.tv will help teach you how to use Unreal Engine 5 and get you started on an exciting new adventure. Master the universally beloved game engine with our comprehensive bundle composed of industry-leading courses like <em>Unreal Engine 5 C++: Make Your Own Action Combat Game</em>, <em>Unreal Engine 5 Blueprints: First Person Shooter</em>, and more! Start creating and help support Direct Relief with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royalty Free Music, SFX &amp; More from GameDev Market 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/royalty-free-music-sfx-and-more-from-gamedev-market-2025-software</link>
      <description>Pitch perfect sounds, loops &amp; more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Create the perfect audioscape for your next game with this bundle of professional quality sounds from GameDev Market! This massive library features over 40 hours of audio tracks and more than 6000 individual sound effects to bring your game to life. Craft exhilarating boss battle music with the <em>Boss Battles & Combat Music</em>, excite players with addicting loot tunes with the <em>Game Music Treasury</em>, and bring explosions and more to life with the <em>Urban Destruction Demolition Debris & Explosions</em>. Get the assets you need to achieve the sound you’re looking for, and help support Hilarity For Charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 20:45:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Learn to Code Bundle 2025</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-learn-to-code-bundle-2025-software</link>
      <description>Learn to code games like a pro</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Achieve your New Year's resolution and learn to code! This comprehensive curriculum will help you level up your skills with courses like Unreal Engine 5.5 Game Developer's Toolbox - Essential Templates and Assets, Godot 4 Game Creator's Pack - Essential Templates for Instant Game Development, and many more. Our collection of 40+ courses includes Humble Bundle-exclusive content available only to our community. Familiarize yourself with popular tools like Python and Unreal Engine, all while supporting Direct Relief with your purchase!  ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2025 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>