<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Go Humble! RSS SOFTWARE</title>
    <link>https://feuerlord2.github.io/Humble-RSS-Site/</link>
    <description>Awesome RSS Feeds about HumbleBundle software bundles!</description>
    <managingEditor>DanielWinterEmsdetten+rss@gmail.com (Daniel Winter)</managingEditor>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 01:51:31 +0000</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>SampleTraxx Everything Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/sampletraxx-everything-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Award-winning samples have arrived</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7d0n41-LNaA?si=8oR8aVFyC2RK1gBB" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe> Rock out to 54 signature Sampletraxx sound libraries in one definitive collection—create music in any genre, from pop to electronic and beyond! 100% royalty-free, easy to download, and packed with the highest-quality sonics around. Download the entire 61.4 GB collection quickly and easily via the Pulse downloader, too. Iconic braams, earth-shattering impacts, and tension-building risers—all for a price you choose. Unlock a vast array of uniquely recorded and diverse instruments, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unreal Character Mega Pack by Maksim Bugrimov</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/unreal-character-mega-pack-maksim-bugrimov-software</link>
      <description>Unreal savings on Unreal Engine assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Calling all game developers—we’ve got you covered with a curated collection of custom characters from Maksim Bugrimov! This awesome Mega Pack is optimized for Unreal Engine—an industry-leading game engine for developers of all levels. Pay what you want for countless unique assets, including fantasy creatures and warriors, post-apocalyptic survivors, vikings, and more. Bring your dream characters to life with powerful Unreal creation tools, and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Build It Better: The Ultimate 3D CAD Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/build-it-better-ultimate-3d-cad-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Embrace the CAD-do attitude</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Lay a strong foundation in architecture with Build It Better: The Ultimate 3D CAD Bundle! Map out your future with Ashampoo 3D CAD Professional & Architecture 12’s easy-to-use interface and Office, Interior, and Kitchen Catalog extensions. Perfect for seasoned architects and students alike, this comprehensive library has everything you need to blueprint and plan the building of your dreams. Pay what you want to design the life you want to live, and help support the American Cancer Society!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultimate 3D &amp; VR Sculpting, Character &amp; Game Asset Creation Mega Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultimate-3d-vr-sculpting-character-game-asset-creation-mega-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Sculpt your future in VR &amp; 3D</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Unleash your creativity with the Ultimate 3D & VR Sculpting, Character & Game Asset Creation Mega Bundle from FastTrack Tutorials and Shapelab! This powerhouse collection combines cutting-edge sculpting software, in-depth tutorials, and premium 3D asset packs to help you design stunning characters, creatures, weapons, and props. Whether you’re diving into VR sculpting with Shapelab, mastering AAA character workflows, or expanding your asset library, this bundle equips you with everything you need to level up your 3D artistry.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Design Unlimited Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/design-unlimited-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Draw, render, design, and more</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/4eRHhqT2400?si=shKxtXlEV0v-HJ1t" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br></br> Calling all creatives and graphic designers—bring your vision to life without restrictions using CorelDRAW! Get professional graphic design software with vector, technical illustration, and CAD options to create logos, posters, drafts, and more. Plus, powerful AI applications like Vision FX, Vector FX, and Render FX are included! Level up your creative skills with elite software, and help support the Optimist International Foundation with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ultra Unreal Asset Megapack</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/ultra-unreal-asset-megapack</link>
      <description>Unearth Ultra Unreal Assets</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[The Ultra Unreal Asset Megapack brings together 38 high-end packs, each built for professional use, and designed to deliver AAA-quality visuals straight out of the box. From detailed cityscapes and gothic interiors to vibrant carnivals and sci-fi worlds, everything is fully modular, PBR-ready, and optimized for production. Also included is a Professional License, allowing use in large-scale studio and commercial projects. Expand your project or kickstart the next one, and support No Kid Hungry with your purchase. ]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Programming for Modern Developers by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/programming-for-modern-developers-packt-software</link>
      <description>Get Learn to Code with Rust, Complete Modern C++ (C++11/14/17) and more!</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Pave your way to new beginnings in computer science. Discover a complete suite of courses by Packt, tailored for modern developers beginning their journey in programming. Learn Java, C++, and Rust through detailed lessons designed to take you from square one to seasoned programming veteran. Build strong fundamentals with courses like Java from Beginner to Expert, Complete Modern C++, and Learn Java from Scratch: A Beginner's Guide Specialization—and help support Cancer Research UK with your purchase.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The GODOT Ultimate Asset Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/godot-ultimate-asset-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Godot for beginners &amp; experts</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Stop wondering what game to play next—start creating your own! Harness the power of Godot, the ultimate open-source creation engine! Pay what you want to access professional-quality content for Godot’s latest engine, including ancient cathedrals, stylized pirate port cities, dynamic fighting stages, and more. Perfect for beginners and experienced devs alike—start developing your own 2D and 3D games today! Get the assets you need to help bring your game to life, and help support Save The Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete Unreal Engine 5.7 + Assets Deluxe Bundle+</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-unreal-engine-57-assets-deluxe-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Create and excite with Unreal Engine </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[<iframe width="400" height="200" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ee57nG4aSuE?si=kA36zqa-aVciMXAl" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen></iframe><br><br>Pay what you want for an unrivaled bundle of Unreal Engine 5.7 assets, lessons, and more from Mammoth Club. Learn from 45+ courses designed to specifically fast-track your progression as a game dev master.   Become an asset-independent creator with massive VR, AR, 2D, and 3D libraries at your fingertips. Build professional-quality games featuring cinematic sequences and intelligent physics with an epic collection of environmental packs compatible with Lumen, Nanite, and procedural generation. Unlock powerful assets and help support charity with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AudioHero&#39;s Largest Cinematic Creator Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/audioheros-largest-cinematic-creator-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Royalty free music sure sounds nice</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Add professional-quality polish to your streams, YouTube videos, podcasts, and more with a gigantic bundle of licensed tracks and worldwide rights. One download gives you royalty-free music ranging from Arcade Anthems to Blockbuster Beasts. In this Humble exclusive, you’ll also unlock the Action Hero, Prodigy, and Starter Plans! Get a massive library of over 300,000 royalty-free songs and sounds from AudioHero Inc.—complete with licenses included—all for a price you choose! Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Digital Artist Tutorial &amp; Learning Bundle</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/digital-artist-tutorial-learning-bundle-software</link>
      <description>Execute your vision from concept to completion</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Go from indie to big-time with the Mastering Digital Art: From Concept to Completion Bundle. With powerful tools like Hard-Surface Masters Vol. 1 and Substance Masters Vol. 4, learn how digital art comes to life with bold textures, enhanced sculpting, and so much more. Plus, JROTools included ZBrush Masters Vol. 2, a tutorial series highlighting the workflows and techniques of top ZBrush artists. Add professional-quality polish to your next project and help support Save the Children with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Complete DevOps &amp; MLOps Mastery Bundle by Packt</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/complete-devops-mlops-mastery-bundle-packt-software</link>
      <description>Master machine learning operations</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Get a leg up on the competition with practical machine learning skills from The Complete DevOps & MLOps Mastery Bundle. We’ve teamed up with the experts at Packt to assemble a comprehensive library of courses that include some of the most commonly used platforms in the industry. Pay what you want for hot courses like Python for DevOps: The Ultimate Hands-On Guide and Azure DevOps and Continuous Delivery with Git. Learn the skills you need from industry leaders, and help support The Against Malaria Foundation with your purchase!]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neon &amp; Noir - Elite Photos with Luminar Neo</title>
      <link>https://humblebundle.com/software/neon-noir-elite-photos-with-luminar-neo-software</link>
      <description>Next-gen photo editing at your fingertips </description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[Take your photos to the next level—introducing the Neon & Noir: Elite Photos with Luminar Neo Bundle. Luminar Neo by Skylum Software is an easy-to-use tool that helps you edit and enhance your images with ease! Within this exceptional bundle, you’ll gain access to a how-to-use course, the base software, expressive presets, and dynamic overlays—alongside standout add-ons like Tranquil Dawn Skies and City Lights. Picture-perfect edits at a price you’ll love. Plus, a portion of your purchase helps support Code.org.]]></content:encoded>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>